<FTL>

<event name="FINISH_BEACON_DEEPONE">
	<text id="finish_beacon"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Explore.</text>
		<event load="EXIT_FILLER_LIST"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="OUTPOST_LIST_DEEPONE">
	<event load="EMPTY_DEEPONE"/>
	<event load="FEDERATION_OUTPOST_DEEPONE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="FEDERATION_OUTPOST_DEEPONE" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_outpost" global="true">
		<color r="233" g="123" b="74" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip id="map_outpost_unvisited"/>
		<visitedTooltip id="map_outpost_visited"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You've discovered a Federation outpost! Though, you're a little shocked to see one in Deep One space.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_FED_OUTPOST" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true" blue="false" req="challenge_level" lvl="0" max_group="1">
		<text>Contact the outpost.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You hail, and to your shock, a Deep One answers! "Welcome... Federation Ship. Please, make... your needs known." You don't know how, but the Federation must have convinced them to keep this outpost running.</text>
			<damage amount="-7"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request fuel.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A box of fuel, covered in damp handprints, is brought onboard.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="fuel" min="7" max="7"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request ammunition.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A shipment of ammunition, covered in damp handprints, is delivered to your ship.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="missiles" min="4" max="4"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request droneparts.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A shipment of droneparts, covered in damp handprints, is delivered to your ship.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="drones" min="3" max="3"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
				<text>(Deep One) Have your Deep One bargain for a bit of everything.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It only takes the sight of your Deep One to light up the outpost captain's face. "Kin? Aboard a Multiverse ship... For you, friend... anything."</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="fuel" min="3" max="3"/>
						<item type="missiles" min="2" max="2"/>
						<item type="drones" min="1" max="1"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" blue="false" req="challenge_level" lvl="1" max_group="1">
		<text>Contact the outpost.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You hail, and to your shock, a Deep One answers! "Welcome... Federation Ship. Please, make... your needs known." You don't know how, but the Federation must have convinced them to keep this outpost running.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request repairs.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Deep Ones send a team to repair your ship. You hope they don't get water in any of the electronics...</text>
					<damage amount="-7"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request fuel.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A box of fuel, covered in damp handprints, is brought onboard.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="fuel" min="7" max="7"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request ammunition.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A shipment of ammunition, covered in damp handprints, is delivered to your ship.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="missiles" min="4" max="4"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request droneparts.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A shipment of droneparts, covered in damp handprints, is delivered to your ship.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="drones" min="3" max="3"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
				<text>(Deep One) Have your Deep One bargain for a bit of everything.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It only takes the sight of your Deep One to light up the outpost captain's face. "Kin? Aboard a Multiverse ship... For you, friend... anything."</text>
					<damage amount="-3"/>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="fuel" min="3" max="3"/>
						<item type="missiles" min="2" max="2"/>
						<item type="drones" min="1" max="1"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" blue="false" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="2">
		<text>Attack the outpost!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You've decided, instead of receiving help, to attack this outpost full of friendlies...</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="EMPTY_DEEPONE">
	<text load="TEXT_EMPTY_DEEPONE"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="TEXT_EMPTY_DEEPONE">
	<text>Upon arriving at the beacon, you spot a decrepit, abandoned store. To your disappointment it appears to have been picked clean by the Deep Ones.</text>
	<text>The beacon here appears to be empty. Though, you can't help but feel like you're always being watched when you're in Deep One space...</text>
	<text>You're immediately greeted by an object whizzing past at an indescribable speed. As quickly as it came, it goes, and you're not sure what to make of the blue blur.</text>
	<text>It's quickly assessed that there's nothing of value here. As the FTL charges, you think you see something move outside, but scans of the area don't seem to pick anything up. Must've been your imagination.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddtruemystery" global="false">
		<color r="120" g="144" b="156" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You can't say why you felt compelled to come here, and you don't see anything out of the ordinary, but... you feel that something's wrong. Deeply, deeply wrong.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice req="loc_mysterious_entity_seen" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" hidden="true" blue="false">
		<text>Check behind you.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You quickly turn around, but there's... nothing there. There's nothing there, right?</text>
			<variable name="loc_mysterious_entity_seen" op="set" val="1"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Turn back around.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You turn back to face outside your cabin window, but that crushing sense of dread hasn't yet left.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check behind you again.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Sweat begins to bead as you swiftly turn around once more. Again, nothing...</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Turn back around, again.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Refusing to let paranoia get the better of you, you shake your head and return to staring out the window.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Blink.</text>
										<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_MIDDLE"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Scan the room.</text>
								<event>
									<text>There's something wrong, there has to be. Your eyes dart around to every corner of the room, looking for something, anything, to prove you aren't just going crazy. After a few minutes of frantic searching you're about to give up, when you finally see... it. Something's in the airvent.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Inspect the airvent.</text>
										<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_NEUTRAL_END"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Stare outside the window and try to relax.</text>
						<event>
							<text>There's nothing outside but the stars. You take slight comfort in the fact that no matter where you go, the stars are always there to keep you company.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Blink.</text>
								<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_MIDDLE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Glance around the room.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You glance around the room cautiously, but don't see anything out of the ordinary.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Turn back around.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You turn back to face outside your cabin window, but that crushing sense of dread hasn't yet left.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Check behind you again.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Sweat begins to bead as you swiftly turn around once more. Again, nothing...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Turn back around, again.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Refusing to let paranoia get the better of you, you shake your head and return to staring out the window.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Blink.</text>
												<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_MIDDLE"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Scan the room.</text>
										<event>
											<text>There's something wrong, there has to be. Your eyes dart around to every corner of the room, looking for something, anything, to prove you aren't just going crazy. After a few minutes of frantic searching you're about to give up, when you finally see... it. Something's in the airvent.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Inspect the airvent.</text>
												<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_NEUTRAL_END"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Stare outside the window and try to relax.</text>
								<event>
									<text>There's nothing outside but the stars. You take slight comfort in the fact that no matter where you go, the stars are always there to keep you company.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Blink.</text>
										<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_MIDDLE"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_mysterious_entity_seen" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Sensing déjà vu, check behind you.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Huh. There's nothing there. Suppose nothing's wrong after all! You have time to do something on the ship.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
                <text>Check the storage.</text>
                <event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
            </choice>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Do nothing.</text>
                <event/>
            </choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_MIDDLE">
	<text>The stars blink back.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They... what?</text>
		<event>
			<text>Just then, the power goes out! You hear the other crew shuffling about in their cabins nearby, but your room is completely dark save for the infinitesimally faint light emanating from the ether outside your window.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Glance outside the window.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone. The stars are gone.</text>
					<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
					<playMusic>ddtracklightslament</playMusic>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="1" blue="false">
						<text>Scream.</text>
						<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_BAD_END"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
						<text>Scream.</text>
						<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_BAD_END_NOCREW"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Sit in silence, refusing to look back outside.</text>
				<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_MIDDLE_TWO"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_MIDDLE_TWO">
	<text>You wait. Then, you wait some more. As time passes, you feel your paranoia worsening; the darkness feels as if it's growing darker and the silence is becoming deafening. Just as you get up to look for your crew, you hear a noise come from the corner of the room, between you and the door. Something's been in the room with you.</text>
	<modifyPursuit amount="2"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand that they reveal themselves.</text>
		<event>
			<text>No response is made. As far as you can tell, no movement is made either.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Repeat yourself; who goes there?</text>
				<event>
					<text>You hesitate and repeat your demand feebly. For a moment, there's silence and you begin to assume you must've just misheard something. That was before the heavy footsteps began pounding towards your direction.</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="1" blue="false">
						<text>Scream.</text>
						<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_BAD_END"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
						<text>Scream.</text>
						<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_BAD_END_NOCREW"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Go silent.</text>
				<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_GOOD_END"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Keep quiet.</text>
		<event load="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_GOOD_END"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_BAD_END">
	<text>You wake up to the sound of one of your crew screaming. You rush to their room, along with your other crew, but none of you are prepared for the horrifying scene before you. They've been completely eviscerated, their blood sprayed along every crevice of the room and their face left so terribly disfigured you wouldn't know who you were looking at without their nametag. You're about to throw up when you notice a set of sector coordinates has been written on the wall in their blood... Whatever bastard did this clearly wants you to head here, and you don't plan on disappointing them. They won't get away with this.</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND</changeBackground>
	<playMusic/>
	<removeCrew>
		<clone>false</clone>
		<text>Whatever did this was smart enough to disable your clone bay and destroy your DNA backups too. Dammit...</text>
	</removeCrew>
	<variable name="coords_enlightened" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<event name="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_BAD_END_NOCREW">
	<text>You wake up to the sound of... someone screaming. You're the only one on this ship, though... cautious, you check your ship's systems, but something's off. The same string of characters and numbers repeats itself regardless of the console or system, and you realize you recognize it to be a set of coordinates. You're not sure what's going on, but whatever's done this really wants your attention... still, there's no lasting damage to any of your systems. Perhaps these coordinates are worth visiting, eventually.</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND</changeBackground>
	<playMusic/>
	<variable name="coords_enlightened" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<event name="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_NEUTRAL_END">
	<text>As soon as you approach the air vent, the power goes out! Whatever's in there makes the loudest getaway in history but there's nothing you can do without being able to see. Moments later, you begin to hear some sort of... tearing... something's ripping through the very hull of the ship! You yell to your crew to get their oxygen masks and, sure enough, the hole in the hull must've come from whatever was in the vent because all the oxygen in the ship is immediately vented out. The power swiftly returns in the nick of time and you're able to send some crew out to patch up the hole and restore the ship's oxygen, but that's not the end of it. Your crew claim that there's sector coordinates "written" on the hull, crudely cut into the ship. You surmise that it's most likely a trap seeing that whatever did this couldn't possibly have had good intentions, but you're intrigued nonetheless and log the coords down.</text>
	<damage amount="6"/>
	<variable name="coords_enlightened" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<event name="ENLIGHTENED_QUEST_START_GOOD_END">
	<text>You stay silent and, for a while, nothing happens. That is, until the power returns! Overwrought, you search around the room with an intense, paranoia-fueled fervour but nothing seems to be out of the ordinary. You're replaying the sound you heard whilst the lights were out in your head when one of your crew rushes into the room. Then another, and another. Apparently, everyone had similar experiences; an overwhelming sense of dread followed by waiting in the darkness and refusing to speak to whatever was there. One particularly flustered crew member, however, reports that the being in the darkness actually spoke to them... nonstop, in fact. They claim it kept repeating a string of numbers, over, and over, and over, and over... until the power returned and nothing was there. Familiar with the patterning, you recognize the string of numbers as a set of sector coordinates. Whatever mysterious entity, or group of entities, is behind this clearly wants you to go there; but who's to say what's waiting.</text>
	<variable name="coords_enlightened" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<eventList name="STORELIST_DEEPONE">
	<event load="STOREEVENT_ALIENS"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_RIDDLE"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_WAR"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_STANDARD"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_INSULT"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_FED_AUTO"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_ROCK_MISSION"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_PIRATE_REFUELING"/>
	<event load="STOREEVENT_PIRATE_SECURITY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_RIDDLE" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_deepone" global="false">
		<color r="255" g="245" b="175" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>There appears to be a Deep One merchant ship at this beacon, a welcome sight to say the least.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A giddy Deep One responds to your hail, "Welcome... potential customer. Should you... care to trade, you must... solve my riddle."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Accept.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"They have..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>"...eight fingers."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"They also have a..."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>"...pair of thumbs."</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event>
													<text>"But..."</text>
													<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event>
															<text>"...they aren't alive."</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Continue...</text>
																<event>
																	<text>"What... are they?"</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>You, if you don't shut the hell up and start trading.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>The Deep One frowns, "You must be... fun at parties. Fine, feel free... to look around."</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Continue...</text>
																				<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
																		<text>(Deep One) "They are... a pair of... gloves!"</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>The merchant's ecstatic about someone getting his riddle right, and he even gives you some resources on the house!</text>
																			<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Continue...</text>
																				<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>We don't have time for this.</text>
												<event>
													<text>"A terrible... shame." They close communications.</text>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Oh, man! I hate riddles! Attack the merchant.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You hate riddles... THAT much?" You move in to attack the riddling Deep One merchant, and it prepares to defend itself.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Maybe... next time, then." They close communications.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Yeah, a welcome sight... a ship to blow up!</text>
		<event>
			<text>The merchant ship notices your refusal to accept hails as you approach and turns hostile. Prepare for combat.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You ignore the merchant ship, and the merchant ship ignores you.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_WAR" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_deepone" global="false">
		<color r="255" g="245" b="175" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>Upon arriving at the beacon, several Deep One ships whiz past your view. Then, several more... there's an entire armada here! You glance around, looking for the merchant ship, and finally spot it within a crowd of other ships. It'd be suicide to attack it with such a fleet at the ready.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Approach the ship and hail.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The merchant accepts your hail, but he appears to be busy packing something in the background.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Inquire as to what he's doing.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Preparing to... head off for war. We all are, were it not... obvious. The... Theocracy has been ruthless, and we... don't intend to stand idly by."</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="rock_commando">
						<text>(Lost Sun) Your commando wishes to speak.</text>
						<event>
							<text>With a remorseful look in their eyes, your member of the Lost Suns steps forward to speak to the merchant, "Of smoldered rock or scaly flesh, it matters not to the Theocracy. We are both seen as a disease, with this 'holy' crusade being their attempt at a cure. We are bound by this, the Elders' ire, and as such I see you as no lesser than any Lost Sun; to me, we are kin, and we could use your strength in the battles to come."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>The merchant seems to have really taken your commando's speech to heart. You can see them tearing up a bit, but, for a moment, they don't reply. Eventually, they break the silence, "Your words... speak true... kin. Yet, this is a fight that I cannot... abandon. My people here, they... need me. Should there be... anything I can do for you, though, let it be... known."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Glance outside at his repair team and ask if you could have them go to work on your hull.</text>
										<event>
											<text>He nods his head and sends his team to repair your hull. You're offered a chance to shop while they get to work.</text>
											<damage amount="-14"/>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Glance at the Deep One lighting fixtures that lay uninstalled in the corner of the room.</text>
										<event>
											<text>He catches your glance and responds, "An... impressive feat of technology, our luminescence... Should you install them... I'm sure you'll find the results to be... satisfactory." You take him up on his offer and take a moment to shop while they're being installed.</text>
											<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Glance at the Deep One weapon sitting on a nearby shelf and ask if you can have it.</text>
										<event>
											<text>He seems to ponder the request for a moment, and then accepts. "The... Jellyfish Beam. Among the first... weapons created by our ancient kin. They studied... existing ion technology, and then concentrated it... ensuring it would never miss its intended target. Feel... free to shop as I have it installed."</text>
											<weapon name="DEEPONE_JELLYFISH"/>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Offer to help fund the war effort.</text>
						<event>
							<text>His face lights up at your generosity.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-40" max="-40"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"You are... a kind soul. Should you be... willing, I'd like to employ one of my... finest to protect you during these... turbulent times in exchange for this... altruism. Of course, you're welcome to... shop as well."</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Offer a mighty sum to help fund the war effort.</text>
						<event>
							<text>His eyes go wide at your generosity.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-80" max="-80"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Your kindness is... truly heartening. I'll see to it that we... slow down the rebels for you while on our... crusade. Please, buy... whatever you need." You're not sure how he knew you were on the run from the rebels but you appreciate the gesture nonetheless.</text>
									<modifyPursuit amount="-3"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Offer to practically pay for the whole damn war yourself.</text>
						<event>
							<text>He jumps back in shock as a pile of scrap larger than himself is teleported into the room next to him.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-120" max="-120"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"You either... really love us or... really hate the Theocracy. As such... I find no greater irony than entrusting you with... their general, whom we've captured. He's quite... obedient, after the hell we've... put him through. Feel free... to shop and then do with him... as you see fit."</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="rock_crusader"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Request to shop.</text>
						<event>
							<text>He doesn't turn around, but hurriedly mutters "Yes, yes..." and ushers you inside.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Request to shop.</text>
				<event>
					<text>He doesn't turn around, but hurriedly mutters "Yes, yes..." and ushers you inside.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Heh, "Suicide" is my middle name! Attack that merchant!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Well, Federation "Suicide" Renegade, you're able to make it about eleven seconds before you're spotted and asked to make your intentions known. You respond with two middle fingers and are promptly shot at by over a dozen ships. Needless to say, you don't reach the merchant.</text>
			<damage amount="16"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking" lvl="2">
		<text>(Upg. Cloaking) Cloak, and attempt to rob the merchant ship.</text>
		<event load="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_WAR_CLOAKING"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You ignore the merchant ship and are not bothered as the FTL charges.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_WAR_CLOAKING">
	<event>
		<text>In an act that can only be described as a miracle, your cloaking manages to last long enough for your crew to dock with the merchant ship, rob them blind, and then get out of there without anybody noticing a thing. Poor sap was busy packing while muttering some nonsense about going off to war.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your cloaking lasts long enough for your crew to dock with the merchant ship, but as they begin to start taking things as they see fit you realize your cloaking's about to give out. You hurry them back with their light haul, but, as you expected, your cloaking wears off during the getaway! The merchant realizes what's happened and requests immediate fire support. A few shots graze your hull as you escape, but, overall, it could've been much worse.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
		<damage amount="4"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Unfortunately, your cloaking gives out before you even reach the merchant ship. Startled by your sudden appearance, the nearby ships attack you, shredding your hull as you try to make your getaway.</text>
		<damage amount="11"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Unfortunately, your cloaking gives out before you even reach the merchant ship. Startled by your sudden appearance, the nearby ships attack you, shredding your hull as you try to make your getaway.</text>
		<damage amount="11"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_STANDARD" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_deepone" global="false">
		<color r="255" g="245" b="175" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>There's a Deep One merchant vessel here, who promptly hails you upon your entrance to the beacon and offers to trade.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Look around and shop.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The lights within the Deep One store are practically blinding, and you can't get over the overwhelming smell of must and fish. Just as you think this assault on your senses can't get any worse, the clerk just screams at the ceiling for no discernible reason. You try your best to shop quickly.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Blow them up!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You've decided to attack the trader.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_INSULT" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_deepone" global="false">
		<color r="255" g="245" b="175" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You're hailed the second you enter the beacon...</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Accept the hail.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Two Deep Ones show up on the monitor, but before you can say anything they just start screaming. Then, they... keep screaming.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Stare in disbelief.</text>
				<event>
					<text>After a few minutes of more screaming, the Deep Ones suddenly cut communications and promptly refuse further hails. Such civility...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Scream back.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You scream at the Deep Ones, who go silent and recoil in shock. One speaks, "Such... barbarism." to which the other responds "We knew Feds were... stupid, yet I still find myself utterly... astonished." You shrug, and they cut communications. You go to leave when, suddenly, their weapons come to life! Talk about barbarism...</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
				<text>(Deep One) Have your Deep One scream back.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Deep One screams and the two opposing Deep Ones are taken aback. "Such... eloquence." claims one, "Such... beauty!" proclaims the other. They seem starstruck, and offer to trade. Nothing around here makes any sense to you...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse the hail.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Whatever this ship wants, you aren't interested. You decline their request to hail, and their weapons spring to life in response!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_ATTACK" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_ROCK_FIGHT">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="STORE_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="STORE_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="STORE_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_WIN">
	<text>The colony thanks you a thousand times over for your heroism and offers to trade.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_deepone" global="false">
		<color r="255" g="245" b="175" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<img planet="PLANET_MOONS"/>
	<text>There's a Deep One trading colony on a nearby moon here, a member of which promptly hails you upon your entrance to the beacon and offers to trade.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Move in to trade.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're almost there when you detect an FTL signature nearby, it appears that a Rock ship has jumped into the beacon! They move in to attack the colony, whose anti-ship batteries can't penetrate the Rocks' hull armor.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_ATTACK" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Protect the colony!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Not today, you crazed zealots. You prepare to intercept the now hostile Rock ship.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Betray the colony and offer the Rocks some ammunition to make their job a little easier.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Rocks take the ammunition and chuckle.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="missiles" min="-8" max="-8"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice>
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_BETRAYAL"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Stay out of it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You decide to not intervene. You're sure you've just left the colony to a terrible fate, but it's not any of your business.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_CRYSTAL">
				<text>(Crystal) Have your Crystal hail the Rocks.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Upon viewing your Crystal, the Rocks go into hysterics; screaming and smashing everything around them. In the process, one of them must have accidentally hit the button that triggers the FTL, as the ship promptly jumps out of the beacon. The colony is about as dumbfounded as you are, but they thank you and offer to trade nonetheless.</text>
					<instantEscape/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the colony.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're not interested in trading right now.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="STOREEVENT_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_BETRAYAL">
	<event>
		<text>You see them bundle the missiles together with whatever material they had laying around and promptly launch the makeshift bomb at the colony. It's completely leveled by the explosion, and debris is sent flying everywhere. You scrap some, and the Rock ship leaves; satisfied with their work.</text>
		<instantEscape/>
		<autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
		<choice>
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>However, moments later an explosion rocks their ship! They must've accidentally set a missile off but, suspecting that you sent them faulty ammunition, the Rocks turn on you. Meanwhile, the colony's inhabitants collectively figure this must've been a planned reverse-betrayal and are rooting for you.</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<enemyDamage amount="6"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="STORE_LOAD_DEEPONE">
	<store>STORE_DEEPONE</store>
	<text>Before you shop, you still have some time to do something else aboard the ship.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DEEPONE">
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_FRIENDLY"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DREAD"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_FRIENDLY" unique="true">
	<text>There's a colony of Deep Ones at this beacon, and upon your approach they beckon you to land.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We have some time to spare, agree to land.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You approach the Deep One colony with caution, but your wariness is quickly proven to be unwarranted. They explain that they so rarely see visitors and are ecstatic at your arrival, soon showering you with gifts! You return the favor with lavish stories of your exploits across the Multiverse, the Deep Ones' eyes further widening in wonder with each self-indulgent tale. Though you spend more time than you probably should, your crew appreciates the rare moment of respite.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We don't have any time to spare.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You explain to the Deep Ones that time is of the upmost importance in regards to your mission. They're saddened by your refusal, but they understand.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST">
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_STUFF"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_STUFF"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_STUFF"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_STUFF"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_REACTOR"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_REACTOR"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_DARKWEAPON"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_DARKDRONE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_STUFF">
	<text>You begin to make a mental note to have a word with the Federation engineers responsible for your ship's systems, but you're met with a strange sight once you get back to your room. An assorted pile of junk sits in the middle of it, a mess of scrap and resources that's somehow been planted here whilst leaving the rest of the room undisturbed. Your crew's as clueless about it as you are once you ask around, and the cameras seem to have been conveniently disabled during the incident. Though it makes you uneasy, you surmise that free scrap is free scrap and prepare to leave the beacon in a hurry.</text>
	<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_REACTOR">
	<text>You begin to make a mental note to have a word with the Federation engineers responsible for your ship's systems, but you're met with a strange sight once you get back to your room. A neatly stacked pile of reactor cores sits in the middle of it, a sizeable collection that's somehow been planted here whilst leaving the rest of the room undisturbed. Your crew's as clueless about it as you are once you ask around, and the cameras seem to have been conveniently disabled during the incident. Though it makes you uneasy, you surmise that free cores are free cores and prepare to leave the beacon in a hurry.</text>
	<upgrade amount="2" system="reactor"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_DARKWEAPON">
	<text>You begin to make a mental note to have a word with the Federation engineers responsible for your ship's systems, but you're met with a strange sight once you get back to your room. A peculiar piece of machinery sits in the middle of it, a weapon of ominous make that's somehow been planted here whilst leaving the rest of the room undisturbed. Your crew's as clueless about it as you are once you ask around, and the cameras seem to have been conveniently disabled during the incident. Though it makes you uneasy, you surmise that a free weapon is a free weapon and prepare to leave the beacon in a hurry.</text>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_WEAPONS"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST_DARKDRONE">
	<text>You begin to make a mental note to have a word with the Federation engineers responsible for your ship's systems, but you're met with a strange sight once you get back to your room. A peculiar piece of machinery sits in the middle of it, a drone of ominous make that's somehow been planted here whilst leaving the rest of the room undisturbed. Your crew's as clueless about it as you are once you ask around, and the cameras seem to have been conveniently disabled during the incident. Though it makes you uneasy, you surmise that a free drone is a free drone and prepare to leave the beacon in a hurry.</text>
	<drone name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_DRONES"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD" unique="true">
	<text>Immediately upon entering the system, your ship identifies a foreign mass materializing in the ship's hold. There's no ships nearby for anyone to have teleported from, so you suspect it's a false alarm, but nevertheless you approach the hold with a blaster in hand. Upon further inspection, your suspicions are quickly proven to be correct, as there's nothing out of order here.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DARKGOD_LIST"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST">
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_REWARD"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_REWARD"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_REWARD"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_NOTHING"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_LOST"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_ASSAULT"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_REWARD">
	<text>Your team makes a break for the exit, but they manage to stumble upon something they weren't expecting along the way: an Engi Separatist, simply standing there in the hallway. It wasn't here earlier... your crew ask it to identify itself, but it ignores them and instead addresses you directly, "I have been: -waiting- for you, Renegade. Our time here: is [short]." It turns to your crew, finally acknowledging them, "Quickly: -this- way." It leads your crew through the maze of hallways, confident in its movements, and, indeed, they manage to make it out much quicker than you expected. Once onboard, the Engi doesn't request to join your crew as much as it simply... does. You don't have any qualms with that, you suppose.</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="engi_separatist"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_NOTHING">
	<text>You don't say a word, but your team agrees with you. They quickly turn around and begin to sprint back the way they came but, to their bewilderment, they find the exit within the first couple minutes of backtracking. Though this endeavour has proven fruitless, at least your crew's okay.</text>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_LOST">
	<text>You decide it's time to pull out, but... where exactly is out? Your team spends what feels like hours trying to retrace their steps, until eventually they come across the initial T-shaped hallway they entered from. They barely make it out before the ship buckles for the last time, collapsing in on itself. The fleet's surely caught up to you in the meantime, and you've gotten absolutely nothing out of it, but at least your crew's safe.</text>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST_ASSAULT">
	<text>Your team doesn't struggle to find their way out, but they notice something odd as they approach the exit... the sound of footsteps, echoing towards them. Rapidly. They make a sprint for it as SOMETHING follows them at an impossible speed, and, though they barely manage to make it back onboard in time, you're not able to close the airlock before whatever was following them makes its way inside as well... just what in the hell IS this thing?</text>
	<playSound>ddilldrythkfog2</playSound>
	<boarders min="1" max="1" class="ddilldrythk_statue"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK" unique="true">
	<text>You're met with the sight of a Deep One wreck, its signatures completely cold but its lights as radiant as ever. There's no telling how long it's been here, and the hull seems to somehow be impenetrable to your ship's scans.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Inspect the inside of the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You send a team to explore the inside of a ship, though upon entering you can immediately tell that this place won't hold together much longer. With the time limit in mind, your team embarks; requesting your instructions in exploring the labyrinth.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Go... right.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your team copies and heads right. After a few minutes of silently wandering through the iridescent halls, your team reports a collective sense of dread amongst themselves. You don't think much of it at first, but then you begin to recognize a pattern in the turns your crew are making. It appears that these hallways loop endlessly, but... they haven't seen the entrance since, well, entering. Your crew begins to panic, and you hear the ship buckle. There's not much time left before it rips itself apart.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Assure them to keep going.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You reassure your team that everything is fine and encourage them to push forward. Begrudgingly, they begin to comply, but moments later they've stopped again. You've nearly returned to reassuring them when you notice the tall, motionless shadow of a figure just out of view ahead of them. Is this the first hallway without a light?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Demand that they confront the figure.</text>
								<event>
									<text>With stern resolve, you demand that your crew confronts the figure ahead of them. Before they can even protest, however, the visuals on the call abruptly go down and not even a split second later all you can hear through the comms is screaming... followed by heavy footsteps. Both quickly grow fainter and it becomes apparent that your team has dropped their mics amidst the panic. All you can do is sit there in disbelief and wait.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Wait.</text>
										<event>
											<text>A few minutes go by and, miraculously, your team emerges from the wreck; still screaming and with a Deep One chasing in tow! You demand an explanation and though your crew is in hysterics, the Deep One begs to be given a chance to speak. As it turns out, he didn't mean to scare your team and was merely likewise shocked at the sight of outsiders on what remained of his ship. He explains that he's been drifting for a few days as a result of a collision tearing the engines apart, stranding him here and slowly depressurizing the ship. As if on cue, the ship buckles for the last time and collapses in on itself in the background. Disgruntled, and with nothing left for him here, he offers to join your crew to try to make amends for all the accidental fright he's caused.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Alright, it's definitely time to leave.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Maybe it's time to leave.</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Go... left.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your team copies and heads left. After a few minutes of silently wandering through the iridescent halls, they come across a couple rooms labeled in an alien tongue you don't recognize. You hear the ship begin to buckle, and it becomes apparent that you don't have time to explore both rooms.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Enter the dark room.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your crew heads into the room without any lighting, and quickly figure out that it's the ship's resource hold. They gather what loot they can and prepare to leave before the inside of the ship comes crashing down around them. Mission successful.</text>
							<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Enter the illuminated room.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your crew enters the blindingly bright room, but are unsure of what to make of their surroundings. The room appears to twist in one's peripheral vision, each corner never remaining constant unless focused upon. One thing that's certain is that the room is empty, save for the dismantled remains of an Engi. Though, upon further inspection, it's not a form you've ever seen any Engi take... Black and purple, with no arms, and strange spikes jutting out its back; its nanites ever shifting, akin to the room around it.</text>
							<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DISPARITY">
								<text>(Disparity Crew) Wait a minute. You know exactly what this is!</text>
								<event>
									<text>These are the remains of a Disparity Elite! You have your team grab them and pull out, and, once aboard, your own Disparity crew member gets to work on putting them together again. Once finished, the newly rebuilt Disparity Elite stutters a few words in thanks, "[B-b-b-brothers...] -here...?- T-t-thank: y-you..." They'll take some time to fully recover, but, as thanks, they offer to join your crew!</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="disparity_engidefault"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_SEPARATIST">
								<text>(Separatist Crew) Your Separatist seems to recognize the design.</text>
								<event>
									<text>They speak to you through the comms, "I have: heard -tell- of these ones. I think: I can [fix] them." You have your team grab the dismantled Engi and pull out, and, once aboard, your Separatist crew member gets to work on putting them together again. Once finished, the newly rebuilt Engi stutters a few more words in thanks, "[B-b-b-brothers...] -here...?- T-t-thank: y-you..." They'll take some time to fully recover, but, as thanks, the strange Engi offers to join your crew!</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="disparity_engidefault"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>I don't know what this is.</text>
								<event>
									<text>As strange as it is, there's nothing you can do. You hear as the ship buckles... this will have to be a mystery for another day.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>It's time to leave.</text>
										<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
						<text>(Deep One) Your Deep One offers to read the labels for you.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your Deep One explains that the dark room is labelled 'HOLD' and that the illuminated one is, quite literally, labelled 'DANGER METAL MAN'.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Enter the hold.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Your crew heads into the hold. They gather what loot they can and prepare to leave before the inside of the ship comes crashing down around them. Mission successful.</text>
									<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Enter the strangely labeled room.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Your crew enters the blindingly bright room, but are unsure of what to make of their surroundings. The room appears to twist in one's peripheral vision, each corner never remaining constant unless focused upon. One thing that's certain is that the room is empty, save for the dismantled remains of an Engi. Though, upon further inspection, it's not a form you've ever seen any Engi take... Black and purple, with no arms, and strange spikes jutting out its back; its nanites ever shifting, akin to the room around it.</text>
									<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DISPARITY">
										<text>(Disparity Crew) Wait a minute. You know exactly what this is!</text>
										<event>
											<text>These are the remains of a Disparity Elite! You have your team grab them and pull out, and, once aboard, your own Disparity crew member gets to work on putting them together again. Once finished, the newly rebuilt Disparity Elite stutters a few words in thanks, "[B-b-b-brothers...] -here...?- T-t-thank: y-you..." They'll take some time to fully recover, but, as thanks, they offer to join your crew!</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="disparity_engidefault"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_SEPARATIST">
										<text>(Separatist Crew) Your Separatist seems to recognize the design.</text>
										<event>
											<text>They speak to you through the comms, "I have: heard -tell- of these ones. I think: I can [fix] them." You have your team grab the dismantled Engi and pull out, and, once aboard, your Separatist crew member gets to work on putting them together again. Once finished, the newly rebuilt Engi stutters a few more words in thanks, "[B-b-b-brothers...] -here...?- T-t-thank: y-you..." They'll take some time to fully recover, but, as thanks, the strange Engi offers to join your crew!</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="disparity_engidefault"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>I don't know what this is.</text>
										<event>
											<text>As strange as it is, there's nothing you can do. You hear as the ship buckles... this will have to be a mystery for another day.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>It's time to leave.</text>
												<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_WRECK_ESCAPE_LIST"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Scrap the outside of the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You skirt around the outside of the ship and scrap what you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't have any time for ominous wrecks, let alone ones in Deep One space. Not trying to get jumped by some kind of abominable horror, you prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST_LIST">
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST_LIST_WIN"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST_LIST_LOSS"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST_LIST_WIN">
	<text>"Quick... to answer. So be it, then. An enemy of the Theocracy... is a friend of ours." they say, before offering to share in some spoils from their recent heist of a Rock outpost! They regale you with tales of their exploits as their ship zooms into view, and, while they transfer the spoils over, you regale them with tales of your own.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST_LIST_LOSS">
	<text>"So... you say. I... am not so easily fooled." They cut communications, having never revealed their ship, and you're left wondering how exactly they expected you to answer that.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST" unique="true">
	<text>Before you can do anything, you're hailed with an invitation to a call on a private channel. You don't see any ships nearby when you look outside. Feels odd...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Accept the call.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're greeted with a dark room, duly lit by cyan lights on the ceiling. While you can't make anything out, you recognize the lights as being the same ones the Deep Ones use. A voice from the darkness speaks, "Have you... respect for the Rocks?" and silence ensues as they wait for a reply.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Of course.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Then we have no business with you." The call is ended, and you're left alone in silence.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
				<text>(Deep One) Let your Deep One answer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Deep One growls something scathing over the mic. The Deep Ones over the call seem to quite enjoy this answer, and after laughing for a moment brighten the room to reveal themselves. "An enemy of the Theocracy... is a friend of ours." they say, before offering to share in some spoils from their recent heist of a Rock outpost! They regale you with tales of their exploits as their ship zooms into view, and, while they transfer the spoils over, you regale them with tales of your own.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ROCK">
				<text>(Rock Crew) Let your Rockman answer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Rockman answers "Yes! An infinite well of respect!" proudly, and you're met with a brief moment of silence before the other end replies; "A shame. An infinite well... of shame." The call is ended, and you're left alone in silence.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_CRYSTAL">
				<text>(Crystal) Let your Crystal answer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Crystal shuffles a bit and answers meekly, "Not particularly. Those guys are a little weird, and... fanatical." and you hear a sigh from the Deep Ones as they reply; "Fanatical... to an extreme. Still, an enemy of the Theocracy... is a friend of ours." they say, before offering to share in some spoils from their recent heist of a Rock outpost! They regale you with tales of their exploits as their ship zooms into view, and, while they transfer the spoils over, you regale them with tales of your own.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Of course not.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_HEIST_LIST"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse the call.</text>
		<event>
			<text>No attempt to call again is made. You have some time before the FTL charges... though you feel uneasy.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DEEPONE_DREAD" unique="true">
	<text>Something feels off as you pull into the beacon. You're met with the sight of a Deep One outpost, but your hails aren't answered and the whole place seems still.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dock into the station.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You and your crew enter the station, and things quickly get weird. There are innumerable Deep Ones, all unmoving, their stares trance-like. You know Deep Ones are an odd bunch, but this seems bizarre even for them. Are they okay?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Try to grab a Deep One's attention.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You walk up to one of the Deep Ones and wave. Nothing. You clap a few times and still, nothing.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Try shaking it.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You clasp your hands around the Deep One's shoulders, and immediate dread fills your very being upon making contact. You see dozens of images, each filling you with more terror than the last; visions of rituals and cults. A Deep One brutalized, scarred; blood splatters across the ground as an entourage of yellow Deep Ones look on in worship of the horrible display. Prayers and followers in the name of...</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>You're brought back to reality as your crew pulls you away. What the hell was that, and why did you see it? What's going on with these Deep Ones?</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Head deeper into the outpost.</text>
										<event>
											<text>You and your crew walk past countless Deep Ones, and never once do they stir. At the heart of the outpost lies a pile of... garbage? No, scrap, and a note with it that reads "For you... captain." Do the Deep Ones really put pauses in their writing, too? No, more importantly, is this for you? Did they know you were coming? Your questions fall on deaf ears as the Deep Ones continue to stare into nothing for what feels like eternity, not moving an inch as you and your crew retreat to your ship with your newfound scrap.</text>
											<autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>This isn't right, head back before something goes wrong.</text>
										<event>
											<text>You and your crew turn back around, and the Deep Ones still don't move. Disturbed, but safe, you've got some time to kill before the FTL charges.</text>
											<choice>
												<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
												<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
											</choice>
											<choice>
												<text>Do nothing.</text>
												<event/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Stop trying, and just keep walking.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You and your crew walk past countless Deep Ones, and never once do they stir. At the heart of the outpost lies a pile of... garbage? No, scrap, and a note with it that reads "For you... captain." Do the Deep Ones really put pauses in their writing, too? No, more importantly, is this for you? Did they know you were coming? Your questions fall on deaf ears as the Deep Ones continue to stare into nothing for what feels like eternity, not moving an inch as you and your crew retreat to your ship with your newfound scrap.</text>
							<autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ignore the Deep Ones and keep moving.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You and your crew walk past countless Deep Ones, and never once do they stir. At the heart of the outpost lies a pile of... garbage? No, scrap, and a note with it that reads "For you... captain." Do the Deep Ones really put pauses in their writing, too? No, more importantly, is this for you? Did they know you were coming? Your questions fall on deaf ears as the Deep Ones continue to stare into nothing for what feels like eternity, not moving an inch as you and your crew retreat to your ship with your newfound scrap.</text>
					<autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
				<text>(Deep One) Your Deep One looks troubled.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You look to your Deep One for insight into the situation, but they don't seem too keen to provide answers. After pushing a little, they say one word; "Ritual." They insist you leave the Deep Ones here undisturbed. Ominous...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Push deeper into the outpost.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You and your crew walk past countless Deep Ones, and never once do they stir. At the heart of the outpost lies a pile of... garbage? No, scrap, and a note with it that reads "For you... captain." Do the Deep Ones really put pauses in their writing, too? No, more importantly, is this for you? Did they know you were coming? Your questions fall on deaf ears as the Deep Ones continue to stare into nothing for what feels like eternity, not moving an inch as you and your crew retreat to your ship with your newfound scrap.</text>
							<autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Turn back, this doesn't feel right.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You and your crew turn back around, and the Deep Ones still don't move. Disturbed, but safe, you've got some time to kill before the FTL charges.</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Do nothing.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>This is way too weird. Get out.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You and your crew turn back around, and the Deep Ones still don't move. Disturbed, but safe, you've got some time to kill before the FTL charges.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Nope. Staying right here.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't trust this outpost. As such, you fire up the FTL and prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDCHOSEN">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>What??? How'd you do that???</text>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST_SUCCESS"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST_FAILURE"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST_EXTREMEFAILURE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST_SUCCESS">
	<text>You try your best to fly in the general direction of where the ship was, and you breathe a sigh of relief as its silhouette appears in the near distance. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hurry!</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST_FAILURE">
	<text>Despite your best efforts, your search proves to be fruitless. Eventually, deciding that feeling around in the dark is pointless, you make the call to prepare to leave before the Rebellion gains any more ground.</text>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST_EXTREMEFAILURE">
	<text>It doesn't take long for you to find the shrouded ship... as you crash into it, sending it cascading back into the darkness! Maybe cluelessly searching around in the dark wasn't the greatest idea after all, but, at least the damage isn't too severe. Still, you're not going to risk trying to find it again...</text>
	<damage amount="4"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD">
	<text>You rush onboard the damaged ship, but quickly realize it's just as dark in here as it was out there... and, yet, you don't necessarily feel as lost. An esoteric warmth in your chest seems to guide you forward, and you don't so much as bump into anything as you traverse the pitch black halls. Eventually, your hand comes to rest on something. The feeling of its surface is alien, almost indescribable, but it emits a heat comparable to the one you feel guiding you. Something wanted you to find this... whatever it is.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>How strange...</text>
		<event>
			<text>There's a loud, tearing noise, and the realization dawns on you that the ship is about to collapse. You're going to have to settle with taking... whatever this object is back, and you're going to have be quick! You pick it up, as heavy as it is, and make a sprint for the exit...</text>
			<playSound>ddsoulplague_creaking1</playSound>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Run!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your mad, blind dash through the darkness goes as smoothly as your entrance had, to your amazement, and you're able to make a decisive leap back into your ship's airlock. As it closes, you see the ship behind you as it's torn apart, and for the first time you get a good look at the object you just risked your life to secure... it seems to be a strange weapon of sorts. The warmth in your chest leaves you, and the weapon quickly becomes almost searing hot to the touch. You're not sure what exactly it is, what's just happened here, or why you couldn't find any of the ship's inhabitants... but you're all the richer for it as you prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
					<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_WEAPONS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE" unique="true">
	<text>The two ships here, while undoubtedly of Deep One design, are not ones you can say you recognize in the slightest. Whereas most Deep One ships overcompensate with their lighting, these ones seem to lack any amount of external lights whatsoever. In fact, you feel as if they suck in the very light around them... you're not sure if they've noticed you, but you get the impression that they're communicating with each other.</text>
	<ship load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Approach the two ships.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Before you can really get moving, an explosion rocks one of the mysterious Deep One ships; simultaneously, the other jumps out of the beacon. From where the first ship's hull was breached, a dark cloud begins to spew forth, and you find your ship rapidly enveloped in pitch blackness... it's impossible to see anything in here. Still, there's a chance you can locate the remaining ship before it's too late...</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
			<playSound>explosion_heavy</playSound>
			<instantEscape/>
			<choice hidden="true" req="deeponecultist">
				<text>(Enlightened Crew) Allow your Enlightened Cultist to guide you through the darkness.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Familiar with the darkness that surrounds you, your Enlightened Cultist is successfully able to peer through it and see exactly where the strange ship is located. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hurry!</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_thescarred">
				<text>(The Scarred) Allow the Scarred to guide you through the darkness.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Familiar with the darkness that surrounds you, the Scarred is successfully able to peer through it and see exactly where the strange ship is located. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hurry!</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="dddeepone_chosen">
				<text>(Chosen Crew) Allow your Chosen to guide you through the darkness.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Familiar with the darkness that surrounds you, your Chosen is successfully able to peer through it and see exactly where the strange ship is located. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hurry!</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SLUG">
				<text>(Slug Crew) Allow your Chosen to guide you through the darkness.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Capable of reading the minds of those nearby, your Slug is successfully able to catch a reading and see exactly where the strange ship is located. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hurry!</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_CREW_SNAIL">
				<text>(Telepathic Shell) Allow your Shell to guide you through the darkness.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Capable of reading the minds of those nearby, your Shell is successfully able to catch a reading and see exactly where the strange ship is located. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hurry!</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIFE_SCANNER">
				<text>(Lifeform Scanner) Allow your Lifeform Scanner to guide you through the darkness.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Capable of locating nearby lifeforms, your Lifeform Scanner is successfully able to catch a reading and see exactly where the strange ship is located. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hurry!</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
				<text>(Adv. Sensors) Allow your sensors to guide you through the darkness.</text>
				<event>
					<text>As powerful as your sensors are, they're still only able to barely catch a reading and see exactly where the strange ship is located. Once there, you're able to make its shape out enough to dock, but you're also able to recognize that the damage to its hull is truly severe. If anyone alive's left onboard, odds are that you don't have much time to save them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hurry!</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_REWARD"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Try your best to feel your way through the darkness.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_CHOSENESCAPE_NAVIGATION_LIST"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Screw this. Stay put.</text>
				<event>
					<text>God knows what's going on out there, or what exchange you've managed to stumble upon. You're content simply staying put while the FTL drive charges, and ensuring that you don't crash into anything while blindly flying through clouds of unnatural darkness.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Keep to yourself.</text>
		<event>
			<text>What business do you have intruding upon random ships' interactions? That, and these ships in particular kind of give you the creeps... you're quite content keeping to yourself while the FTL drive charges.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH"/>
</eventList>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW_STEADY">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW_STEADY_LUCKY"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW_STEADY_UNLUCKY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW_STEADY_LUCKY">
	<text>You raise the bid, and the crowd goes quiet... is this truly all you needed to win? The auctioneer yells out, "We have 65! Going once, going twice..." The crowd stays silent in their shock, and a gavel rings out somewhere, "Sold, to the Federation officer for 65 scrap!" Excited murmurs break out amongst the crowd, and you're ushered to the front before being led to a private room backstage. The auctioneer enters a few moments later, cage in tow, and you're able to get a good look at it for the first time... it's truly massive, and you swear you can hear a strange, faint, almost wet noise coming from within. You get a good look at the auctioneer, as well: a shorter, hunched man adorned in black robes. Around his neck is a pendant that you recognize as sharing the strange symbol on the mysterious ships outside, and he turns to you, "So! Cash or credit?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
		<text>(The Minister) The Minister clears his throat.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The robed man jumps as he notices the Minister's presence, before collapsing to his knees and bowing his head, "I-It's not what it looks like, Hand! We were just, uh... gathering funds, in the Tempest's name!" The Minister looks over at the cage, scoffing, "When I said you can find other homes for your excess spawn, I didn't mean aboard civilian ships, you imbecile. You're lucky I don't crush you like the conniving bug you are." The man's bow deepens, and he begins pleading incoherently.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Minister rolls his eyes, "I'll be confiscating this spawn. Allow me to catch you pawning off the Tempest's blessings again, and I'll be infinitely less merciful in the future." He slams a hand against the cage, and it shatters, revealing a Stormborn Spawn. The Minister turns to you, "Let's go. We've wasted enough time here." You and him leave the room, the spawn following in his shadow, and the crowd eyes you and your entourage in disbelief the whole way back to the ship.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Cash!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have the 65 scrap brought in by your crew, and the robed man counts it excitedly. Once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-65" max="-65"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Credit!</text>
		<event>
			<text>There's not really any such thing as scrap credit, but you have the 65 scrap brought in by your crew. The robed man counts it excitedly, and, once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-65" max="-65"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>I, eh... can't actually afford this.</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW_STEADY_UNLUCKY">
	<text>For a moment, the crowd stays quiet, but then a particularly well-dressed man curtly raises his hand:
	
	"I'll end this. 200."
	
	There's an uproar amongst the auction-goers, and the auctioneer's eyes go wide. "200?! That is 200 from my generous friend in the black suit! 200, going once, going twice..." Is this it?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Stamp your foot down, and raise the bid to 205.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The sound of your foot meeting the floor echoes throughout the room, and everyone in the crowd turns to you. Even the previous bidder seems shocked... but he doesn't raise his hand again. The auctioneer, again, roars to life, "WE HAVE 205! GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE..." The crowd stays silent in their shock, and a gavel rings out somewhere, "SOLD, TO THE GENEROUS FEDERATION OFFICER FOR 205 SCRAP!" Excited murmurs break out amongst the crowd, and you're ushered to the front before being led to a private room backstage. The auctioneer enters a few moments later, cage in tow, and you're able to get a good look at it for the first time... it's truly massive, and you swear you can hear a strange, faint, almost wet noise coming from within. You get a good look at the auctioneer, as well: a shorter, hunched man adorned in black robes. Around his neck is a pendant that you recognize as sharing the strange symbol on the mysterious ships outside, and he turns to you, "So! Cash or credit?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
				<text>(The Minister) The Minister clears his throat.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The robed man jumps as he notices the Minister's presence, before collapsing to his knees and bowing his head, "I-It's not what it looks like, Hand! We were just, uh... gathering funds, in the Tempest's name!" The Minister looks over at the cage, scoffing, "When I said you can find other homes for your excess spawn, I didn't mean aboard civilian ships, you imbecile. You're lucky I don't crush you like the conniving bug you are." The man's bow deepens, and he begins pleading incoherently.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Minister rolls his eyes, "I'll be confiscating this spawn. Allow me to catch you pawning off the Tempest's blessings again, and I'll be infinitely less merciful in the future." He slams a hand against the cage, and it shatters, revealing a Stormborn Spawn. The Minister turns to you, "Let's go. We've wasted enough time here." You and him leave the room, the spawn following in his shadow, and the crowd eyes you and your entourage in disbelief the whole way back to the ship.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Cash!</text>
				<event>
					<text>You have the 205 scrap brought in by your crew, and the robed man counts it excitedly. Once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-205" max="-205"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Credit!</text>
				<event>
					<text>There's not really any such thing as scrap credit, but you have the 205 scrap brought in by your crew. The robed man counts it excitedly, and, once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-205" max="-205"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I, eh... can't actually afford this.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Clench your teeth, and stay quiet.</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_CHICKENINGS"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW">
	<text>You're able to find one of the few empty spots to dock, and are uninterrupted as you and your crew board the outpost. The space inside isn't massive, and you're able to quickly spot a giant crowd of people deeper within. Approaching them, you make out a man raised at the center of the crowd as he circles a cloaked cage and shouts, "Now that you're all aware of what exactly's at stake here... do we have any bidders? The bid starts at a measly 5 scrap!" So this is some sort of auction... hands from the crowd begin to fly into the air as people shout out their bids:
					
	"10!"
	
	"Oh, I'll take it for 15!"
	
	"This is easy, then; 20!"
	
	"I'll raise you 25!"
	
	Things seem to be going steadily, but there's still a brief silence that allows you to get a word in.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Raise the bid to 30.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You make your bid, and the man raised in the center of the crowd looks at you, "Oh, Federation! Not exactly who we expected when we pictured paying customers, but... as long as you're not busting us! Very well, 30 it is! Will anybody raise it to 35?!" A few more hands shoot up:
							
			"I guess I can do 35..."
			
			"40! 40!"
			
			"I'm almost out, but... fuck it, 50!"
			
			"How about 60?!"
			
			The bidding has doubled, just like that, and the crowd murmurs in shock.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Keep things steady. Raise it to 65.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_LOW_STEADY"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Blow their socks off. Raise it to 120.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The crowd collectively turns to you in shock, and the auctioneer yells out triumphantly, "WE HAVE 120! GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE..." The crowd stays silent in their shock, and a gavel rings out somewhere, "SOLD, TO THE GENEROUS FEDERATION OFFICER FOR 120 SCRAP!" Excited murmurs break out amongst the crowd, and you're ushered to the front before being led to a private room backstage. The auctioneer enters a few moments later, cage in tow, and you're able to get a good look at it for the first time... it's truly massive, and you swear you can hear a strange, faint, almost wet noise coming from within. You get a good look at the auctioneer, as well: a shorter, hunched man adorned in black robes. Around his neck is a pendant that you recognize as sharing the strange symbol on the mysterious ships outside, and he turns to you, "So! Cash or credit?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
						<text>(The Minister) The Minister clears his throat.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The robed man jumps as he notices the Minister's presence, before collapsing to his knees and bowing his head, "I-It's not what it looks like, Hand! We were just, uh... gathering funds, in the Tempest's name!" The Minister looks over at the cage, scoffing, "When I said you can find other homes for your excess spawn, I didn't mean aboard civilian ships, you imbecile. You're lucky I don't crush you like the conniving bug you are." The man's bow deepens, and he begins pleading incoherently.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>The Minister rolls his eyes, "I'll be confiscating this spawn. Allow me to catch you pawning off the Tempest's blessings again, and I'll be infinitely less merciful in the future." He slams a hand against the cage, and it shatters, revealing a Stormborn Spawn. The Minister turns to you, "Let's go. We've wasted enough time here." You and him leave the room, the spawn following in his shadow, and the crowd eyes you and your entourage in disbelief the whole way back to the ship.</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Cash!</text>
						<event>
							<text>You have the 120 scrap brought in by your crew, and the robed man counts it excitedly. Once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-120" max="-120"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Credit!</text>
						<event>
							<text>There's not really any such thing as scrap credit, but you have the 120 scrap brought in by your crew. The robed man counts it excitedly, and, once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-120" max="-120"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>I, eh... can't actually afford this.</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Chicken out. This is too much.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_CHICKENINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>You're not really interested in an auction. Get out of here.</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_LEAVINGS"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH_STEADY">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH_STEADY_LUCKY"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH_STEADY_UNLUCKY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH_STEADY_LUCKY">
	<text>You raise the bid, and the crowd goes quiet... is this truly all you needed to win? The auctioneer yells out, "We have 155! Going once, going twice..." The crowd stays silent in their shock, and a gavel rings out somewhere, "Sold, to the Federation officer for 155 scrap!" Excited murmurs break out amongst the crowd, and you're ushered to the front before being led to a private room backstage. The auctioneer enters a few moments later, cage in tow, and you're able to get a good look at it for the first time... it's truly massive, and you swear you can hear a strange, faint, almost wet noise coming from within. You get a good look at the auctioneer, as well: a shorter, hunched man adorned in black robes. Around his neck is a pendant that you recognize as sharing the strange symbol on the mysterious ships outside, and he turns to you, "So! Cash or credit?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
		<text>(The Minister) The Minister clears his throat.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The robed man jumps as he notices the Minister's presence, before collapsing to his knees and bowing his head, "I-It's not what it looks like, Hand! We were just, uh... gathering funds, in the Tempest's name!" The Minister looks over at the cage, scoffing, "When I said you can find other homes for your excess spawn, I didn't mean aboard civilian ships, you imbecile. You're lucky I don't crush you like the conniving bug you are." The man's bow deepens, and he begins pleading incoherently.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Minister rolls his eyes, "I'll be confiscating this spawn. Allow me to catch you pawning off the Tempest's blessings again, and I'll be infinitely less merciful in the future." He slams a hand against the cage, and it shatters, revealing a Stormborn Spawn. The Minister turns to you, "Let's go. We've wasted enough time here." You and him leave the room, the spawn following in his shadow, and the crowd eyes you and your entourage in disbelief the whole way back to the ship.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Cash!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have the 155 scrap brought in by your crew, and the robed man counts it excitedly. Once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-155" max="-155"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Credit!</text>
		<event>
			<text>There's not really any such thing as scrap credit, but you have the 155 scrap brought in by your crew. The robed man counts it excitedly, and, once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-155" max="-155"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>I, eh... can't actually afford this.</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH_STEADY_UNLUCKY">
	<text>For a moment, the crowd stays quiet, but then a particularly well-dressed man curtly raises his hand:
	
	"I'll end this. 500."
	
	There's an uproar amongst the auction-goers, and the auctioneer's eyes go wide. "500?! That is 500 from my generous friend in the black suit! 500, going once, going twice..." Is this it?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Stamp your foot down, and raise the bid to 505.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The sound of your foot meeting the floor echoes throughout the room, and everyone in the crowd turns to you. Even the previous bidder seems shocked... but he doesn't raise his hand again. The auctioneer, again, roars to life, "WE HAVE 505! GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE..." The crowd stays silent in their shock, and a gavel rings out somewhere, "SOLD, TO THE GENEROUS FEDERATION OFFICER FOR 505 SCRAP!" Excited murmurs break out amongst the crowd, and you're ushered to the front before being led to a private room backstage. The auctioneer enters a few moments later, cage in tow, and you're able to get a good look at it for the first time... it's truly massive, and you swear you can hear a strange, faint, almost wet noise coming from within. You get a good look at the auctioneer, as well: a shorter, hunched man adorned in black robes. Around his neck is a pendant that you recognize as sharing the strange symbol on the mysterious ships outside, and he turns to you, "So! Cash or credit?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
				<text>(The Minister) The Minister clears his throat.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The robed man jumps as he notices the Minister's presence, before collapsing to his knees and bowing his head, "I-It's not what it looks like, Hand! We were just, uh... gathering funds, in the Tempest's name!" The Minister looks over at the cage, scoffing, "When I said you can find other homes for your excess spawn, I didn't mean aboard civilian ships, you imbecile. You're lucky I don't crush you like the conniving bug you are." The man's bow deepens, and he begins pleading incoherently.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Minister rolls his eyes, "I'll be confiscating this spawn. Allow me to catch you pawning off the Tempest's blessings again, and I'll be infinitely less merciful in the future." He slams a hand against the cage, and it shatters, revealing a Stormborn Spawn. The Minister turns to you, "Let's go. We've wasted enough time here." You and him leave the room, the spawn following in his shadow, and the crowd eyes you and your entourage in disbelief the whole way back to the ship.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Cash!</text>
				<event>
					<text>You have the 505 scrap brought in by your crew, and the robed man counts it excitedly. Once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-505" max="-505"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Credit!</text>
				<event>
					<text>There's not really any such thing as scrap credit, but you have the 505 scrap brought in by your crew. The robed man counts it excitedly, and, once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-505" max="-505"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I, eh... can't actually afford this.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Clench your teeth, and stay quiet.</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_CHICKENINGS"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH">
	<text>You're able to find one of the few empty spots to dock, and are uninterrupted as you and your crew board the outpost. The space inside isn't massive, and you're able to quickly spot a giant crowd of people deeper within. Approaching them, you make out a man raised at the center of the crowd as he circles a cloaked cage and shouts, "Now that you're all aware of what exactly's at stake here... do we have any bidders? The bid starts at a measly 5 scrap!" So this is some sort of auction... hands from the crowd begin to fly into the air as people shout out their bids:
					
	"10!"
	
	"Oh, I'll take it for 50!"
	
	"50?! That quickly?!"
	
	"I'll raise you 60!"
	
	An awkward silence hangs in the air as the bidding immediately get pricy.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Raise the bid to 65.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You make your bid, and the man raised in the center of the crowd looks at you, "Oh, Federation! Not exactly who we expected when we pictured paying customers, but... as long as you're not busting us! Very well, 65 it is! Will anybody raise it to 70?!" A few more hands shoot up:
							
			"I guess I can do 70..."
			
			"Fuck it, 100!"
			
			"Are you mad?!"
			
			"You think THAT'S mad? 150!"
			
			The bidding has more than doubled, just like that, and the crowd murmurs in shock.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Keep things steady. Raise it to 155.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART_HIGH_STEADY"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Blow their socks off. Raise it to 250.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The crowd collectively turns to you in shock, and the auctioneer yells out triumphantly, "WE HAVE 250! GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE..." The crowd stays silent in their shock, and a gavel rings out somewhere, "SOLD, TO THE GENEROUS FEDERATION OFFICER FOR 250 SCRAP!" Excited murmurs break out amongst the crowd, and you're ushered to the front before being led to a private room backstage. The auctioneer enters a few moments later, cage in tow, and you're able to get a good look at it for the first time... it's truly massive, and you swear you can hear a strange, faint, almost wet noise coming from within. You get a good look at the auctioneer, as well: a shorter, hunched man adorned in black robes. Around his neck is a pendant that you recognize as sharing the strange symbol on the mysterious ships outside, and he turns to you, "So! Cash or credit?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
						<text>(The Minister) The Minister clears his throat.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The robed man jumps as he notices the Minister's presence, before collapsing to his knees and bowing his head, "I-It's not what it looks like, Hand! We were just, uh... gathering funds, in the Tempest's name!" The Minister looks over at the cage, scoffing, "When I said you can find other homes for your excess spawn, I didn't mean aboard civilian ships, you imbecile. You're lucky I don't crush you like the conniving bug you are." The man's bow deepens, and he begins pleading incoherently.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>The Minister rolls his eyes, "I'll be confiscating this spawn. Allow me to catch you pawning off the Tempest's blessings again, and I'll be infinitely less merciful in the future." He slams a hand against the cage, and it shatters, revealing a Stormborn Spawn. The Minister turns to you, "Let's go. We've wasted enough time here." You and him leave the room, the spawn following in his shadow, and the crowd eyes you and your entourage in disbelief the whole way back to the ship.</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Cash!</text>
						<event>
							<text>You have the 250 scrap brought in by your crew, and the robed man counts it excitedly. Once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-250" max="-250"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Credit!</text>
						<event>
							<text>There's not really any such thing as scrap credit, but you have the 250 scrap brought in by your crew. The robed man counts it excitedly, and, once everything is accounted for, he turns to you once more, "Very well, then! The payment's all here; I'll have my subordinates wheel this bastard over to your ship. Glad to finally get rid of this thing, it's been causing a real ruckus... what with all the, uh, man-eating and all." For a moment, you assume he's joking, but you quickly realize the look on his face is completely serious.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-250" max="-250"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Uh... man-eating?</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>I, eh... can't actually afford this.</text>
						<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Chicken out. This is too much.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_CHICKENINGS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>You're not really interested in an auction. Get out of here.</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_LEAVINGS"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_WINNINGS">
	<text>He nods, a tired look on his face, "Yeah, these spawn can be a real hassle sometimes. The big guy upstairs keeps gifting them, and we keep taking 'em, but there's only so many we can afford to house onboard after a certain point. Thankfully, the Hand doesn't mind us, uh, 'giving' them away. We keep the whole auction thing on the down-low, but... cultists have to pay the bills somehow." Spawn? The big guy upstairs? The Hand?? Cultists??? Speechless during the trip back to your ship, you wonder what exactly it is you've won here...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Wait for your winnings aboard the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It doesn't take long for similarly robed men to arrive at your ship with the strange cage in hand. They leave it in the ship's hold, dropping it in a hurry and rushing back outside before you can get so much as a word in. Alone with it now, you get a clearer idea of the sound you'd heard earlier... there's certainly something alive in there.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Remove the cage's cover.</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you move to uncloak the cage, it breaks apart, to your shock, and one of its sides comes crashing down on you. Dazed for a moment, you realize you're pinned to the floor... and standing over you is the cage's former inhabitant. An indescribable, horrific mass of tentacles, eyes and teeth towers over you, its many maws agape. The abomination roars out, and your ears are left ringing as it crawls its way over your legs, onto your torso and towards your head...</text>
					<playSound>ddstormbornspawngrowl</playSound>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Scream.</text>
						<event>
							<text>...and removes the side of the cage that had been crushing you, before harmlessly crawling away. 'Removes' is putting it simply; it literally dragged the bars into its being and consumed them. The strange thing leaves the room, slowly but surely, and you're left on the floor catching your breath. There's no telling what in the hell you've just unleashed onboard, but at least it seems to be on your side. The more, the merrier...?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDTEMPEST">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN_MONSTERGAMBLE">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN_MONSTERGAMBLE_LUCKY"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN_MONSTERGAMBLE_UNLUCKY"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN_MONSTERGAMBLE_UNLUCKY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN_MONSTERGAMBLE_LUCKY">
	<text>As you move to uncloak the cage, it breaks apart, to your shock, and one of its sides comes crashing down on you. Dazed for a moment, you realize you're pinned to the floor... and standing over you is the cage's former inhabitant. An indescribable, horrific mass of tentacles, eyes and teeth towers over you, its many maws agape. The abomination roars out, and your ears are left ringing as it crawls its way over your legs, onto your torso and towards your head...</text>
	<playSound>ddstormbornspawngrowl</playSound>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Scream.</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and removes the side of the cage that had been crushing you, before harmlessly crawling away. 'Removes' is putting it simply; it literally dragged the bars into its being and consumed them. The strange thing leaves the room, slowly but surely, and you're left on the floor catching your breath. There's no telling what in the hell you've just unleashed onboard, but at least it seems to be on your side. The more, the merrier...?</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN_MONSTERGAMBLE_UNLUCKY">
	<text>As you move to uncloak the cage, it breaks apart, to your shock, and you just narrowly dodge out of the way as one of its sides nearly crashes down on you. You look over, and standing over you is the cage's former inhabitant... an indescribable, horrific mass of tentacles, eyes and teeth towers over you, its many maws agape. The abomination roars out, bloodthirsty, and you sprint out of the room as it begins to make its advance!</text>
	<playSound>ddstormbornspawngrowl</playSound>
	<boarders min="1" max="1" class="ddtempest_stormborn_spawn_enemy"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>With the ship and its otherworldly inhabitants defeated, you turn to the cage you'd brought onboard and realize you recognize the noises coming from it. It's the same ones that one of the monsters you just defeated had been making...</text>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="engines" amount="100"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Swallow your fear, and remove the cage's cover.</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT_WIN_MONSTERGAMBLE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Launch the cage out the airlock. Better safe than sorry.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You wheel the cage over to the airlock, its wet noises never once quieting, and are able to flush it outside without incident. A crisis averted, surely.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS">
	<text>The robed man blinks, "You... what? Why did you bid it then?" He puts his head in his hands, lamenting his wasted time, and you realize there's an opportunity here...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Punch the man while he's distracted.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You clock him straight in the head, and he crashes to the floor... he's out cold. On the clock now, you rush out of the room with the cage in hand, but you don't get very far before a similarly robed man spots you, surmises what happened, and yells out, "STOP! THIEF!" The crowd looks over, shock on their faces, and you sprint towards the ship as fast as your legs can carry you. It's good that this cage came on wheels, as you're able to get it onboard before anyone can catch up to you, but you're not out of the woods yet... as you lift off, one of the odd ships you'd spotted before gives chase! A streak of lightning bolts from their ship, striking yours, and you realize they've managed to disable your engines... get ready!</text>
			<ship load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FAILINGS_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
			<status type="limit" target="player" system="engines" amount="0"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hold back. I'm at fault here.</text>
		<event>
			<text>He raises his head, annoyance on his face, "Can you, like, get out, then? Why are you here?" He sighs, pushing you out of the room, and you catch him saying one more thing under his breath, "I'll have to hold another auction now... Hopefully the Hand doesn't catch wind of all this commotion..." The Hand? You're not sure who he's referring to, but you don't mind having something to ponder as you make your walk of shame back to the ship... empty-handed.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_CHICKENINGS">
	<text>You're not about to go broke keeping this going. The trip back to the ship is uneventful, but a part of you wonders what exactly was inside of that cage as you prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_LEAVINGS">
	<text>You're not about to go broke participating in an auction. The trip back to the ship is uneventful, but a part of you wonders what exactly was inside of that cage as you prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDTEMPEST">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>With the ship and its otherworldly inhabitants defeated, you ponder the peculiarity of the abominations they had onboard... what exactly is going on at that outpost? You may never know, now, you fear.</text>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION" unique="true">
	<text>A blindingly bright light forces you to cover your eyes as you enter the beacon, but its source is not the Deep One lights you'd expect it to be. Not entirely, anyways; there's a small, makeship outpost here with several dozen ships huddled around it. Some of them are indeed Deep One ships, but not as many as you'd expect seeing that you're in the closest thing they have to proper territory.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Inspect the outpost further.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Comically large spotlights beam off of the outpost, moving in a constant sweeping pattern. You make sure to duck your ship to avoid being blinded again, and you get a closer look at the ships gathered here as you do so... to your surprise, it seems to be mostly Union ships. That, the Deep One ships, and a few alien ships you recognize the make of, but not the paint jobs and markings of: they've been painted all black, save for what seems to be a symbol of a light blue eye next to a lightning bolt. Your curiosity is piqued...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>This seems interesting... dock your ship, and board the outpost.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_BIDSTART"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Hmm. I'm feeling some terrorism right about now. Attack the outpost!</text>
				<event>
					<text>You open fire on the ships parked around the outpost, and it doesn't take long for one of the odd ships you'd noticed before to roar to life. You make a break for it, but they manage to catch up some ways away from the outpost... get ready!</text>
					<ship load="ITEMS_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTAUCTION_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Nah. I don't care, actually. Ignore the outpost.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Curiosity, more like SCHMURIOSITY. You turn away from the outpost, an indignant look on your face, and prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_GOOBER"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_LANIUS"/>
	<event load="DEEPONE_CONFUSION"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_MATTERVIRUSDEALER"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_GOOBER" unique="true">
	<text>You're quickly hailed, met by a little Deep One, "BEHOLD... GUUBARE." You behold Guubare. Besides being short and of a stout build, he's notably... shaky. Fear? The cold? Do fish-people shiver? Whatever it is, it makes an already unintimidating Deep One even less threatening.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>O' mighty GUUBARE, I beholdeth thou in full. Doth thou taketh pity on mine soul?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"THIS ONE... SPEAKS AKIN TO THE GHOSTS. YET, THEY SPEAK... HIGHLY OF GUUBARE. GUUBARE... TAKES PITY. BEGONE, LITTLE... THING." Guubare cuts communications and you're left with nothing to do but charge the FTL.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>You're such a little... goober, Guubare.</text>
		<event>
			<text>His shaking worsens. He speaks again, but his voice is way less deep now, high-pitched even; "Man... I told you guys I wasn't cut out for this..." Gloomy, he walks away and a new, giant Deep One takes his place. "You've... upset Guubare. The price, for this transgression... is your head." They cut communications and a ship zooms into view, guns charging!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_ROCK_FIGHT">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_FANATIC"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_FANATIC"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<ship name="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_CALM" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_ROCK_FIGHT">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can. Hopefully the lights survived...</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CALM_RUBBLE"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can before looking for the lights.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CALM_CREWKILL"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<ship name="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC_TIMED" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_ROCK_FIGHT">
	<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC_TIMED_FAIL" time="60" thisFight="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_TIMER" pos="combat">
			<warning time="10.0" flash="true"/>
			<tooltip>If you do not defeat the Rock ship in this amount of time, the second ship's signature will go cold!</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can before trying to track the second ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC_TIMED_SUCCESS"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can before trying to track the second ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC_TIMED_SUCCESS"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_FANATIC">
	<text>Unphased by the first ship's destruction, the second speaks up; "A fool, that one. I've got some explaining to do to our superiors, but still, I'd argue you've done me a favor. Here, you can have the lights. There's plenty more where they came from, and I shouldn't have any problems convincing my brethren of their uses with this half-wit silenced." They beam the lights over and promptly leave the system.</text>
	<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CALM_RUBBLE">
	<text>You comb through the wreckage, and eventually find the lights unharmed! The first ship seems amused by this and speaks up, "FOOLISH, that one. To THINK, they'd DEFY the texts and seek power in the UNHOLY. Take the lights if you wish, FED. I won't be missing their GHASTLY glow." They cut communications and promptly leave the system.</text>
	<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CALM_CREWKILL">
	<text>You comb through the now-empty ship, and eventually find the lights unharmed! The first ship seems amused by this and speaks up, "FOOLISH, that one. To THINK, they'd DEFY the texts and seek power in the UNHOLY. Take the lights if you wish, FED. I won't be missing their GHASTLY glow." They cut communications and promptly leave the system.</text>
	<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC_TIMED_FAIL">
	<text>The second ship's signature has gone cold. With their partner safe, the first ship escapes off in the opposite direction. Seeing that there's little point in giving chase if you won't be catching the second ship regardless, you prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<instantEscape/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC_TIMED_SUCCESS">
	<text>The second ship's signature is still warm! You log their coordinates on your map and prepare to leave the beacon, triumphant.</text>
	<quest event="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_CHASE"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF" unique="true">
	<text>There appear to be two Rock ships at this beacon, communicating on an open channel. They don't pay you any mind, but there's nothing stopping you from listening in...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Listen in.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"They MUST be DESTROYED. This foul creation of the legged-fish-things is blasphemy of the HIGHEST ORDER!" says one ship, to which the other responds "There's nothing in the texts about these infernal lights. Foul they may be, they have their uses in our hands; namely, against the Deep Ones themselves." They notice you listening in and the second ship speaks again, "You there, Federation ship. What know you of these lights?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>They're... cyan?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"CYAN? Are you visually IMPAIRED, FED? They're CLEARLY turquoise. I TIRE of these games. First, YOU. THEN, we discuss the destruction of these ABOMINABLE lights." The first ship turns to you, weapons charged! The second ship doesn't seem to want to get involved, but sticks around nonetheless.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ROCK">
				<text>(Rock) Let your Rock answer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Rock speaks up, "Blasted things blind you good, boarding these... "Deep Ones" is a right pain." Satisfied with your answer, the second ship responds, "Hah, indeed. Glad I'm not the only one capable of seeing their potential. Tell you what, seeing that my... partner here is insistent on having them destroyed, I wouldn't mind having you put them to good use. For a price, of course, but I'll give you a discount... I like you."</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Agree to the trade.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The first ship grumbles a little bit over the comms but doesn't intervene. With the lights transferred, and the argument settled, the two ships hang around for a moment before jumping out of the system.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-45" max="-45"/>
							</item_modify>
							<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Pass on the offer.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"I understand. Suppose I've got to keep listening to this idiot's blathering, then..." The first ship erupts at this insult and the two go back to arguing. That's that, then.</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The greatest discount is "free." Attack, and take the lights from them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"It's like that, then? Fine, come at me!" They turn to you and prepare to defend themselves. The first ship doesn't seem to want to get involved, but sticks around nonetheless.</text>
							<ship load="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_CALM" hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
				<text>(Deep One) Let your Deep One answer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Deep One explodes at the two Rocks, "Our technology is not... for the likes of you. Thieves... murderers." The second ship chuckles, "The Federation harboring Deep Ones these days? Suppose they'll let anyone in... deal with them. We'll finish this argument later." The first ship turns to you, weapons charged, and the second jumps out of the system. If you're quick, you might be able to track their FTL signatures and take the lights from them!</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_FANATIC_TIMED" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Not much.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Not particularly useful, then, are you? We'll be taking our leave, if you have nothing worthwhile to add. We've no need for eavesdroppers." The two ships jump away, and you're left wondering who wins the argument...</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You ignore the two ships. You're here to save reality, not eavesdrop on random Rocks' conversations.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_CHASE" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_ROCK_FIGHT">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can. Hopefully the lights survived...</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CHASE_RUBBLE"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can before looking for the lights.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CHASE_CREWKILL"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CHASE_RUBBLE">
	<text>You find the lights among the wreckage, unharmed... either they're extremely durable, or you're extremely lucky. Regardless, you hope they're worth all the bloodshed, and continue on your way.</text>
	<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_WIN_CHASE_CREWKILL">
	<text>You find the lights within the ship's hold, unharmed. They glow so enticingly in the dark, here... you hope they're worth all the bloodshed and continue on your way.</text>
	<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_CHASE">
	<text>The second Rock ship is at this beacon, as expected. "You... chased me here? You want these lights that badly? Vicious, this so-called 'Federation.' Fine then, to battle!" They cut communications. Prepare to fight.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_ROCKOFF_CHASE" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_SMALL"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_SMALL"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_SMALL"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_MEDIUM"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_MEDIUM"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_MEDIUM"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_MEDIUM"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_JACKPOT_SOULPLAGUE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_JACKPOT_DARKWEAPON"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_JACKPOT_DARKDRONE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_SMALL">
	<text>Indeed, there's little here of value... still, free scrap is free scrap.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_MEDIUM">
	<text>Though it's not an absurd amount of loot, you manage to find way more resources than you expected!</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_JACKPOT_SOULPLAGUE">
	<text>You're moving from ship to ship, scrapping what you can when a strange, iridescent ship catches your eye... investigating its cargo, you manage to find a peculiar weapon in seemingly perfect condition. You weren't expecting to find something so unique in the equivalent of a space-landfill, but you've managed to all the same!</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_WEAPONS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Jackpot!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Taking your new loot aboard, you notice as some sort of goo secretes off of it. This goo smacks against the floor, and then immediately begins to writhe and bubble before rising to take the form of a humanoid figure... this is a Soulplague Husk! More of these goo-things begin to propagate, and you realize you've got trouble!</text>
			<playSound>blobDeath</playSound>
			<boarders min="2" max="4" class="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUERANDOM_SUMMON_ENEMY"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_JACKPOT_DARKWEAPON">
	<text>You're moving from ship to ship, scrapping what you can when a strange, decrepit Deep One ship catches your eye... investigating its cargo, you manage to find a peculiar weapon in seemingly perfect condition. You weren't expecting to find something so unique in the equivalent of a space-landfill, but you've managed to all the same!</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_WEAPONS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Jackpot!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Taking your new loot aboard, you notice as some sort of darkness emanates from it. This darkness coalesces, eventually forming a mass of tentacles atop the floor. Then, another, and another... what is this madness? More of these shadow-things begin to propagate, and you realize you've got trouble!</text>
			<playSound>ddsoulplague_creaking1</playSound>
			<boarders min="3" max="6" class="darkgodtendrils"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST_JACKPOT_DARKDRONE">
	<text>You're moving from ship to ship, scrapping what you can when a strange, crystalline ship catches your eye... investigating its cargo, you manage to find a peculiar drone in seemingly perfect condition. You weren't expecting to find something so unique in the equivalent of a space-landfill, but you've managed to all the same!</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<drone name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_DRONES"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Jackpot!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Taking your new loot aboard, you notice as some sort of darkness emanates from it. This darkness coalesces, eventually forming a mass of tentacles atop the floor. Then, another, and another... what is this madness? More of these shadow-things begin to propagate, and you realize you've got trouble!</text>
			<playSound>ddsoulplague_creaking1</playSound>
			<boarders min="3" max="6" class="darkgodtendrils"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT" unique="true">
	<text>A grim sight lays before you. The remains of dozens of ships, some Deep Ones, some Theocracy, are scattered across space here. One intact ship remains, a Deep One Scout that seems to be moving from wreck to wreck.</text>
	<ship load="DEEP_ONE_SCOUT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A few seconds go by before they accept your request to open communications. "Federation... Speak."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>What happened here?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"The answer remains... unclear. No... call for help was made. No... plans to attack the Theocracy were shared. What occurred... remains a mystery." The Deep One pauses. "I'm here... analyzing. Searching for... anything."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Any theories?</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Deep One takes a moment to answer. "I.. believe no fight was had. Rather..." It looks around, as if to check if anybody's looking, "...they were brought here. The... wrecks. Individually." It emphasizes that last word, rather ominously.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Brought here? For what purpose?</text>
								<event>
									<text>"...Tribute." It doesn't elaborate.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Tribute? From who, to what?</text>
										<event>
											<text>It seems hesitant to answer for a while. Eventually, in a hushed tone, it says "I... should not say. It is not... for you to know. Or... for me, to say."</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Insist.</text>
												<event>
													<text>It looks like it's about to answer when, out of nowhere, communications are cut. You begin to move to hail them again when a violent flash from outside stops you in your tracks; the Deep One's ship has just exploded! It sends the nearby ship debris flying in all directions, and your ship with it. Whatever remains is beyond salvaging, and you're left with nothing but questions.</text>
													<recallBoarders/>
													<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
													<damage amount="4"/>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Relent.</text>
												<event>
													<text>The Deep One seems relieved to not be questioned further. "I do believe... we are done here. Feel free to... make use of anything that remains. I... must go, and report." With that, the Deep One leaves, and you're left with the field of debris.</text>
													<instantEscape/>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Let's see what we can find here...</text>
														<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Mind if I scrap all this?</text>
				<event>
					<text>Slightly confused, it blinks, and then answers "I... suppose I am done here. There's... little of value, but feel free to... use what you can." With that, the Deep One leaves, and you're left with the field of debris.</text>
					<instantEscape/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Let's see what we can find here...</text>
						<event load="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_WARSCOUT_LOOT_LIST"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't know what happened to these ships and you don't have any intention of joining them. The Deep One Scout turns to you, realizes your intent, and prepares to fight back.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the ship, and the field.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Uninterested, you turn away from the field and prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DEEPONE_LANIUS" unique="true">
	<text>There's a Lanius ship at this beacon, but it doesn't appear to be doing much. Cautiously, you observe it for a while, but still; nothing.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Try to communicate.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Lanius are notoriously difficult to communicate with, but you try anyways. They do, at the very least, accept your hail and say "Stuck. Need eat. Lights, can't. Help?" They appear to be trying to eat Deep One lights and failing...</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Offer them some scrap to eat.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Lanius gladly accept, but they quickly eat through it and turn back to you. "Need eat more. Help?" They're really hungry, you suppose...</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-20"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice>
						<text>Offer them even more scrap to eat.</text>
						<event>
							<text>This time, it takes them a bit longer to eat through it. Satisfied, they say "Junk eat good. Lights don't eat good. Lights yours, thanks junk. Will send in minute. Any else?"</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-35"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice>
								<text>Yes, else. I kinda like feeding you guys.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"You, more junk?" They look delighted, and take a minute to eat it.</text>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-20"/>
									</item_modify>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>Once they're finished, one of the Lanius speaks up; "Like you. Like you more junk. Staying you, many junk wait me." Moments later, the Deep One lights are beamed into your ship's hold, along with the Lanius! Seems he's up for an adventure, and he's in luck, because there's plenty of scrap to be found when you're working for a Renegade.</text>
											<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="lanius"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>No, else. Thank you.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Understand. Thanks junk again." Moments later, the Deep One lights are beamed into your ship's hold. Somehow, they're in pristine condition despite the Lanius' innumerable attempts at eating them.</text>
									<augment name="DEEPONE_LIGHTS"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>I'm cutting you guys off.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Have help, won't give. Need eat. Take help." Hungry enough to turn on you, the Lanius prepare to attack!</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I can't help, sorry.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Lanius look displeased, "Understand. Try eat lights more." They return to what they were doing and promptly cut communications. Hopefully they manage to eat those lights...</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Whatever they're doing can't be good, attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You give the order to charge the weapons and the Lanius recognize your aggression, they turn and prepare to defend themselves!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You leave the Lanius to their... whatever it is that Lanius do, and prepare to leave the system.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DEEPONE_CONFUSION" unique="true">
	<text>Upon arriving at the beacon, you are immediately hailed by a particularly furious Deep One. Though their translator is lacking, you're certainly able to pick up that you aren't wanted here.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
		<text>(Deep One) Your Deep One offers to step in.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Over the course of a brief conversation between the two Deep Ones you watch as fury is quickly replaced with remorse. As it turns out, pirate raids have been ravaging the local Deep Ones in the area and they've since been wary of strangers. Teary-eyed, he turns to you, and your Deep One explains that he's curious as to your reasoning for coming here.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We're on a quest to save this reality.</text>
				<event>
					<text>He doesn't understand what you mean exactly, but he nods and seems eager to help get you on your way.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
					<damage amount="-7"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We're passing through whilst trying to escape the rebel fleet.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The fury returns to his eyes at the mention of the word "rebel." He mutters something and, with an air of determination, turns away before cutting communications. Your Deep One assures you the fleet won't be getting through without a fight.</text>
					<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We're kicking ass and taking scrap.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Deep One stifles a laugh as you're both met with a blank stare. He begins to try to explain your words when he's cut off by what you can only describe as the garbled fish-man equivalent of screaming bloody murder... Suddenly, comms are cut, and you pick up a teleportation signature! Before anyone else reacts, your equally as confused Deep One intervenes and manages to parse that you've inspired the opposing captain to join you in your revelry... Somehow!</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Try to apologize and leave.</text>
		<event load="DEEPONE_CONFUSION_FLEE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Attack first!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Who cares what the hell they're saying, if it's a fight they want it's a fight they'll get!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="DEEPONE_CONFUSION_FLEE">
	<event>
		<text>You awkwardly manage to make it clear that you mean no harm and the opposing Deep One begrudgingly lets you go, yet you have a feeling that you're still being watched as you cut communications and prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
			<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Do nothing.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Despite your best efforts, it seems the Deep One on the other end has lost his patience. If you won't leave, he'll remove you by force!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Despite your best efforts, it seems the Deep One on the other end has lost his patience. If you won't leave, he'll remove you by force!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<ship name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDTEMPEST">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>You're in the middle of processing the horrors you just witnessed when one final bolt of lightning shoots out from the remains of the strange ship, striking the very room you're standing in... but, instead of being electrocuted and fried to death, a hooded figure harmlessly manifests beside you. You recognize it as being identical to one of the ones you just fought, and prepare to defend yourself, but it makes no move against you. If anything, it seems to be repairing damage and helping around. You're not one to be lulled into a false sense of security, but... you're willing to trust this tentacled freak as long as it remains useful.</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_spawn_warden"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
		<text>(The Minister) "Hah! To think they'd come at their own Hand..."</text>
		<event>
			<text>You ask him what's got him laughing, but he dismisses you completely before leaving the room, mumbling something about inferior beings. This guy's not very forthcoming, is he...</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Dear lord...</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST_STRANGENOISES"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST_ESCAPEDSACRIFICES"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST_BLESSING"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST_STRANGENOISES">
	<text>You accept the hail, but the opposing ship doesn't have a camera feed. Instead, you're only given disturbing audio... a faint, heavy breathing from the other side. No, not breathing; growling. Is this their idea of a prank?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Clear your throat and try to ask what they need.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Despite your best efforts, you receive no answer from the other side of the call. It's just that rhythmic growling...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I've had enough of this. Hang up the call.</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you move to do so, you catch the briefest start of a hushed sentence, "...succulent-" Then, communications are cut as the strange ship whirs to life... they're moving in to attack!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I've REALLY had enough of this. Attack!</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you move to cut communications and begin your assault, you catch the briefest start of a hushed sentence, "...succulent-" Then, the strange ship whirs to life... they're moving in to attack as well!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST_ESCAPEDSACRIFICES">
	<text>You're met with the visage of a human, terribly bloody and bruised. Before you can say a word, they put a finger over their mouth to signal that you should be quiet.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Tilt your head to the side (to mimic confusion).</text>
		<event>
			<text>The human points behind them, into the darkness, before running their thumb across their throat. You get the feeling that they're being held captive and need your help... they must be risking their life to make this call.</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="teleporter">
				<text>(Teleporter) Nod, and flail your fingers around (to mimic teleportation).</text>
				<event>
					<text>They don't quite understand your intention, but you're able to teleport them aboard all the same. As you do so, the lights come on over the call, and the strange ship begins to move... it seems your actions haven't gone unnoticed, as they're moving in to attack!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check on the human before preparing for battle.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You pull the beaten human to their feet, and ask if they feel fine enough to fight. They nod, and move to take whatever position you need of them... do they know they don't still have to be quiet, or do they just like pantomiming?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="human"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Put your hand up to your chin (to mimic thinking).</text>
				<event>
					<text>You're so busy engaging in pantomime that you forget to actually think for a moment, but then it hits you... you just have to sneakily board the ship!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Tighten your shoulders, raise your forearms and bob up and down (to mimic skulking).</text>
						<event>
							<text>The human laughs at your ridiculous display, before immediately covering their mouth as the realization of what they've done washes over them. The last thing you see before the video feed dies is their look of terror as the lights come on behind them... then, the strange ship begins to move. It seems your involvement hasn't gone unnoticed, as they're moving in to attack!</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the signal, and ask them what's going on.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A look of terror overtakes their face as the lights come on behind them, and the video feed dies. You blink a couple times, dumbfounded by your own actions. A few moments then pass, before the strange ship begins to move... it seems your involvement hasn't gone unnoticed, as they're moving in to attack!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST_BLESSING">
	<text>An electric shock runs through your hand as you accept the call, and an immense amount of power surges through it and into your systems somehow. You're expecting this to be some kind of virus, or maybe a cyberattack, but everything quickly returns to normal... if anything, it seems to have made things run MORE efficiently. You look outside, and, to your further confusion, the ship has vanished into thin air. What in the hell just happened...?</text>
	<instantEscape/>
	<upgrade amount="3" system="reactor"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING" unique="true">
	<text>For a moment, everything seems quiet, but then your systems start blaring as requests to hail are spammed. Looking at the space outside, you manage to spot a single ship far off in the distance. They don't seem to be moving... what could they want?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Get closer and try to identify the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You fly in to get a good look at the ship, and they remain still as you do so. You recognize the make of the ship, but not the colors they fly... the hastily painted markings are reminiscent of the many pirate ships throughout the Multiverse, but you can't say you've seen these ones in particular before. As you observe the ship, many more dozens of requests to hail have since been sent.</text>
			<ship load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Accept the request.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_TEMPESTSCAVENGING_HAILLIST"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Attack the ship.</text>
				<event>
					<text>These guys sure are persistent... you'll teach them a thing or two about spamming a Renegade's systems! You move in further, your intentions clear, and the strange ship finally begins to move as they recognize your hostility... looks like you've picked a fight!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ignore the request, and the ship.</text>
				<event>
					<text>This is likely just some amateur pirate trap... and you're no amateur! You put a good distance between you and the strange ship, and the requests to hail eventually go quiet.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Keep to yourself.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't know who's spamming you with requests to hail, but you really wish they'd be a little more considerate and not be so annoying about it. You put a good distance between you and the mystery ship, and the requests to hail eventually go quiet.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_UNION_FIGHT">
	<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT_FIGHT_LOSS" time="40" thisFight="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_TIMER" pos="combat">
			<warning time="6.0" flash="true"/>
			<tooltip>If you do not defeat the Union ship in this amount of time, their esoteric ritual will be completed.</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT_FIGHT_LOSS">
	<text>The space outside warps as the civilians cry out one final, incomprehensible chant...</text>
	<ship hostile="false"/>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and it is done. With their ritual complete, a wave of destructive energy is sent out from the Union ship as it's torn apart, and a cloud of darkness fills the space outside. Some of this strange darkness manages to seep into the newly formed breaches in your ship - and you realize you've got company!</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
			<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
			<damage amount="4"/>
			<damage amount="1" system="random" effect="breach"/>
			<damage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
			<boarders min="3" max="6" class="darkgodtendrils"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>You stopped the ship before they could complete their unknowable ritual, but you've dirtied your hands with Union blood nonetheless. It's hard to win, sometimes...</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT" unique="true">
	<text>To your surprise, it's a Union ship that greets you here. Well, to call it a greeting would be a bit of an exaggeration... it's more like, they hail, threateningly, and say "Give us a human sacrifice or it's YOUR head that's rolling, Renegade!" Not exactly a warm welcome...</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<ship load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_SHADOWCULT_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DARKGOD_CURSED_BOOK">
		<text>(Otherworldly Tome) I need them for my own purposes, you blabbering fool.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Picking up on the reasoning behind the citizen's demands, you brandish the Otherworldly Tome for them to see. Doing so quells their aggression slightly, as they stagger backwards at the sight of it, but then they step back forward, "You may possess THEIR teachings as well, but what makes you any more worthy of using these sacrifices than us? What makes YOU better?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_ENLIGHTENED_HORRORS">
				<text>(Lilith) I am greater, for I pursue the Ascension Rituals, simpleton.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The crimson red texts?! I've caught myself staring at those hellish, incomprehensible diagrams more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DISPARITY">
				<text>(Disparity Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Crystalline Tales, moron.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The vibrant purple texts?! I've caught myself staring at those beautiful, crystalline depictions more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="deeponecultist">
				<text>(Enlightened Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Prayers of Proving, idiot.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The glistening yellow texts?! I've caught myself staring at their strange, dark imagery more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="dddeepone_chosen">
				<text>(Chosen Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Dark Callings, dumbass.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The murky gray texts?! I've caught myself enamored by their hateful illustrations more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDCREW_ILLDRYTHK_ALLGOOBERS">
				<text>(Ill'drythk Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Hymns to Salvation, ignoramus.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The fuzzy brown texts?! I've caught myself staring at those eldritch, plant-like caricatures more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTEMPEST_ALIGNED">
				<text>(Tempest Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Tidings of the Tempest, stupid.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The electric blue texts?! I've caught myself lost in their pictures of vast, stormy clouds more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDULTIMAARMOR">
				<text>(Ultima Armor) I am greater, for I pursue the Neoborn Edicts, imbecile.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The blindingly white texts?! I've caught myself staring at the image of that strange, ominous armor more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_ALIGNED">
				<text>(Soulplague Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Corrupting Whispers, dimwit.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The citizen gasps, "The iridescent rainbow texts?! I've caught myself fascinated by their portrayals of death and decay more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I simply pursue the Beginner's Guide to the Occult.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Is that all? Well, welcome to the club, Feddie; you're no better than us at all! If you think you can step all over us while standing here as our equals, then you've got another thing coming!" The citizen turns around, yelling off into the hallway, "PREPARE THE SACRIFICE! This beacon is being blown to HELL! IN THEIR NAME!" You're going to need to stop them before they do whatever it is they're doing, and fast!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Woah, woah, woah. What the hell are you talking about?</text>
		<event>
			<text>They interrupt you, mid-sentence, "NO! No questions. Not unless you want us to drag this beacon to HELL! WE'VE SEEN HORRORS GREATER THAN DEATH! WE'RE NOT AFRAID OF YOU!" You're not even sure if you're the one they're shouting at... regardless, they've made their demands clear. What's your answer?</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="DARKGOD_CURSED_BOOK">
				<text>(Otherworldly Tome) Fine, then. If playing stupid doesn't satisfy you... I need them for my own purposes, you blabbering fool.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Picking up on the reasoning behind the citizen's demands, you brandish the Otherworldly Tome for them to see. Doing so quells their aggression slightly, as they stagger backwards at the sight of it, but then they step back forward, "You may possess THEIR teachings as well, but what makes you any more worthy of using these sacrifices than us? What makes YOU better?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_ENLIGHTENED_HORRORS">
						<text>(Lilith) I am greater, for I pursue the Ascension Rituals, simpleton.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The crimson red texts?! I've caught myself staring at those hellish, incomprehensible diagrams more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DISPARITY">
						<text>(Disparity Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Crystalline Tales, moron.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The vibrant purple texts?! I've caught myself staring at those beautiful, crystalline depictions more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="deeponecultist">
						<text>(Enlightened Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Prayers of Proving, idiot.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The glistening yellow texts?! I've caught myself staring at their strange, dark imagery more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="dddeepone_chosen">
						<text>(Chosen Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Dark Callings, dumbass.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The murky gray texts?! I've caught myself enamored by their hateful illustrations more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDCREW_ILLDRYTHK_ALLGOOBERS">
						<text>(Ill'drythk Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Hymns to Salvation, ignoramus.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The fuzzy brown texts?! I've caught myself staring at those eldritch, plant-like caricatures more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTEMPEST_ALIGNED">
						<text>(Tempest Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Tidings of the Tempest, stupid.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The electric blue texts?! I've caught myself lost in their pictures of vast, stormy clouds more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDULTIMAARMOR">
						<text>(Ultima Armor) I am greater, for I pursue the Neoborn Edicts, imbecile.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The blindingly white texts?! I've caught myself staring at the image of that strange, ominous armor more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_ALIGNED">
						<text>(Soulplague Crew) I am greater, for I pursue the Corrupting Whispers, dimwit.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The citizen gasps, "The iridescent rainbow texts?! I've caught myself fascinated by their portrayals of death and decay more than once... truly, your cause to THEM is greater than ours. In that case, allow us to serve THEM through serving you; pray be that an ounce of your greatness may rub off on us, o' Feddie one." For a moment, you can't tell if they're completely enthralled by you, or if they're making fun of you, but then a human sacrifice is beamed over from their ship and offered to you in the name of tribute. Being an evil, murderous cultist has its social perks as well, you suppose... assuming you associate yourself with like-minded sickos, that is.</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddhuman_sacrifice"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>I simply pursue the Beginner's Guide to the Occult.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Is that all? Well, welcome to the club, Feddie; you're no better than us at all! If you think you can step all over us while standing here as our equals, then you've got another thing coming!" The citizen turns around, yelling off into the hallway, "PREPARE THE SACRIFICE! This beacon is being blown to HELL! In THEIR name!" You're going to need to stop them before they do whatever it is they're doing, and fast!</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice req="ddhuman_sacrifice">
				<text>(Human Sacrifice) Yeah, alright. You can have it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You beam your prepared human sacrifice over, and the citizen over the comms becomes ecstatic, "OH! You're familiar with THEIR ways...? A member of the Federation...? What are you, some kind of spy?" You shrug, and the citizen chuckles, "Well, thanks, Renegade! We're off to go spill some blood! Maybe a Ritual of Corruption, this time..." Their ship jumps out of the beacon, and you're left somewhat confused and considerably less sacrifice-ful.</text>
					<instantEscape/>
					<removeCrew class="ddhuman_sacrifice">
						<clone>false</clone>
						<text>You cannot clone your human sacrifice, as they are not dead.</text>
					</removeCrew>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice req="LIST_CREW_HUMAN">
				<text>(Human Crew) Yeah, alright. You can have them.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You beam your human over, ignoring their kicking and screaming, and the citizen over the comms calms down a bit, "Finally, FINALLY! We can take lives with our own hands, and take our lives into our own hands!" You shuffle slightly, uncomfortable, and the citizen chuckles, "Well, thanks, Renegade! We're off to go spill some blood! Maybe a Ritual of Corruption, this time..." Their ship jumps out of the beacon, and you're left somewhat horrified and considerably less crew-ful.</text>
					<instantEscape/>
					<removeCrew class="LIST_CREW_HUMAN">
						<clone>false</clone>
						<text>You cannot clone your human crew member, as they are not dead.</text>
					</removeCrew>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I'm not sending anybody over to die, you psycho.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Then you're condemning us ALL to death, FEDDIE! You, us, AND your little buddies... PREPARE TO DIE!" You watch as they stand around a ritual circle in the middle of the room, and an eldritch power flows through them... you're going to need to stop them before they do whatever it is they're doing, and fast!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_MATTERVIRUSDEALER_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="DDDEEP_ONE_BATTLESHIP_DDSOULPLAGUE_CORRUPTION">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_MATTERVIRUSDEALER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_MATTERVIRUSDEALER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_MATTERVIRUSDEALER_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>Now that you have a moment to catch your breath, you're left completely bewildered by what you just witnessed. Soulplague Husks, masquerading as Deep Ones and trying to trick people... if not for the spoils of war and the mess all over the place, you'd figure you just dreamt all that. Still, there's little you can do sitting here pondering... it's time to leave, unanswered qustions in tow.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_ALIGNED">
		<text>(Soulplague Crew) Your Soulplague-aligned crew member makes a strange gurgling noise.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It's hard to think about the madness you've just had the displeasure of living through with your crew member making noises like that... can't they see you're trying to solve a mystery here?</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>I don't get paid enough for this...</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_MATTERVIRUSDEALER" unique="true">
	<text>You feel a little lightheaded as you enter the beacon, but it's quickly brushed aside as a nearby Deep One vessel approaches and hails you. They seem a bit disheveled, their speaking little more than a whisper, "...scrap... give... scrap..." You can hardly make out their form under their robes, but you get the sense that something is off...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hold on. Scrap? What for, and how much?</text>
		<event>
			<text>The cloaked Deep One lowers their head even more, "...reward... boon... favor... 60..." They say no more than that.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Alright, sure. Color me intrigued.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You send the requested scrap over, and it manifests beside the strange Deep One. A moment of silence passes between the two of you, and you're about to break it when the figure derobes and reveals their true form... or, rather, the lack of any form at all. They're little more than a humanoid, oily blob... they feast on the scrap you've sent for a moment, before turning back to you and whispering once more, "...generous... gratitude..." It hits you that they don't speak so much as you simply hear their whispering in your head, and then you realize what it is you're facing: a Soulplague Husk.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-60" max="-60"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Uh... what was my reward, exactly?</text>
						<event>
							<text>They whisper in your head again, "...travel... companion... assist..." You raise an eyebrow, and they melt into a puddle before vanishing... then, a moment later, they somehow manage to reappear beside you! "...captain... spread... love..." The Husk staggers away, and you make a mental note to check the ship's carbon monoxide levels...</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUERANDOM_SUMMON"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No, sorry. Not interested.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You're not running a charity here... nor are you interested in any mystery reward. Your intentions clear, the strange figure derobes and reveals their true form... or, rather, the lack of any form at all. They're little more than a humanoid, oily blob... they roar out, and the Deep One ship makes a strange, wobbly advance towards you. With its weapons hot, your instincts begin to kick in... prepare for battle!</text>
					<ship load="NEUTRAL_DDDEEPONE_MATTERVIRUSDEALER_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="DISTRESS_DEEPONE">
	<event load="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_DRIFTING"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_TRAP"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_MISUNDERSTANDING"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_DRIFTING" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>Arriving at the distress beacon, you spot a Deep One ship off in the distance. It makes no attempt to move.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your attempts to hail the ship are met with failure. They aren't denied, they just don't seem to reach the ship in the first place...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Approach the ship and inspect it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Upon closer inspection, this isn't a ship at all; at least, not anymore. Effectively a pile of shredded scrap, the immortality of the Deep Ones' lights made it look alright from a distance. You begin to wonder how long the wreck and its distress beacon have been drifting like this, when you notice... shuffling, amongst the wreckage?</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Get a closer look.</text>
						<event>
							<text>It's a Deep One! Alive, in space, just... waiting within this wreck! You quickly get your crew to work, and you have the Deep One on board only a couple minutes later. It might be alive, but it still appears to be in terrible condition; it's barely holding on.</text>
							<choice hidden="true" req="medbay" lvl="2">
								<text>(Upg. Medbay) Use your upgraded Medbay to save it.</text>
								<event>
									<text>You put the Deep One in your Medbay and it gets to work. Mere moments later, the Deep One's alright and extremely grateful. "A thousand... blessings, and thank-you's upon you, friend. Without you..." it pauses, "I'm afraid I would've... met my end in that wreck."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>What happened to your ship?</text>
										<event>
											<text>It seems hesitant to answer. After remaining silent for a moment, it says "I'm... sorry. I cannot tell you, for your good... and mine. I know that sounds... menacing, but I ask that you... trust me." A moment passes. "Regardless, I owe you... my life. Seeing that my ship's now in... pieces, I see no better way to... thank you than to fight by your side. You have... my aid, as I've had yours." With that, it turns away. You have questions, but... you're happy to have its aid.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="clonebay" lvl="2">
								<text>(Upg. Clonebay) Use your upgraded Clonebay to save it.</text>
								<event>
									<text>You use your Clonebay to clone the Deep One. Mere moments later, it's alright and extremely grateful. "A thousand... blessings, and thank-you's upon you, friend. Without you..." it pauses, "I'm afraid I would've... met my end in that wreck."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>What happened to your ship?</text>
										<event>
											<text>It seems hesitant to answer. After remaining silent for a moment, it says "I'm... sorry. I cannot tell you, for your good... and mine. I know that sounds... menacing, but I ask that you... trust me." A moment passes. "Regardless, I owe you... my life. Seeing that my ship's now in... pieces, I see no better way to... thank you than to fight by your side. You have... my aid, as I've had yours." With that, it turns away. You have questions, but... you're happy to have its aid.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MEDICAL">
								<text>(Medical Crew) Use your medical crew to save it.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Your crew get to work on stabilizing the Deep One. Mere moments later, it's alright and extremely grateful. "A thousand... blessings, and thank-you's upon you, friend. Without you..." it pauses, "I'm afraid I would've... met my end in that wreck."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>What happened to your ship?</text>
										<event>
											<text>It seems hesitant to answer. After remaining silent for a moment, it says "I'm... sorry. I cannot tell you, for your good... and mine. I know that sounds... menacing, but I ask that you... trust me." A moment passes. "Regardless, I owe you... my life. Seeing that my ship's now in... pieces, I see no better way to... thank you than to fight by your side. You have... my aid, as I've had yours." With that, it turns away. You have questions, but... you're happy to have its aid.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="DRONE_CONTROL_MEDICAL">
								<text>(Medical Drone) Use a medical drone to save it.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Your drone gets to work on stabilizing the Deep One. Mere moments later, it's alright and extremely grateful. "A thousand... blessings, and thank-you's upon you, friend. Without you..." it pauses, "I'm afraid I would've... met my end in that wreck."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>What happened to your ship?</text>
										<event>
											<text>It seems hesitant to answer. After remaining silent for a moment, it says "I'm... sorry. I cannot tell you, for your good... and mine. I know that sounds... menacing, but I ask that you... trust me." A moment passes. "Regardless, I owe you... my life. Seeing that my ship's now in... pieces, I see no better way to... thank you than to fight by your side. You have... my aid, as I've had yours." With that, it turns away. You have questions, but... you're happy to have its aid.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="BOMB_HEAL">
								<text>(Medical Bomb) Use a medical bomb to save it. [-1}]</text>
								<event>
									<text>You use your Medical Bomb to stabilize the Deep One. Mere moments later, it's alright and extremely grateful. "A thousand... blessings, and thank-you's upon you, friend. Without you..." it pauses, "I'm afraid I would've... met my end in that wreck."</text>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="missiles" min="-1" max="-1"/>
									</item_modify>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>What happened to your ship?</text>
										<event>
											<text>It seems hesitant to answer. After remaining silent for a moment, it says "I'm... sorry. I cannot tell you, for your good... and mine. I know that sounds... menacing, but I ask that you... trust me." A moment passes. "Regardless, I owe you... my life. Seeing that my ship's now in... pieces, I see no better way to... thank you than to fight by your side. You have... my aid, as I've had yours." With that, it turns away. You have questions, but... you're happy to have its aid.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="RECON_AND_TELEPORT">
								<text>(Reconstructive Teleporter) Use your Reconstructive Teleporter to save it.</text>
								<event>
									<text>A bit unconventional, but you teleport the Deep One in and out of your ship to heal it with your Reconstructive Teleporter. Mere moments later, the Deep One's alright and extremely grateful. "A thousand... blessings, and thank-you's upon you, friend. Without you..." it pauses, "I'm afraid I would've... met my end in that wreck."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>What happened to your ship?</text>
										<event>
											<text>It seems hesitant to answer. After remaining silent for a moment, it says "I'm... sorry. I cannot tell you, for your good... and mine. I know that sounds... menacing, but I ask that you... trust me." A moment passes. "Regardless, I owe you... my life. Seeing that my ship's now in... pieces, I see no better way to... thank you than to fight by your side. You have... my aid, as I've had yours." With that, it turns away. You have questions, but... you're happy to have its aid.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>I can't save it.</text>
								<event>
									<text>The Deep One, having suffered too much trauma, dies mere moments later. With nothing left to do, you're forced to move on. Damn it all...</text>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Give up.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh well, you tried. If they want help the least they can do is answer your calls... You turn away and prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You've got better things to be doing than saving people. You turn away and prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_SLUG_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_CLAN_FIGHT">
	<destroyed>
		<text>Though the Deep Ones aren't here to thank you, you feel rather good about yourself as you scrap the Clansman ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>Though the Deep Ones aren't here to thank you, you feel rather good about yourself as you scrap the Clansman ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<ship name="SHIP_DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_DEEPONE_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DEEPONES">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_DEEPONE_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_DEEPONE_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_DEEPONE_WIN">
	<text>Once you're satisfied with what you've salvaged, the Clansmen hail you, "Hope you weren't exxxxxpecting much in the way of thanksssss, Fed, that wasssss our mark. Ssssstill, not like they were going down easssssy..." The Slug pauses for a second. "Guesssss we'll be calling it even. Be ssssseeing you, Fed." With that, the Clansmen jump out of the beacon. Not exactly a standing ovation, but they seemed thankful enough.</text>
</event>

<eventList name="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_GETOUT">
	<event>
		<text>Miraculously, you manage to escape from the fight unscathed and find somewhere quiet to keep your distance while the FTL charges.</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
			<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Do nothing.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Though your ship catches a few stray blasts, you manage to escape from the fight and find somewhere quiet to recuperate while the FTL charges.</text>
		<damage amount="3"/>
		<choice>
			<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
			<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Do nothing.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your ship catches more crossfire than you would've liked, but you do manage to escape and find somewhere quiet to recuperate while the FTL charges.</text>
		<damage amount="8"/>
		<choice>
			<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
			<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Do nothing.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your ship catches more crossfire than you would've liked, but you do manage to escape and find somewhere quiet to recuperate while the FTL charges.</text>
		<damage amount="8"/>
		<choice>
			<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
			<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Do nothing.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>Upon arriving at the distress beacon, you're immediately greeted with the sight of shots whizzing past your window... You've dropped into the middle of a fight between two ships! It appears some Slug Clansmen must be on the hunt for Deep Ones for sport, and you'll have to pick a side fast unless you want to get caught in the crossfire.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the Clansmen.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You face the Clansmen and prepare to attack. Deciding you're the bigger threat, they turn to face you. Meanwhile, the Deep One ship immediately seizes the opportunity to escape and leave the system. Suppose you won't be getting any thanks...</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_SLUG_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the Deep Ones.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You face the Deep Ones and prepare to attack. Deciding you're the bigger threat, they turn to face you. Meanwhile, the Clansmen seem to have ceased firing; they're watching the fight from a distance. Suppose you won't be getting any help...</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Take your chances; try to escape.</text>
		<event load="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_CLANSMAN_GETOUT"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_TRAP" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>You arrive at the distress beacon, but the Deep One ship here quickly turns to face you, weapons charging; you've become the victim of an ambush. Though not typically malevolent, perhaps something's made these Deep Ones desperate... regardless, it's time to defend yourself!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_DEEPONE_MISUNDERSTANDING" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>There's a Deep One settlement on a nearby moon here. You surmise that it must be the source of the distress call, but nothing seems immediately wrong from this distance.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Get closer and investigate.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Nothing seems out of the ordinary here. Ships are flying in and out at a regular pace and Deep Ones are casually roaming the streets undisturbed.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Land and narrow down the source of the distress call.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You land, immersing yourself in the surrounding Deep One architecture; a sea of blues and purples, complete with an excessive amount of blinding turquoise lights. The Deep Ones don't seem to mind your presence here, and eventually you home in on the source of the distress call. You're taken to a quiet corner of the settlement, one of the smaller houses at the end of the residential district. There still isn't anything that strikes you as an emergency as you stand at the door.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Knock.</text>
						<event>
							<text>No answer is made, and you can't hear any noise from inside.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Knock again.</text>
								<event>
									<text>This time, you knock much louder. Something shuffles around inside, but nobody comes to answer the door.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Knock again...</text>
										<event>
											<text>As you go to begin knocking a third time, the door is swung open; you're met with the sight of a dishevelled, old Deep One. It eyes you down, taking in your uniform before speaking, "Federation, here... at my door? For... what purpose?"</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>There's a distress call emitting from inside your house.</text>
												<event>
													<text>"A d-" The Deep One pauses briefly, taken aback. "Excuse me... for a moment." It closes the door, and you hear further shuffling. It doesn't take long for it to return with a distress beacon in hand, though this one seems to be in a serious amount of disrepair. "Is this... the source of the call?"</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Indeed, that's a distress beacon.</text>
														<event>
															<text>Obviously embarrassed, it responds "My... goodness. This was sold to me by a... traveling Free Mantis salesman, who had claimed... it to be a 'De-Stress' beacon... Unless, I had just... misheard him." It thinks on this for a moment before continuing, "I'm so... terribly sorry for troubling you, officer. I... wish there were any way I could make this... up to you, but, I don't think there is."</text>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
																<text>(Deep One Crew) Maybe there is?</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your Deep One whispers something to the older one before you, and a sense of dread seems to overcome its face. It nods, murmuring something in return, before closing the door and vanishing back inside. You ask your Deep One what that was about, but it hushes you and insists that you both wait a moment.</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>We'll wait, then.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>After waiting for a while, the Deep One returns, a briefcase in hand. "Let us go, then... if that is what they decree." It puts extra stress on the word they, and you raise an eyebrow, but your Deep One merely brushes it off. You all return to the ship, the old Deep One in tow, and it seems intent on joining your crew. You're not sure what was said to convince it to abandon everything it has going on here, but... you're not one to turn down new deckhands.</text>
																			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
																			<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_FREEMAN">
																<text>(Free Mantis Crew) "Do not doubts traveler-salesing!"</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your Free Mantis smacks the beacon in the Deep One's hand, and it suddenly emits a wave of soothing energy... wow, that IS de-stressing. Equally as amazed by this, the Deep One tries its best to speak amidst its sighs of relief, "This... is wonderful... Here, take... this... It's the least... I can do to... repay this... immense favor..." It slowly trudges back inside, its steps steeped in bliss, and it returns with a massive pile of goodies in hand... you're not sure if it's giving this stuff to you in its best mind, but you're not one to turn down hospitality. You accept the reward, bidding the Deep One farewell, and then begin your trek back to the ship.</text>
																	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SLUG">
																<text>(Slug Crew) "Heh, typical sssscam!"</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your Slug gives a hearty laugh, smacking the small device out of the Deep One's hands in the process, and it suddenly emits a wave of soothing energy... wow, that IS de-stressing. This wave seems to have the opposite effect on your Slug, as they scream and run back to the ship in horror, but you figure that they're probably just terrified of their own mechanically-gifted power. Equally as amazed by this, the Deep One tries its best to speak amidst its sighs of relief, "This... is wonderful... Here, take... this... It's the least... I can do to... repay this... immense favor..." It slowly trudges back inside, its steps steeped in bliss, and it returns with a massive pile of goodies in hand... you're not sure if it's giving this stuff to you in its best mind, but you're not one to turn down hospitality. You accept the reward, bidding the Deep One farewell, and then begin your trek back to the ship.</text>
																	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
																<text>(Engineer Crew) Have your engineer inspect the beacon.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your engineer weighs the small device in their hands for a few moments, before giving it a decisive SMACK with their wrench. The beacon roars to life, and it suddenly emits a wave of soothing energy... wow, that IS de-stressing. Equally as amazed by this, the Deep One tries its best to speak amidst its sighs of relief, "This... is wonderful... Here, take... this... It's the least... I can do to... repay this... immense favor..." It slowly trudges back inside, its steps steeped in bliss, and it returns with a massive pile of goodies in hand... you're not sure if it's giving this stuff to you in its best mind, but you're not one to turn down hospitality. You accept the reward, bidding the Deep One farewell, and then begin your trek back to the ship.</text>
																	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>You wouldn't happen to have any... junk lying around, would you?</text>
																<event>
																	<text>"...Junk?" It looks around for a moment, before its gaze meets the beacon in its hands, "This... would be junk, now, I... suppose." The Deep One hands it to you, apologizes again, and you make your way back onto your ship and out of the settlement. This was a big waste of time, for the most part, but you do get to break down the beacon and get the barest amount of something out of it...</text>
																	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Enough of this, break the door down!</text>
										<event>
											<text>As you move to break the door down, it's swung open; you're met with the sight of a dishevelled, old Deep One. It eyes you down, taking in your uniform before speaking, "Federation, here... at my door? For... what purpose?"</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>There's a distress call emitting from inside your house.</text>
												<event>
													<text>"A d-" The Deep One pauses briefly, taken aback. "Excuse me... for a moment." It closes the door, and you hear further shuffling. It doesn't take long for it to return with a distress beacon in hand, though this one seems to be in a serious amount of disrepair. "Is this... the source of the call?"</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Indeed, that's a distress beacon.</text>
														<event>
															<text>Obviously embarrassed, it responds "My... goodness. This was sold to me by a... traveling Free Mantis salesman, who had claimed... it to be a 'De-Stress' beacon... Unless, I had just... misheard him." It thinks on this for a moment before continuing, "I'm so... terribly sorry for troubling you, officer. I... wish there were any way I could make this... up to you, but, I don't think there is."</text>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DEEPONES">
																<text>(Deep One Crew) Maybe there is?</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your Deep One whispers something to the older one before you, and a sense of dread seems to overcome its face. It nods, murmuring something in return, before closing the door and vanishing back inside. You ask your Deep One what that was about, but it hushes you and insists that you both wait a moment.</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>We'll wait, then.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>After waiting for a while, the Deep One returns, a briefcase in hand. "Let us go, then... if that is what they decree." It puts extra stress on the word they, and you raise an eyebrow, but your Deep One merely brushes it off. You all return to the ship, the old Deep One in tow, and it seems intent on joining your crew. You're not sure what was said to convince it to abandon everything it has going on here, but... you're not one to turn down new deckhands.</text>
																			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
																			<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_FREEMAN">
																<text>(Free Mantis Crew) "Do not doubts traveler-salesing!"</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your Free Mantis smacks the beacon in the Deep One's hand, and it suddenly emits a wave of soothing energy... wow, that IS de-stressing. Equally as amazed by this, the Deep One tries its best to speak amidst its sighs of relief, "This... is wonderful... Here, take... this... It's the least... I can do to... repay this... immense favor..." It slowly trudges back inside, its steps steeped in bliss, and it returns with a massive pile of goodies in hand... you're not sure if it's giving this stuff to you in its best mind, but you're not one to turn down hospitality. You accept the reward, bidding the Deep One farewell, and then begin your trek back to the ship.</text>
																	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SLUG">
																<text>(Slug Crew) "Heh, typical sssscam!"</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your Slug gives a hearty laugh, smacking the small device out of the Deep One's hands in the process, and it suddenly emits a wave of soothing energy... wow, that IS de-stressing. This wave seems to have the opposite effect on your Slug, as they scream and run back to the ship in horror, but you figure that they're probably just terrified of their own mechanically-gifted power. Equally as amazed by this, the Deep One tries its best to speak amidst its sighs of relief, "This... is wonderful... Here, take... this... It's the least... I can do to... repay this... immense favor..." It slowly trudges back inside, its steps steeped in bliss, and it returns with a massive pile of goodies in hand... you're not sure if it's giving this stuff to you in its best mind, but you're not one to turn down hospitality. You accept the reward, bidding the Deep One farewell, and then begin your trek back to the ship.</text>
																	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
																<text>(Engineer Crew) Have your engineer inspect the beacon.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Your engineer weighs the small device in their hands for a few moments, before giving it a decisive SMACK with their wrench. The beacon roars to life, and it suddenly emits a wave of soothing energy... wow, that IS de-stressing. Equally as amazed by this, the Deep One tries its best to speak amidst its sighs of relief, "This... is wonderful... Here, take... this... It's the least... I can do to... repay this... immense favor..." It slowly trudges back inside, its steps steeped in bliss, and it returns with a massive pile of goodies in hand... you're not sure if it's giving this stuff to you in its best mind, but you're not one to turn down hospitality. You accept the reward, bidding the Deep One farewell, and then begin your trek back to the ship.</text>
																	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>You wouldn't happen to have any... junk lying around, would you?</text>
																<event>
																	<text>"...Junk?" It looks around for a moment, before its gaze meets the beacon in its hands, "This... would be junk, now, I... suppose." The Deep One hands it to you, apologizes again, and you make your way back onto your ship and out of the settlement. This was a big waste of time, for the most part, but you do get to break down the beacon and get the barest amount of something out of it...</text>
																	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Break the door down.</text>
								<event>
									<text>What if there's an emergency in there? You don't have time to be standing around, idle! You throw yourself against the door, and it provides little resistance; it doesn't come down as much as you tear right through it. You begin pondering as to the logistics behind Deep One architecture, but your thoughts are quickly interrupted by the Deep One in front of you. Screaming in terror, it runs past you and through the hole you've just created. Suppose you won't get a chance to explain yourself...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Uh oh.</text>
										<event>
											<text>You spend a moment standing there dumbfounded, and you've only barely gotten back outside when alarms begin to blare around you! What was once a quiet street explodes into a hub of activity as Deep Ones escape their homes in panic. You had good intentions, but, it looks like things have quickly gotten out of control... and they're only going to get worse unless you get out of here quickly!</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>It's time to leave!</text>
												<event>
													<text>Besides the few looks of terror you catch, your sprint back to your ship generally goes unnoticed. However, as you make your ascent back into space, a Deep One ship begins to tail you; looks like you're not getting out of this without a fight... and to think, you were just trying to help!</text>
													<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Must be a false alarm.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Everything seems to be in order here. Satisfied, you turn away from the settlement and prepare to leave the system.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Not interested.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You can't afford to be distracted, you have a mission to complete. Turning away from the settlement, you prepare to leave the system.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="DDDEEP_ONE_DESTROYER_SOULPLAGUE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION_FIGHT_WIN_DESTROYED"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION_FIGHT_WIN_DEADCREW"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION_FIGHT_WIN_DESTROYED">
	<text>You're still trying to process what just happened as another roar breaks out, this time all around you, and the space outside begins to... shift? An odd darkness envelops your ship, as realization dawns on you: some impossibly large THING is trying to swallow you whole. You aren't sure what it is, or what exactly's going on, but you know you've got to get out of here, and fast!</text>
	<playSound>ddsoulplague_assault</playSound>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDSOULPLAGUEHEART</changeBackground>
	<backgroundObject name="DDSOULPLAGUEAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddsoulplagueaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Make a break for it!</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you move to make your escape, the thing's tendrils crash into your ship, and more Soulplague Husks begin to flood in from the resulting breaches. They're trying to prevent your getaway!</text>
			<boarders min="2" max="3" class="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUERANDOM_SUMMON_ENEMY"/>
			<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
			<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION_FIGHT_WIN_DEADCREW">
	<text>One of the Husks melts into a puddle on the floor before you, and you watch as its matter twists and writhes... as it takes on a new form. Rather than any being, though, it instead resembles some sort of oily weapon...</text>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_WEAPONS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>What in the hell is going on...?</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're still trying to process what just happened as another roar breaks out, this time all around you, and the space outside begins to... shift? An odd darkness envelops your ship, as realization dawns on you: some impossibly large THING is trying to swallow you whole. You aren't sure what it is, or what exactly's going on, but you know you've got to get out of here, and fast!</text>
			<playSound>ddsoulplague_assault</playSound>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDSOULPLAGUEHEART</changeBackground>
			<backgroundObject name="DDSOULPLAGUEAURA_BACKGROUND">
				<layer z="0">background</layer>
				<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
				<anim>ddsoulplagueaura_bg</anim>
			</backgroundObject>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Make a break for it!</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you move to make your escape, the thing's tendrils crash into your ship, and more Soulplague Husks begin to flood in from the resulting breaches. They're trying to prevent your getaway!</text>
					<boarders min="2" max="3" class="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUERANDOM_SUMMON_ENEMY"/>
					<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
					<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>Though you can't pinpoint why, you feel uneasy as you arrive at the distress beacon and are met with a Deep One ship. Its engines are off, but it otherwise appears to be powered... what exactly do they need help with?</text>
	<ship load="DISTRESS_DDDEEPONE_SOULPLAGUEINCURSION_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the drifting ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your hail seems to automatically connect, but you're not quite sure what you're seeing. The screen is extremely dark, though not quite completely black, and you can't really make much out... save for some figures on the opposite side of the room. A strange gurgling can be heard over the call... you know Deep Ones can be weird, but are they typically THIS weird? If they're aware that they've been hailed, they don't seem to want to act on it. Or do much of anything, really. They're just standing there.</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_ALIGNED">
				<text>(Soulplague Crew) Have your Soulplague-aligned crew member gurgle back.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your crew member mimics the odd gurgling, and the figures in the back of the room snap their heads to face the screen. You hear as one of them roars at you, to your bewilderment, before they all collectively sprint out of the room... then, their ship's engines roar to life! Whatever the hell's going on, they seem to be making a move on your ship. Get ready!</text>
					<playSound>ddsoulplague_assault</playSound>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>As you're preparing for battle, a Soulplague Husk teleports into the room next to you, but you realize it isn't hostile... it seems intent on joining you. You weren't aware that Husks could perform mutinies, but you figure your crew member's gurgling somehow convinced it to do so. Still, its allies don't seem to be so agreeable!</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="ddsoulplague_husk_deepone"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Clear your throat.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You cough slightly, and the figures in the back of the room snap their heads to face the screen. You hear as one of them roars at you, to your bewilderment, before they all collectively sprint out of the room... then, their ship's engines roar to life! Whatever the hell's going on, they seem to be making a move on your ship. Get ready!</text>
					<playSound>ddsoulplague_assault</playSound>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Cut the call. This is weird.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Indeed, you end communications with the strange Deep Ones and aren't once bothered by them as you prepare to leave the beacon.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the ship, before they realize you're here.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You move to engage the Deep One ship, and readings from your ship's systems make you realize something is off... before you can hesitate, though, the opposing ship's engines roar to life! Whatever the hell's going on, they seem to be making a move on your ship. Get ready!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them. If they want help, they can ask for it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>And, yet... they don't ask for it. You're left completely undisturbed as you sit there, preparing to leave the beacon.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE">
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_DEEP"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_DEEP"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_DEEP"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_DEEP"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_PIRATE"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_REBEL"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_LANIUS"/>
</eventList>

<event name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_DEEP">
	<text load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_DEEP_TEXT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_DEEPONE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_DEEP_TEXT">
	<text>The Deep One ship at this beacon doesn't take kindly to your sudden appearance and it turns towards you, weapons charging! They're typically not aggressors... Regardless of what's got them on edge, you have to defend yourself!</text>
	<text>Upon entering the system, you receive a hail; "Federation, you... are not welcome here. This space... is sacred!" You must be encroaching on their territory, and they see it fit to have you removed by force!</text>
	<text>A Deep One ship descends upon you, and you're sent a series of one-word messages that all say the same thing: "TRIBUTE." Vague and ominous, but one thing's for sure; it's time for battle.</text>
</textList>

<event name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY">
	<text load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_TEXT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_ROCK_ALL" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_THEOCRACY_TEXT">
	<text>A Deep One ship whizzes past your view, and hot on their tail is the Theocracy! Whether they think you're a bigger threat or an easier target is unclear, but, regardless of their reasoning, they focus their attention on you and allow the Deep One ship to escape. A thankless job, being a distraction...</text>
	<text>There's a Rock ship awaiting you at this beacon. Weapons primed, they charge towards you; it seems they're keen to prey on more than just the Deep Ones. Show them what happens when you try to prey on an apex predator.</text>
	<text>You receive a hail, "Hah, it's nothing personal, Feddie. Crusades don't pay for themselves." With that, a Theocracy ship flies into view and prepares to engage.</text>
</textList>

<event name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_PIRATE">
	<text load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_PIRATE_TEXT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_PIRATE_TEXT">
	<text>Thriving in the unruly conditions, pirate ships aren't uncommon in the vaguely controlled territory that is Deep One space. One comes at you now, weapons hot!</text>
	<text>There's a few pirate vessels gathered here. It's unclear what they're up to, and most of them flee at your sudden appearance, but one in particular seems confident in its ability to take you on; it approaches, ready to attack.</text>
	<text>In Deep One territory, it always pays to be wary, and you get the feeling that something's not quite right at this beacon... Whether it's preternatural instincts or blind luck, seconds later, a pirate ship reveals itself from behind a nearby satellite and moves in to attack!</text>
</textList>

<event name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_REBEL">
	<text load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_REBEL_TEXT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_AUTO_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_REBEL_TEXT">
	<text>The Rebels rarely travel through Deep One space themselves, but there's nothing stopping them from sending fleets of Auto-ships to do their dirty work for them. Likewise, there's nothing stopping you from making short work of them.</text>
	<text>Though empty, this beacon appears to be under watch by a Rebel Auto-ship. You're not sure why it's standing guard in territory belonging to the Deep Ones, let alone in empty space, but you're not given much of a chance to think about it; here it comes!</text>
	<text>"Vessel detected. Identity: Federation. Location: Sector Deep-78314920746128..." It continues for a while, before finally finishing, "...62103. Protocol: Neutralization." With that, it bares its weapons and begins its assault.</text>
</textList>

<event name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_LANIUS">
	<text load="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_LANIUS_TEXT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="HOSTILE_DEEPONE_LANIUS_TEXT">
	<text>Lanius ships are crowding around a gigantic Deep One wreck present at this beacon. They've eaten around the lights, but it still appears to have plenty of metal left... they must not all be content with their meal, however; one of the ships breaks off from the wreck and decides you're its next feast!</text>
	<text>Unsurprisingly, the Lanius find Deep One sectors to be quite comfortable. Effectively lawless and unguarded save for the Deep Ones' settlements and fleets, the Lanius are practically free to roam and eat what they like. Unfortunately for you, that includes Renegades!</text>
	<text>You're hailed by a nearby Lanius ship whose translator seems especially lacking, "Eaten need, not eat, eat. Thank." Moments later, their weapons go online and they begin their assault!</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEEPONE_SURRENDER">
	<text load="DEEPONE_SURRENDER_TEXT"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their offer.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>We will not accept surrender!</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="DEEPONE_SURRENDER_TEXT">
	<text>The Deep Ones, as hot-headed as they are, still don't have complete disregard for their lives. They're offering a surrender.</text>
	<text>You receive several messages that are composed of complete gibberish and accompanied by bribes. You assume this is their idea of surrendering.</text>
	<text>The Deep Ones hail and struggle to speak your tongue, "For...give... Please."</text>
	<text>In a moment of clarity, the Deep Ones forget their rage for but a moment and plead for their lives.</text>
	<text>As the opposing Deep One ship buckles and begins to collapse, you receive a desperate hail for surrender.</text>
	<text>Fear's not a look that well-suits the Deep Ones. Nevertheless, they cower before you, begging to be spared.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEEPONE_ESCAPE">
	<text>Your scanners are picking up FTL signatures, the Deep Ones are trying to escape!</text>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
</event>

<event name="DESTROYED_DEEPONE">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_DEEPONE"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_DEEPONE">
	<text>As you scrap the strange ship, you muse to yourself that the Deep Ones would've been better off had they never left the water if the likes of you are all that awaits them in space.</text>
	<text>The Deep One ship sends one last hail as it splits into two, yet your translator can't even begin to decipher it.</text>
	<text>During the scrapping operation, your crew comments that the lights adorning the Deep Ones' hull appear to never die. You find that quite ironic.</text>
	<text>You pull up a database on Old Earth marine life as your crew scraps the ship. The Deep Ones have fine taste in ship architecture, yet they have finer scrap.</text>
	<text>Though you barely understand the creatures you've just blown up, you can't help but feel like it didn't have to end this way.</text>
	<text>You breathe a sigh of relief once it's been confirmed that the threat's been eliminated. There's a certain lingering dread that accompanies those in the presence of the Deep Ones...</text>
	<text>The ship breaks apart much more violently than you expected it to, sending cyan debris in all directions. Or was it turquoise?</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_DEEPONE">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_DEEPONE"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_DEEPONE">
	<text>As you wander the halls of the strange ship, you muse to yourself that the Deep Ones would've been better off had they never left the water if the likes of you are all that awaits them in space.</text>
	<text>While cleaning out the ship you come across a dying Deep One who meets your gaze and mutters something before collapsing, yet your translator can't even begin to decipher it.</text>
	<text>During the scrapping operation, your crew comments that the lights adorning the Deep Ones' halls appear to never die. You find that quite ironic.</text>
	<text>You pull up a database on Old Earth marine life as your crew explores the now-empty ship. The Deep Ones have fine taste in ship architecture, yet they have finer scrap.</text>
	<text>Though you barely understand the creatures you've just slaughtered, you can't help but feel like it didn't have to end this way.</text>
	<text>You breathe a sigh of relief once it's been confirmed that the crew's been eliminated. There's a certain lingering dread that accompanies those in the presence of the Deep Ones...</text>
	<text>Amidst scrapping, your crew begins to argue about what color the lights the Deep Ones use are. Obviously they're turquoise, but you don't want to ruin their fun.</text>
</textList>

</FTL>