<FTL>

<ship name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="DDFALSE_RADIANCE_ARCHANGEL_GATEKEEPER">
	<destroyed>
		<text>You did it! By Father, you actually did it! It's no wonder my sister brought you here... you're amazing!</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="1" blue="false">
			<text>Visualize a victory - hard-fought, and welcomed even harder.</text>
			<event load="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
			<text>Visualize a victory - hard-fought, and welcomed even harder.</text>
			<event load="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER_FIGHT_WIN_DEATH"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>Power over time and space... the window is brief, but my sister's vessel should be able to harness the Archangel's power - she needs all the strength that she can get if she's going to fix herself back up.</text>
	<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGATEKEEPERDEFEAT</achievement>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize power - something needed in times of crises, even if it's often responsible for causing them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Yes, like that! She can only do so much, with things as they are, but... it should be enough to at least turn back the clock a bit, and restore your ship's integrity. As well, we should be able to locate the other Archangels with it - Father knows we'll need every advantage we can get, on the journey ahead... speaking of! I guess it's time to get going? I know everything's, um... foggy, so I'll be doing my best to guide you through it all, but... I know that you can do it! You just proved that you can! So, ah... let's do it together, okay?</text>
			<variable name="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gatekeeper" op="set" val="1"/>
			<damage amount="-27"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a journey - that which lies ahead, filled with moments of hope and strife alike.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER_FIGHT_WIN_DEATH">
	<text>I wouldn't worry about my sister's vessel, too much. With each defeat of an Archangel, there should be more than enough leftover power to fix herself back up. Um, speaking of power! Complete dominion over time and space... the window is brief, but my sister's vessel should be able to harness it now.</text>
	<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGATEKEEPERDEFEAT</achievement>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunique_theshade" all_skills="1">The Shade</crewMember>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize power - something needed in times of crises, even if it's often responsible for causing them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Yes, like that! She can only do so much, with things as they are, but... it should be enough to at least turn back the clock a bit, and restore your ship's integrity. As well, we should be able to locate the other Archangels with it - Father knows we'll need every advantage we can get, on the journey ahead... speaking of! I guess it's time to get going? I know everything's, um... foggy, so I'll be doing my best to guide you through it all, but... I know that you can do it! You just proved that you can! So, ah... let's do it together, okay?</text>
			<variable name="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gatekeeper" op="set" val="1"/>
			<damage amount="-27"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a journey - that which lies ahead, filled with moments of hope and strife alike.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER">
	<text>Wait - I'm sensing something. Is that...
	
	...I think you need to get out of there, now!</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a friendly gesture - welcome, but far too late to leave an impact.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Oh, Father... it's here, isn't it? GATEKEEPER? If it's already found you, I don't think there's any use in running... I... I, ah... I don't know how I can help...</text>
			<ship load="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
			<deathEvent thisFight="true">DDDEATH_ARCHANGELPROTOCOL</deathEvent>
			<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize hope - that which doesn't dwindle in the face of anything.</text>
				<event>
					<text>...Really? You've got this? I... well, alright! At the very least... I, um, can try to elaborate on its powers, I think.
					
					Archangel Protocol: GATEKEEPER... its entourage of Lightborne and key-system both rely on the manipulation of time - it will try to slow you down long enough for its Focus weapons to chain, and begin obliterating your ship. If you can prevent anything, it should be that - do not allow those weapons to continuously chain!
					
					However, it's also worth noting two things about the Archangels... firstly, their crystalline armor - if you try to break it too fast, you're just going to be swarmed by their enslaved Shadows. Unless you have the means to take on a small army, I'd be tactical with your strikes. Secondly, something that applies to all members of the False Radiance - it is NOT safe to board them with several people at once. Something about that... weird, ethereal glow of theirs makes things destabilize rapidly when sharing a room with each other.
					
					Well, that's everything I can think to share - I believe in you! Give it hell for me, won't you?!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_LOREDROP">
	<text>Well, judging from what my sister's seen - you're capable, at least! Don't, um... sell yourself short. You've travelled far to get here, on her behalf.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a sibling - trusted, caring and always by one's side.</text>
		<event>
			<text>My sister? Right now, she's somewhat dormant, but... she can still sense things through her vessel - the same way I can feel you through her, sort of.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a shadow - ever-present, ever-dark, forever running from the light.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Right, her vessel! It's been with you for some time now - it carries my sister around. We can't, um... carry ourselves, so... normally we'd all have one, but... Father prefers to keep me close. Honestly, I can't remember why, or, ah... how I got here... or where exactly 'here' is...
					
					...truthfully, I'm... kind of terrified right now. I've never had a lapse in my memory like this before, or needed to rely on the senses of one of my sisters. And, my sister... the Lightborne, they...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a light - ever-welcome, ever-bright, forever keeping the shadows at bay.</text>
						<event>
							<text>No, you've got it wrong. There's nothing welcoming about the Lightborne... well, at least the majority of them, right now - nor are the Shadows the bad guys here! My sister's quite a bit more knowledgeable on the subject than I, but, essentially... they're sort of, like, tyrants?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a Rebel - tyrrany, made manifest.</text>
								<event>
									<text>M-maybe, based on what little my sister's overheard on the subject. Though, it's less to do with, like, super-space-fascism and more, ah... blindness. What you're feeling right now, this senseless nothingness - it's not just an infliction upon yourself, but this entire reality. The Lightborne, they... they sought something from Father. In exchange, they were asked to swear away everything - everything, but their trust in him. In divinity.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize a father - a frightful figure, quick to show disapproval.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Yeah, that's him... you two HAVE met, right? You must've if sister's here... well, regardless, the Lightborne took his deal. They swore away all that he'd asked them to, and then some - all in the name of peace with the Shadows. From Father, they'd requested a mutual leader... someone who could keep both parties in check, and ensure their coexistence. And, so... he sent my sister.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize a light - worthy of fear, but paradoxically striving for peace.</text>
												<event>
													<text>Right, well... though the two sides used to always war, some Lightborne were less keen on it than others. Four in particular sought Father's audience, and sealed this reality's fate... and, though they're long-gone now, Father thought to assist my sister in her overseeing duties by constructing four lesser divinities, in their likenesses.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a divinity - omniscient, and as such, likely visualizing you in turn.</text>
														<event>
															<text>These lesser divinities, dubbed the Archangel Protocols, were formed to embody everything the Lightborne had become. Magnificent, divinely-empowered... and blind.
															
															
															
															Archangel Protocol: GATEKEEPER - a being granted power over both time and space. A guardian, first and foremost - meant to protect against Multiversal intrusion.
															
															Archangel Protocol: GRAVEDIGGER - a being granted power over death, and the ability to restore energy. A safeguard against entropy, should the Lightborne begin to burn out within their freshly-grayed existence.
															
															Archangel Protocol: GODCORE - a being granted power over divine fire... a weapon of destruction, primarily. It's main purpose was to be beared against the Shadows, should they prove themselves discontent.
															
															And, finally... Archangel Protocol: GENESIS. Other than my sister, it was granted both the greatest power, and greatest honor, of all - the power to manipulate... everything, in the truest sense of the word. It was a gateway, greater than any other - it could move anything, anywhere. Between worlds, galaxies, realities - even CLUSTERS! Father had a particular fondness for this one, finding it a convenient way to move things places... even if it was often on a whim.</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Visualize genesis - the creation of everything.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Above even GENESIS, though... was my sister! A true overseer, she had power over the Archangels - a collective force used to keep the Lightborne and Shadows in their states of endless, senseless bliss. That, and... collect what was asked of her, by Father. He'd ask for Shadows, primarily - though for what, she didn't know.</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>Visualize the past - that which will never again come to pass.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>I'm getting to that! You see, sister has something of an... obsession. Much greater than I, or our other sister... she wishes to see Mother again. Father's made it a point that it'll never happen - not in a million, billion, or even trillion years - but she's never been one to give up hope on the matter.
																			
																			And so, one day... when Father wasn't looking, she moved to wield GENESIS. Power over everything, as she saw it, was the power to defy even Father - the power to bring Mother back. And, perhaps she was right, but... she wasn't ready for what she'd see. What GENESIS would see.</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Visualize a mistake - one rectified by neither foresight or hindsight.</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>GENESIS forged that link, that connection to our Mother - and it wasn't all hell that broke loose, or some other great catastrophe... but, rather, the visage of a small mirror. In that mirror, my sister saw herself - not as others perceived her, as Father's blade... but as the little girl she'd never gotten to be. Her inner-child, so to speak... or, that's how she rationalized it, at least. I'm not so sure, but, um... it's not that important, anyways.
																					
																					What WAS important, though... was GENESIS. In that strange mirror, its great, many eyes could see something as well - exactly WHAT it was remains a mystery, even to my sister, but... whatever it saw, it was enough to change something inside of it. It acted on its own accord, severing its interdimensional connection and whisking the mirror away almost immediately - but, by then, the damage had already been done. GENESIS' center now radiated an ethereal, multi-colored glow... a series of colors more beautiful than anything the Lightborne had sworn away. And it BROKE the Archangel.</text>
																					<choice hidden="true">
																						<text>Visualize a broken clock - right twice a day, and no less wrong for it.</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>It had never known anything but the divinity it swore upon - the very same divinity it was borne by. And, yet... despite having power over everything, it could never begin to comprehend the resplendent radiance now emanating from within it. A taste of TRUE divinity - color, feeling, thoughts... that which had been sworn away, prior to its creation, and kept away from it ever since. GENESIS had felt it all, now... and it, ah... wanted more.
																							
																							My sister thought to stop its newly-birthed machinations, and return the Archangel to its state of senselessness... but it fought against her. It moved to enlighten its kin - the GATEKEEPER, the GRAVEDIGGER and the GODCORE - and, with their divine strength combined... they stripped my sister of her power. She was their overseer no longer, and the Archangels had the reins now.</text>
																							<choice hidden="true">
																								<text>Visualize regicide - the death of one tyrant, and the birth of another.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Hey! My sister isn't a tyrant! The Lightborne wanted this, after all - she was just doing what they desired. Even still... the Archangels saw it fit to destroy her, and search for new meaning themselves. Escaping to your reality was everything she could do, just to escape being shattered for a moment - though, she's lucky you were there! What with the Archangels' minions being in hot pursuit, and all...</text>
																									<choice hidden="true">
																										<text>Visualize a minion - a minor cog in a grand machine, thinking itself even grander.</text>
																										<event>
																											<text>Well, as it turns out... whatever effect this newfound resplendence had on the Archangels, it also applies to other, lesser Lightborne. My sister refers to those who succumb to its intoxicating allure as the False Radiance - named after the almost infectious nature of their otherworldly, ethereal glow. Though some Lightborne resist it, and stick to their senseless vows... most seem liable to want to break the mold, and join the Archangels on their quest for 'true' divinity.</text>
																											<choice hidden="true">
																												<text>Visualize a plan - that which is followed closely, and yet quickly abandoned when most convenient.</text>
																												<event>
																													<text>The Archangels, well... they're up to something, for sure. I don't know what, and my sister's hardly even cognizant right now, but... I think it has something to do with me. Wherever it is that I am... I wasn't here earlier, before this all went down. I can't remember much, but... I feel certain of that, at least.
																													
																													With my sister out of commission, the Archangels plotting, and me sitting here, lost in the dark... I don't think there's anyone we can to turn to, other than you. Father seems wary to intervene, himself, and... I don't know why, seeing that this entire thing threatens to compromise that "prophecy" he loves so much, but... it means that we're on our own here, regardless.</text>
																													<choice hidden="true">
																														<text>Visualize a hero - venturing blindly into the dark, in the name of all that is good.</text>
																														<event>
																															<text>Oh, well... how, um... inspiring? I certainly appreciate it, it's just... this isn't going to be easy, you know? Not that my sister has any means of getting you back, as drained as she is... I guess you hardly have much of a choice. Well, if we're going to do this, then I'm going to at least make sure that you're prepared for the road ahead! Though most Lightborne have defected, there are still those who are loyal to their vows. I can lead one to you, through my sister's vessel, but... I can't promise being able to do so more than once - we've already both been stretched thin, as-is.</text>
																															<choice>
																																<text>Visualize truth - that which was sworn away first.</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																																	<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_BURSTMISSILE"/>
																																	<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																															<choice>
																																<text>Visualize the calendar - that which was sworn away second.</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																																	<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_CHAINLASER"/>
																																	<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																															<choice>
																																<text>Visualize words - that which was sworn away third.</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																																	<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_PIERCELASER"/>
																																	<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																															<choice>
																																<text>Visualize values - that which was sworn away fourth.</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																																	<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_CHAINFOCUS"/>
																																	<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																															<choice>
																																<text>Visualize rules - that which was sworn away fifth.</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																																	<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_BREACHBEAM"/>
																																	<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																															<choice>
																																<text>Visualize meaning - that which was sworn away sixth.</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																																	<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_HEAVYION"/>
																																	<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																															<choice>
																																<text>Visualize dignity - that which was sworn away seventh.</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																																	<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_HEAVYSHOTGUN"/>
																																	<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																														</event>
																													</choice>
																												</event>
																											</choice>
																										</event>
																									</choice>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_start" global="false">
		<color r="46" g="252" b="51" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>Abruptly, your ship is ejected out of the other side of the wormhole - but it doesn't lose its momentum entirely. Your ship continues to soar, and, as it does so... everything begins to get blurry.</text>
	<metaVariable name="juke_ddedgeofeeverything" op="set" val="1"/>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
	<playSound>lightspeed</playSound>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Tighten your grip, and shake your head.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You begin to tighten your grip around... the Shade, you realize. It must've been the closest thing nearby, when you rushed to find something to hold onto. Your hand feels as if it's numbing, holding onto its strange, metallic surface...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Rip your hand away from the Shade.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Even as you tear it away, you feel as your hand only continues to numb further. Indeed, everything's getting so... foggy. Your sense of sight, touch, smell - even your ability to think is dimming. With a hopeless lurch, you find yourself clumsily stumbling to the ground.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>What's... happening...?</text>
						<event>
							<text>The last thing you see before your every sense fades, is the Shade - standing over you, as still as it ever is. Then, everything gets... dark... and...</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>...</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>...</text>
										<event>
											<text>...</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>...</text>
												<event>
													<text>...hello? Can you hear me?</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>...</text>
														<event>
															<text>I... can't see you, or, um... hear you, but... I can feel you! You're there, aren't you?</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>...</text>
																<event>
																	<text>If you can hear me, well... try to picture shapes. Objects, physicality - they're all the Lightborne have left here, I think...</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>Visualize a screaming, suffering and tormented soul - that which encompasses everything lost.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>Oh, my - alright! Well, at least you can hear me, but... I need you to relax a bit. I'm... scared, myself. I don't know where I am, and... I... I don't suppose you know any better, do you?</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Visualize a murky lake - its contents a mystery to both itself, and any onlookers.</text>
																				<event load="START_DDANTUMBRA_LOREDROP"/>
																			</choice>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Visualize a crystal-clear lake - its contents completely visible, and already seen.</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>Oh, well... isn't that a relief! You probably know more than I do, then, but... I'll try my best to help out, anyways! We'll, um... make a great team!</text>
																					<choice hidden="true">
																						<text>Visualize a team - together, until the end of everything.</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>Well, if we're going to do this, then I'm going to at least make sure that you're prepared for the road ahead! Though most Lightborne have defected, there are still those who are loyal to their vows. I can lead one to you, through my sister's vessel, but... I can't promise being able to do so more than once - we've already both been stretched thin, as-is.</text>
																							<choice>
																								<text>Visualize truth - that which was sworn away first.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_BURSTMISSILE"/>
																									<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																							<choice>
																								<text>Visualize the calendar - that which was sworn away second.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_CHAINLASER"/>
																									<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																							<choice>
																								<text>Visualize words - that which was sworn away third.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_PIERCELASER"/>
																									<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																							<choice>
																								<text>Visualize values - that which was sworn away fourth.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_CHAINFOCUS"/>
																									<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																							<choice>
																								<text>Visualize rules - that which was sworn away fifth.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_BREACHBEAM"/>
																									<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																							<choice>
																								<text>Visualize meaning - that which was sworn away sixth.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_HEAVYION"/>
																									<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																							<choice>
																								<text>Visualize dignity - that which was sworn away seventh.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Alright, that should do it! I'd make sure to sort your equipment out, before we get on our way. The False Radiance's followers - nevermind the Archangels themselves - await, and their arsenals are, um... deadly, to say the least. Best to be prepared, right?</text>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_HEAVYSHOTGUN"/>
																									<jumpEvent>START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGATEKEEPER</jumpEvent>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="STORE_DDANTUMBRA">
	<event load="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_COLORTALK"/>
	<event load="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_DARKNESSTALK"/>
	<event load="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SISTERTALK"/>
</eventList>

<event name="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_COLORTALK" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_ddantumbra_lightborne" global="false">
		<color r="214" g="214" b="214" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...oh, there's... a collective of Lightborne here? These ones still seem to be tied to their vows, too. Should be easy enough to get them to move on over, and provide some assistance... but, um... would you mind if we talked a bit, while you have a moment? If you, you know! Want to! Or, ah...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ear - always waiting to listen, until the day comes that it can't.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Well, it's just... I... the colors, of your cluster... do you think I could see them one day? When this is all over, I mean! Assuming Father wouldn't mind, and, um... you know. I just - I can see them, through sister's memories, and... they're so... breathtaking. Or, at least, um... they would be, if I, ah, had breath to take! Haha...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a nervous wreck - stammering, stuttering, staggering.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Sorry! I am, um... nervous, admittedly... Father just doesn't approve of us doing as we please. I can't imagine he'll take too kindly to my sister's attempt at seeing Mother, for example... but, if you asked him! Or, maybe even... stood by my side...? I, um... I feel like he'd HAVE to agree, right?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a rainbow - better shared than kept to oneself.</text>
								<event>
									<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_LIGHTBORNE</store>
									<text>R-really? I'm... I'm looking forward to it, then. In the meantime, though, um... shopping, right?! And, you know... the Archangels, and, ah...</text>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
										<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize hesitation - stammering, stuttering, staggering.</text>
								<event>
									<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_LIGHTBORNE</store>
									<text>H-hey! I'm just... YOU try being locked up in a dark, endless room, communicating with someone - who's HALF-AWAKE mind you - through your sister's lifeless, debilitated body! I'm trying my best here! It was... a dumb question, anyways. I'll leave you to your, um... shopping, and stuff...</text>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
										<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ant - forever busy, with no time for small talk.</text>
				<event>
					<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_LIGHTBORNE</store>
					<text>O-oh, um... of course! Forever busy, haha... well, I'll just... leave you to it, then!</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_DARKNESSTALK" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_ddantumbra_shadows" global="false">
		<color r="92" g="92" b="92" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...the Shadows have been waiting for you, it would seem? Or my, um... sister. Hard to tell. Guess they're aware of your cause, either way. Though, I do have to wonder... ah, nevermind! Shopping with weird, inky tentacles - yay!</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a detective - curious, and eager to find out more.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, you want to - alright! Well, I was just, um... thinking about the Shadows, I guess. They always seem to play a sort of, like... bystander role in the Lightborne's affairs. The two used to war, sure, but why? And, whereas the Lightborne swore everything away to stop the fighting... the Shadows didn't, and, you know... seem pretty fine stopping anyways. Isn't that a little weird?</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a question - worthy of asking one's sibling.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Well, the thing is... she doesn't know, either. GODCORE was created in case the Shadows ever threatened violence against the Lightborne, but... my sister's never needed to use it. Not only that, but... what even are they? Some kind of hive mind? I know they're relatively friendly here, and it's bad to bite the hand that feeds you, but, ah... the whole thing kinda weirds me out a bit.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize agreement - a curt nod of one's head.</text>
								<event>
									<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SHADOWS</store>
									<text>I guess it doesn't matter too much, ultimately, but... maybe my sister can tell me all about it when this is over, when she's had some more time with them, right? And, then, um... I could tell you all about it, too!</text>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
										<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize disagreement - a stern shake of one's head.</text>
								<event>
									<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SHADOWS</store>
									<text>Really? Maybe I just think too much, I guess. Either way, um... well, it's time to shop, right?</text>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
										<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a shopper - blind to all but the task in front of them.</text>
				<event>
					<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SHADOWS</store>
					<text>Yeah! Shopping! I've, ah... never been shopping, but, um... you make it look fun enough, I think? Though, maybe I should... you know, take it a bit more seriously. What with the whole, um... fighting for your life thing? Whatever! Go enjoy it!</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SISTERTALK_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDFALSE_RADIANCE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>That's what these JERKS get! We should, um... check on the other Lightborne, right?</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Visualize a helping hand - one that lifts up the fallen.</text>
			<event load="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SISTERTALK_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<event name="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SISTERTALK_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>They're about as out of it as you are, but... at least they're otherwise alright. My sister's vessel should be able to rouse them up enough to help out. Speaking of my, um... sister...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize an open book - eager to be read.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I was just wondering, um... what do you think about her?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a corpse - battered, beaten, bloodied.</text>
				<event>
					<text>R-right! I, ah... right... I guess you've never really had the chance to talk to her... W-well, you'll get that chance soon enough! And it'll be great! And, and... I'll, um.. be there, I guess, haha...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a mirror - one reflective of questions, in particular.</text>
						<event>
							<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_LIGHTBORNE</store>
							<text>Me? What do I think about her? Well, she's... she's amazing. Courageous, loving, powerful - she's always been Father's favorite. I'm a bit too, um... timid, I think... so Father keeps me close. And, as far as our other sister is concerned, ah... I think she scares him a bit. She certainly scares me! She's... a bit different from the two of us. More, um... bestial? She doesn't really care for us, too much, but... she's still family!
							
							Either way, though... Father's sent her out on a mission with her own vessel, last I heard. I'm, ah... the only one of us without a vessel. B-but, that's okay! I'm sure Father will get me one, eventually... in the meantime, though - shopping, right?! With the Lightborne! The, um... goooood ol' Lightborne...</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a bee - busy, buzzy, bustling.</text>
		<event>
			<store>STORE_DDANTUMBRA_LIGHTBORNE</store>
			<text>Oh, um... right, I shouldn't distract you. Shopping! Y-yay! Have... fun? As much fun as you can have, anyways, in your, ah... current predicament...</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SISTERTALK" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_ddantumbra_lightborne" global="false">
		<color r="214" g="214" b="214" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...the False Radiance is here? And they're bullying the other Lightborne... we need to step in and save them, right?! Or, um... you need to. You and my, ah... sister! As wrecked as she is...</text>
			<ship load="STORE_DDANTUMBRA_SISTERTALK_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a helping hand - offered in the form of a balled fist.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Y-yeah! Beat 'em up! I'll, um... be cheering you on - from over here! Wherever, ah... 'here' actually is.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a passerby - merely travelling, never looking for a fight.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Are you sure? I thought we were - or, um... you were... well, alright. I guess you have bigger fish to fry, don't you? Still, though... I hope these Lightborne end up being okay.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_WORMHOLE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SHADOWS"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE"/>
</eventList>

<ship name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_WORMHOLE_SUMMONLIST_CHOSEN_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDCHOSEN">
	<destroyed>
		<text>N-nice one! It's a shame that, ah... we couldn't just reason with them, but... well, you did what you had to. Besides! They didn't really strike me as being, um... reasonable types, in the first place.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Visualize exploration - that of this homely, yet still otherworldly wreckage.</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_WORMHOLE_SUMMONLIST_CHOSEN_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>N-nice one! It's a shame that, ah... we couldn't just reason with them, but... well, you did what you had to. Besides! They didn't really strike me as being, um... reasonable types, in the first place.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Visualize exploration - that of this homely, yet still otherworldly wreckage.</text>
			<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_WORMHOLE_SUMMONLIST_CHOSEN_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_WORMHOLE_SUMMONLIST_CHOSEN_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>Oh, there IS something left... what is that? Some strange weapon, back from your reality?
	
	Wait, but... aren't these Shadows inside of it? Does that mean, that... oh, Father! He WAS always asking my sister to transport Shadows for him, via GENESIS... I guess he, just, um... hands them out to his followers? I don't see why, but... who am I to judge him? I'm sure he has his reasons! Haha...</text>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_WEAPONS"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_WORMHOLE" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...what, um... is that? There's some kind of... gray button, here in space. What's it doing here?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a poke - one so very, very fervent.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Wait, be careful! Who knows what'll happen, if you-</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize fervor - fervor, fervor, FERVOR!</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, my - a wormhole?! I told you to be careful! Looks like you've got some company, back from your reality... and they don't seem to be handling the whole, uh, 'forced senselessness' thing very well. They seem pretty confused, even... ah, regardless, they're coming your way! Get ready!</text>
							<ship load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_WORMHOLE_SUMMONLIST_CHOSEN_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize avoidance - that of inexplicable space buttons.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Honestly, yeah... it kind of weirds me out too. Let's just, um...? Leave it to whatever it is that weird buttons do in space? Yeah, that sounds normal!</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SHADOWS" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...oh, the Shadows are here! Though, um... normally they'd be a bit more excited to see my sister. These ones seem to be... anxious? Afraid? They must've been attacked by the False Radiance, recently... assuming that they're still recovering, maybe there's something you can do to help them?</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_WEAPONS">
				<text>Visualize an offering - the kinship found in offering a Shadow weapon.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A weapon? Do you think that'll help? Well... which one, then?</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="SHOTGUN_DARKGOD">
						<text>Visualize a Flak weapon - a shroud of many things.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="SHOTGUN_DARKGOD"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over there from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_HEAVYSHOTGUN"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LASER_DARKGOD">
						<text>Visualize a Light Laser weapon - the bane of its namesake.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="LASER_DARKGOD"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_PIERCELASER"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="BOMB_DARKGOD">
						<text>Visualize a Bomb weapon - one whose torment is inescapable.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="BOMB_DARKGOD"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_BURSTMISSILE"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="DD_BEAM_INSTANT_DARKGOD">
						<text>Visualize a Pre-emptive Beam weapon - a silence set to befall all.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="DD_BEAM_INSTANT_DARKGOD"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_CHAINFOCUS"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="DDLASER_CHARGE_DARKGOD">
						<text>Visualize a Charge Laser weapon - tomorrow's dusk, fated to descend.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="DDLASER_CHARGE_DARKGOD"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_CHAINLASER"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDDARKGOD_DRONES">
				<text>Visualize an offering - the kinship found in offering a Shadow drone.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A drone? Do you think that'll help? Well... which one, then?</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="DRONE_MINISHROUD">
						<text>Visualize a Combat drone - a slow, yet steady, onslaught.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="DRONE_MINISHROUD"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERTHREE_DEVOURLUX"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MORPH_DISPARITYBROODMOTHER">
						<text>Visualize an Anti-Personnel drone - lone, until proven otherwise.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="LIST_CREW_MORPH_DISPARITYBROODMOTHER"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERTHREE_COMMANDLUX"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MORPH_DDDISPARITYADMINISTRATOR">
						<text>Visualize a Utility drone - a beacon for those who need it.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, they're... eating it? Or, um... maybe they're just... absorbing it? I'm not really sure. My sister never really had a lot of chances to get to know the Shadows, despite working to keep them and the Lightborne safe. They, ah... mostly keep to themselves. But, hey! Maybe we can learn something here, and tell her all about it when this is over! Let's, um... let's just let them do their thing, I guess?</text>
							<remove name="LIST_CREW_MORPH_DDDISPARITYADMINISTRATOR"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize patience - one virtue, of many, to be exercised when deemed necessary.</text>
								<event>
									<text>...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - patience's somber bedfellow.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, I guess while they're, um... chewing on that weapon, we could maybe, ah, talk a bit? I... wanted to ask you something - about the Shadows, funnily enough. They're in your reality too, right? It's fuzzy, but I feel like I can recall as much through what my sister saw when she met you. What I wanted to ask, was, um... what are they like there?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize darkness - vast, ravenous and more than deep enough to drown in.</text>
												<event>
													<text>R-really? The Shadows here are so timid, though... seeing how distant your reality is, I guess it's safe to assume that Father brought them over from here. But, what would cause that change in their behavior? And, ah... what's the point in him bring them there anyways, anyways? Especially if they're content here, and angry otherwise... m-maybe we can ask him later? Together, of course...! It's, um... less scary, that way.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize a companion - welcome company when in unwelcoming territory.</text>
														<event>
															<text>A companion? Do you... think that I'm, ah... oh, um, look! The Shadows are done! And it looks like they have something for you?
															
															Is that... a Lightborne? One not under the False Radiance's influence, at that... I wonder if the Shadows were protecting it, and that's why the False Radiance attacked them. I guess they're entrusting it to you, now? Aren't you popular! With the, ah, Shadows, of course...</text>
															<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERTHREE_TIMELUX"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize little - for that's all you have to offer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>They ARE kind of weird, and, ah... amorphous? I guess that I don't really know how to help them, either... though, um... are they getting ready to strike? They... they must think that you're here to finish what the False Radiance started! Quickly - look out!</text>
					<boarders min="5" max="7" class="darkgodtendrils"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDFALSE_RADIANCE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>That's that, then. Not much to do, other than keep moving, r-right?</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_GAMBLE">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_GAMBLE_NOAPPRECIATION"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_GAMBLE_NOAPPRECIATION"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_GAMBLE_YIPPEE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_GAMBLE_NOAPPRECIATION">
	<text>Wait, is it working...? Are the False Radiance really capable of...
	
	...oh, nope. They're definitely, ah... not very appreciative of your kindness. If it's any consolation, I think it's, um... it's really honorable that you tried? They wouldn't do the same for you, obviously, but... still! I think there's at least value in the attempt, isn't there?</text>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<enemyDamage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<enemyDamage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<enemyDamage amount="1" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_GAMBLE_YIPPEE">
	<text>Oh, wow. They're even more damaged than I thought... the Lightborne that makes up their ship is dying, and I don't know if there's really anything that you can do for them. Though, ah... maybe there's something you can do for the lesser Lightborne aboard? That one, there - they might be amicable towards joining you, if it, um... means that they'll live.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a light - that which is more than welcome in this dark place.</text>
		<event>
			<text>They're welcome aboard, then - hopefully they don't cause too much trouble! I admit, though, I, ah... I guess I was wrong about them being TOTAL monsters. Not that they're doing much, other than preserving their own life, but... I really didn't think the False Radiance capable of any form of reason. It feels a bit weird to think that our enemies might not be so different from us, even if they aren't all this agreeable...</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DDFALSERADIANCE_WEAPONS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...the False Radiance is here, but... they're not looking so hot. No, ah, pun intended! It's just that they, um... they seem hurt. Even if they wanted to be aggressive towards you, I'm not sure that they could manage it.</text>
			<ship load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a hand - one offered in assistance.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Y-you... you want to help your enemies? That's really noble, but... I don't think that the members of the False Radiance are all that big on redemption. They don't really seem to care for much, other than their belief in the strength of divinity. I obviously can't, ah... stop you from trying, but... it's hopeless, isn't it?</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize insistence - a hope that burns, even in times of hopelessness.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Well, if you're sure! Just, um... don't say I didn't warn you, alright?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize an approach - cautious, but assuring.</text>
								<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_HURTLIGHT_GAMBLE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize reluctance - inaction, born from hesitation.</text>
						<event>
							<text>I'm sure things are safer this way. Just, ah... keep your distance from these jerks, alright? Don't let them try anything!</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize destruction - a lack of mercy for the wicked.</text>
				<event>
					<text>No shame in hitting them when they're down - they'd do the same to you, wouldn't they? Don't, ah... don't let your guard down, though. Even if they're vulnerable, the False Radiance is still dangerous!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<enemyDamage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
					<enemyDamage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
					<enemyDamage amount="1" system="random" effect="breach"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a gap - a safe distance between two rival parties.</text>
				<event>
					<text>No use in letting them try anything, I guess. Maybe just, um, keep an eye on them? I-if you could, anyways... okay, I'LL keep a metaphorical eye on them, you, ah... you do whatever it is that you need to!</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_DANGER_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDFALSE_RADIANCE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>Wow, n-nice one! You've done it again! Though, ah... it looks like the other Lightborne that were congregated here left during the skirmish. It's a shame, but... you should, um, still be proud of yourself, you know? The False Radiance isn't just ANY measly threat!</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHTHEFURTHEST">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHTHEFURTHEST_SAFE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_DANGER"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHTHEFURTHEST_SAFE">
	<text>W-wow, I... I love your confidence! It looks like it paid off, too? The largest of the Lightborne present here is headed this way, and the False Radiance seems to be none the wiser!</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize victory - the succulent spoils of one's good fortune.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Now, let's see what my sister's dragged in...
	
			...a Radiant weapon! My sister knows a fair bit about the Lightborne, having worked closely with them as their overseer... while most Lightborne function to grow into Radiant Cores, and reproduce from there, some of the larger ones may manage to become Radiant weapons - particularly powerful Lightborne capable of altering space and making it habitable for their lesser kin. Despite their power, they're reliant on even greater Lightborne, still - the, ah, mighty, massive few who serve to house and empower both Radiant Cores and weapons alike. It's a s-strange system, but, um... I think it's kind of endearing, how all of their roles are necessary. They're like a big, uncaring machine!</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DDFALSERADIANCE_WEAPONS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_DANGER">
	<text>Wait, is that... oh, Father - the False Radiance is here! They must've caught onto my sister's signal, after all... i-it's alright, though! I, ah... I know that you can handle them!</text>
	<ship load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_DANGER_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHEVENFURTHER">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHEVENFURTHER_SAFE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHEVENFURTHER_SAFE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_DANGER"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHEVENFURTHER_SAFE">
	<text>So far, so good... my sister's signal has almost reached the center of this Lightborne swarm! You should, ah... probably call it off now, before the False Radiance catches wind of the signal themselves.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize the jackpot - just out of reach, yet worth reaching out for.</text>
		<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHTHEFURTHEST"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize cashing out - a good gambler knows when to call it quits.</text>
		<event>
			<text>That's the spirit! Hardly any use in pushing your luck any further than you already have. Now, let's see what my sister's dragged in...
	
			...a Radiant Core! My sister knows a fair bit about the Lightborne, having worked closely with them as their overseer - Radiant Cores themselves ARE Lightborne, but they also serve as means of reproducing ADDITIONAL, lesser Lightborne. They need to be fed energy to do so, but, um... once they get going, they REALLY get going. With their senses vowed away, reproduction is all that the Lightborne are really capable of, unless my sister grabs their attention... for the most part, anyways. It seems that the Lightborne under the False Radiance's influence have their own interests in mind, but, ah... we'll stop them, right? I mean, um - y-you'll stop them! I'm just, you know, over... over here! Helping! Or, at least, ah, trying to...? I'll s-stop talking...</text>
			<drone name="LIST_DRONES_DDTIERTHREE_FALSERADIANCE"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_SAFE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_SAFE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_SAFE"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_DANGER"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER_SAFE">
	<text>That did the trick - some of the stronger Lightborne seem to be moving about now. Though, you could keep pushing your luck and find some REALLY powerful Lightborne... s-still, ah... up to you!</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize further risk - the potential is worth the other potential.</text>
		<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHEVENFURTHER"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize cashing out - a good gambler knows when to call it quits.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There's no shame in playing it safe - especially when you've taken a risk already! Now, let's see what my sister's dragged in...
	
			...a Radiant Core! My sister knows a fair bit about the Lightborne, having worked closely with them as their overseer - Radiant Cores themselves ARE Lightborne, but they also serve as means of reproducing ADDITIONAL, lesser Lightborne. They need to be fed energy to do so, but, um... once they get going, they REALLY get going. With their senses vowed away, reproduction is all that the Lightborne are really capable of, unless my sister grabs their attention... for the most part, anyways. It seems that the Lightborne under the False Radiance's influence have their own interests in mind, but, ah... we'll stop them, right? I mean, um - y-you'll stop them! I'm just, you know, over... over here! Helping! Or, at least, ah, trying to...? I'll s-stop talking...</text>
			<drone name="LIST_DRONES_DDTIERTWO_FALSERADIANCE"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_TIERONEACQUIRED">
	<text>There's no shame in playing it safe! Now, let's see what my sister's dragged in...
	
	...a Radiant Core! My sister knows a fair bit about the Lightborne, having worked closely with them as their overseer - Radiant Cores themselves ARE Lightborne, but they also serve as means of reproducing ADDITIONAL, lesser Lightborne. They need to be fed energy to do so, but, um... once they get going, they REALLY get going. With their senses vowed away, reproduction is all that the Lightborne are really capable of, unless my sister grabs their attention... for the most part, anyways. It seems that the Lightborne under the False Radiance's influence have their own interests in mind, but, ah... we'll stop them, right? I mean, um - y-you'll stop them! I'm just, you know, over... over here! Helping! Or, at least, ah, trying to...? I'll s-stop talking...</text>
	<drone name="LIST_DRONES_DDTIERONE_FALSERADIANCE"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...oh my, there are so many Lightborne here! They seem to be untouched by the False Radiance's influence, too... if you'd, um, like to, you could maybe use my sister's presence to rile some of them up? It might attract some unwanted attention, but... it might attract some wanted attention, too!</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an agreement - that of the proposed plan.</text>
				<event>
					<text>There ARE a lot of them, though... with this many Lightborne here, you'd have to push her signal a bit past the little guys to reach the big ones. It's, ah, u-up to you if the risk of doing so sounds worth it. The lesser Lightborne can be powerful in their, um... their own right!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize risk - the kind involved in attracting attention.</text>
						<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize safety - that which is found settling upon the outskirts.</text>
						<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_TIERONEACQUIRED"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize hesitation - a caution borne from the dangers involved.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Well, if you want, you can just have her rouse the attention of some of the lesser Lightborne, here on the edge. There shouldn't be much risk involved in doing so, if, ah... if any! I have a feeling that the stronger Lightborne are deeper within the bunch, requiring a more potentially dangerous strength of signal, but... it's u-up to you, really!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize risk - the kind involved in attracting attention.</text>
						<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_PUSHFURTHER"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize safety - that which is found settling upon the outskirts.</text>
						<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_ANXIOUSBORNE_TIERONEACQUIRED"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST_CINDERPRISM"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST_SPIRITSLAY"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST_BREAKCINDER"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_OMGEVERYONEISHAPPY">
	<text>L-lead the way, then! The Lightborne seem to have already caught onto their kin's presence aboard your ship, so, um... they SHOULD be following closely.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>...</text>
				<event>
					<text>I think that this should, um... be far enough, right? Any further and the False Radiance might begin to catch up, and I can hardly think of anything I'd want less.
					
					It looks like each and every one of the Lightborne followed you all the way here, too... aren't they kind of amazing? With all of this empty space, they're sure to have an easy time reproducing!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a proud stance - a result of a job well done.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Though, ah... what are they doing, exactly? They're kind of just, like - wait... my sister's seen this before! They're transferring some of their energy to your ship, by simply rubbing up against it - just like how they used to do, when she would visit them with the Archangels. They must think that you're one of them, somehow... I can't, ah, say why, but, um... who really knows, given how simpleminded the Lightborne are. Regardless, not only have they effectively repaired your ship, but it looks like they're prepared to keep multiplying and do what they can to slow down the False Radiance. You go, little guys!</text>
							<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
							<damage amount="-44"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_PRISMLING">
	<text>That sure was... something. At least the Prismlings are free to pay attention now, right? Have my sister send the signal again, and...
	
	...that should do it - reinforcements, coming right up! All it took was a little, ah... b-bloodshed.</text>
	<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_PRISMLING"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_CINDERLING">
	<text>That sure was... something. At least the Cinderlings are free to pay attention now, right? Have my sister send the signal again, and...
	
	...that should do it - reinforcements, coming right up! All it took was a little, ah... b-bloodshed.</text>
	<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_CINDERLING"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_SLAYLING">
	<text>That sure was... something. At least the Slaylings are free to pay attention now, right? Have my sister send the signal again, and...
	
	...that should do it - reinforcements, coming right up! All it took was a little, ah... b-bloodshed.</text>
	<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_SLAYLING"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_SPIRITLING">
	<text>That sure was... something. At least the Spiritlings are free to pay attention now, right? Have my sister send the signal again, and...
	
	...that should do it - reinforcements, coming right up! All it took was a little, ah... b-bloodshed.</text>
	<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_SPIRITLING"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_BREAKLING">
	<text>That sure was... something. At least the Breaklings are free to pay attention now, right? Have my sister send the signal again, and...
	
	...that should do it - reinforcements, coming right up! All it took was a little, ah... b-bloodshed.</text>
	<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_BREAKLING"/>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST_CINDERPRISM">
	<text>Well, one side's composed of Cinderlings - the other being, um... Prismlings? Yeah, looks like it. Seeing as your ship is uninhabitable to Lightborne, neither pose much of a threat to you... if you wanted to settle this, all you'd REALLY have to do is lure one side onboard.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_CINDERLING">
		<text>Visualize a Cinderling Radiant Core - something present nearby.</text>
		<event>
			<text>That's... an interesting idea. Instead of luring them onboard, maybe you could use your Radiant Core to lead the Cinderlings away? That way, the Prismlings get to use the space here, and the Cinderlings can have their own space somewhere else! Good, ah... good idea, me! I think...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a place further away - light's destination.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_OMGEVERYONEISHAPPY"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_PRISMLING">
		<text>Visualize a Prismling Radiant Core - something present nearby.</text>
		<event>
			<text>That's... an interesting idea. Instead of luring them onboard, maybe you could use your Radiant Core to lead the Prismlings away? That way, the Cinderlings get to use the space here, and the Prismlings can have their own space somewhere else! Good, ah... good idea, me! I think...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a place further away - light's destination.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_OMGEVERYONEISHAPPY"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a flame - a Cinderling, hopelessly trapped aboard one's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I'm not sure how ethical this is, but... right now, my sister needs help, and there's no time for the Lightborne still under her control to be bickering! All it should really take to lure them in is a quick, ah... ramming?</text>
			<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_PRISMLING" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
				<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a ram - bolsterous, blazing, BLEATING!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, wow, uh - yeah, here they come!</text>
					<boarders min="7" max="13" class="ddlightborne_cinderling"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a rainbow - a Prismling, hopelessly trapped aboard one's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I'm not sure how ethical this is, but... right now, my sister needs help, and there's no time for the Lightborne still under her control to be bickering! All it should really take to lure them in is a quick, ah... ramming?</text>
			<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_CINDERLING" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
				<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a ram - bolsterous, blazing, BLEATING!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, wow, uh - yeah, here they come!</text>
					<boarders min="7" max="13" class="ddlightborne_prismling"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize an exit - a way out of this interaction.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Oh, that's, ah... that's fair! The Lightborne will figure out their own weirdness eventually, right? You just need to, you know... keep cruising! Cruising, and, um, grooving...?</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST_SPIRITSLAY">
	<text>Well, one side's composed of Slaylings - the other being, um... Spiritlings? Yeah, looks like it. Seeing as your ship is uninhabitable to Lightborne, neither pose much of a threat to you... if you wanted to settle this, all you'd REALLY have to do is lure one side onboard.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_SLAYLING">
		<text>Visualize a Slayling Radiant Core - something present nearby.</text>
		<event>
			<text>That's... an interesting idea. Instead of luring them onboard, maybe you could use your Radiant Core to lead the Slaylings away? That way, the Spiritlings get to use the space here, and the Slaylings can have their own space somewhere else! Good, ah... good idea, me! I think...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a place further away - light's destination.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_OMGEVERYONEISHAPPY"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_SPIRITLING">
		<text>Visualize a Spiritling Radiant Core - something present nearby.</text>
		<event>
			<text>That's... an interesting idea. Instead of luring them onboard, maybe you could use your Radiant Core to lead the Spiritlings away? That way, the Slaylings get to use the space here, and the Spiritlings can have their own space somewhere else! Good, ah... good idea, me! I think...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a place further away - light's destination.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_OMGEVERYONEISHAPPY"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a warrior - a Slayling, hopelessly trapped aboard one's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I'm not sure how ethical this is, but... right now, my sister needs help, and there's no time for the Lightborne still under her control to be bickering! All it should really take to lure them in is a quick, ah... ramming?</text>
			<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_SPIRITLING" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
				<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a ram - bolsterous, blazing, BLEATING!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, wow, uh - yeah, here they come!</text>
					<boarders min="7" max="13" class="ddlightborne_slayling"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a ghost - a Spiritling, hopelessly trapped aboard one's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I'm not sure how ethical this is, but... right now, my sister needs help, and there's no time for the Lightborne still under her control to be bickering! All it should really take to lure them in is a quick, ah... ramming?</text>
			<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_SLAYLING" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
				<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a ram - bolsterous, blazing, BLEATING!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, wow, uh - yeah, here they come!</text>
					<boarders min="7" max="13" class="ddlightborne_spiritling"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize an exit - a way out of this interaction.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Oh, that's, ah... that's fair! The Lightborne will figure out their own weirdness eventually, right? You just need to, you know... keep cruising! Cruising, and, um, grooving...?</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST_BREAKCINDER">
	<text>Well, one side's composed of Breaklings - the other being, um... Cinderlings? Yeah, looks like it. Seeing as your ship is uninhabitable to Lightborne, neither pose much of a threat to you... if you wanted to settle this, all you'd REALLY have to do is lure one side onboard.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_BREAKLING">
		<text>Visualize a Breakling Radiant Core - something present nearby.</text>
		<event>
			<text>That's... an interesting idea. Instead of luring them onboard, maybe you could use your Radiant Core to lead the Breaklings away? That way, the Cinderlings get to use the space here, and the Breaklings can have their own space somewhere else! Good, ah... good idea, me! I think...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a place further away - light's destination.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_OMGEVERYONEISHAPPY"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERONE_CINDERLING">
		<text>Visualize a Cinderling Radiant Core - something present nearby.</text>
		<event>
			<text>That's... an interesting idea. Instead of luring them onboard, maybe you could use your Radiant Core to lead the Cinderlings away? That way, the Breaklings get to use the space here, and the Cinderlings can have their own space somewhere else! Good, ah... good idea, me! I think...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a place further away - light's destination.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_OMGEVERYONEISHAPPY"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a hammer - a Breakling, hopelessly trapped aboard one's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I'm not sure how ethical this is, but... right now, my sister needs help, and there's no time for the Lightborne still under her control to be bickering! All it should really take to lure them in is a quick, ah... ramming?</text>
			<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_CINDERLING" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
				<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a ram - bolsterous, blazing, BLEATING!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, wow, uh - yeah, here they come!</text>
					<boarders min="7" max="13" class="ddlightborne_breakling"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a flame - a Cinderling, hopelessly trapped aboard one's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I'm not sure how ethical this is, but... right now, my sister needs help, and there's no time for the Lightborne still under her control to be bickering! All it should really take to lure them in is a quick, ah... ramming?</text>
			<triggeredEvent event="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_THEENDOFTHEFIGHT_BREAKLING" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
				<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a ram - bolsterous, blazing, BLEATING!</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, wow, uh - yeah, here they come!</text>
					<boarders min="7" max="13" class="ddlightborne_cinderling"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize an exit - a way out of this interaction.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Oh, that's, ah... that's fair! The Lightborne will figure out their own weirdness eventually, right? You just need to, you know... keep cruising! Cruising, and, um, grooving...?</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...this place sure seems packed, huh? It looks like you've stumbled upon a breeding ground for lesser Lightborne... one that's been left untouched by the False Radiance, too! Shouldn't be too much of a hassle to just, ya know... have my sister wake them up a bit, and see if they can't, um, help you, somehow?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a morning - when man and light alike return in tandem.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, are they not...? It, ah... i-it doesn't look like they're listening to her signal at all. That's rare, but... it's not unheard of, either. Sometimes, Lightborne get into blind, territorial disputes - two different kinds of Lightborne will bump heads against each other until one side inevitably comes out on top, and wins the space. At this point, with life's greater pleasures vowed away, all the Lightborne REALLY care about is multiplying... so it's not too surprising for my sister to, um... find them like this.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a dispute - perhaps one to be settled.</text>
						<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_INFIGHTING_LIST"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a lack of interest - that which pertains to the politics of beasts.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You can just leave them to their weirdness, yeah... it's kind of rude of them to be ignoring my sister, anyways, isn't it? She's trying to protect them! Or at least she, ah... she would be, if she...
							
							...I'm really hoping that this all works out. That my sister's okay, and we can... we can just all go back to how things were, before the False Radiance, and before that... mirror... but, ah! I, um... I didn't mean to bring the mood down! Hey, just, you know, um - let me know if you need anything, okay?!</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDFALSE_RADIANCE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>It looks like the explosives, together with the fleet, um... floated away, while you were fighting. Not necessarily surprising, given that they were busy being up to something, but... well, at least you've disrupted the False Radiance's plans somewhat! A victory is a victory, isn't it?</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<clearCustomFleet/>
		<removeHazards/>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_MADDASH_LIST">
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_MADDASH_LIST_CAUGHT"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_MADDASH_LIST_CAUGHT"/>
	<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_UNDERWAY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_MADDASH_LIST_CAUGHT">
	<text>Wait, be-
	
	...careful. T-they definitely, ah... they definitely see you! You need to defend yourself, before they can get any more attacks off!</text>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="PDS" target="player"/>
	<noASBPlanet/>
	<boarders min="3" max="5" class="ddlightborne_prismling"/>
	<damage amount="1" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<damage amount="1" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<damage amount="2" system="random" effect="fire"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_UNDERWAY">
	<text>Wow, nice one - that actually worked! You're at their explosive pile... a massive mound of volatile Warlockulars, ready to go off at a moment's notice. They're corrupted by the False Radiance already, so I wouldn't, um... worry too much about rigging them to explode. It's kind of sad, but... at least they can still be useful, right?</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Visualize an impromptu explosive - rigged, and prepared to set off a chain reaction.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Now, you just need to get out of there, quickly! Before the False Radiance, ah... n-notices! Or, you know... before the Warlockulars go off?!</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-3" max="-3"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize distance - that which is now desperately needed.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Any second now, it should - oh! Yeah, take that, you, um... you evil jerks! That's for my sister, and her vessel! Not that she, ah... can't avenge herself later, but, um... still!</text>
					<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
					<clearCustomFleet/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize comeuppance - a gift of pain reflected a thousandfold.</text>
						<event>
							<text>With the False Radiance taken care of, their loot is yours for the taking! Plus, you've dealt a blow to their schemes by destroying their fleet and explosives cache... good job, you!</text>
							<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
							<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize satisfaction - the true reward of a job well done.</text>
								<event>
									<text>I can't help but wonder what their schemes WERE exactly, though... that was enough Warlockulars to blow an Archangel to hell. N-not that they would ever do that, but... I just find it a little concerning, you know? My sister's never seen the Lightborne coordinate something like this on their own. Though, as long as you, um... just stay vigilant, I'm sure everything will work out! I hope so, at least...</text>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a problem - a lack of routes forward.</text>
		<event>
			<text>...Oh. That's, um... a problem, indeed, isn't it? I guess you could just, fire at the cache yourself, but... that sounds dangerous, doesn't it?</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="weapons" lvl="1" blue="false">
				<text>Visualize danger - that which is necessary in times like these.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Okay, just, ah... at least get a BIT of distance, alright? Your ship's gonna be scuffed up a bit, but it should be relatively minor. This f-feels a bit crazy, though...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a blast - incoming, imminent, inescapable.</text>
						<event>
							<text>This is actually happening... alright, I'm calm, I'm, I'm...
							
							...wait, it... it's alright?! I-it... it actually worked out! Yeah, take that, you, um... you evil jerks! That's for my sister, and her vessel! Not that she, ah... can't avenge herself later, but, um... still!</text>
							<damage amount="1" system="random" effect="breach"/>
							<damage amount="1" system="random" effect="breach"/>
							<damage amount="2" system="random" effect="fire"/>
							<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
							<clearCustomFleet/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize comeuppance - a gift of pain reflected a thousandfold.</text>
								<event>
									<text>With the False Radiance taken care of, their loot is yours for the taking! Plus, you've dealt a blow to their schemes by destroying their fleet and explosives cache... good job, you!</text>
									<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
									<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize satisfaction - the true reward of a job well done.</text>
										<event>
											<text>I can't help but wonder what their schemes WERE exactly, though... that was enough Warlockulars to blow an Archangel to hell. N-not that they would ever do that, but... I just find it a little concerning, you know? My sister's never seen the Lightborne coordinate something like this on their own. Though, as long as you, um... just stay vigilant, I'm sure everything will work out! I hope so, at least...</text>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="weapons" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
				<text>Visualize a problem - this time, from a lack of a Weapon Control system.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Are you serious?! You don't have a... well, I guess that's impressive, more than anything. There's not really anything to do, though, if you can't ignite the cache... wait, look out! W-we must've taken too long - the False Radiance has spotted you!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<environment type="PDS" target="player"/>
					<noASBPlanet/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a question - that of the worth of this plan.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Yeah, I kind of agree... what to do, then... hmm... wait, look out! W-we must've taken too long - the False Radiance has spotted you!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<environment type="PDS" target="player"/>
					<noASBPlanet/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_REAL">
	<text>...that's... a LOT of explosives - which is to say nothing of the presence of an entire fleet! It looks like the False Radiance are preparing for some sort of attack here, but, um... they also haven't noticed the arrival of your ship yet, I think? If that's the case, it might be a good idea to sneak up on them and sabotage their plans somehow. Before they do something, ah... you know, bad?</text>
	<ship load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<customFleet right="true" firing="true" autoDarkening="true">CUSTOM_FLEET_DDFALSERADIANCE</customFleet>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DRONES_DDFALSERADIANCE">
		<text>Visualize a distraction - one utilizing the allure of a Radiant Core. [1|]</text>
		<event>
			<text>Oh, that's clever! If you leave your Radiant Core here, and have my sister send out a signal, then the False Radiance should come on over and investigate. Then, while they're distracted wanting to convert it to their cause, YOU'RE sneaking your way up to their demolitions supply, and... kaboom! Sounds like a good plan to me - just, um... b-be careful, alright? Your Radiant Core should be fine, as long as you don't take too long - plus, it'll be close enough to get back to you! You know, just in case you're, ah... caught somehow...</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-1" max="-1"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a plan - that which will be executed flawlessly.</text>
				<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_UNDERWAY"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking" lvl="2">
		<text>Visualize a cloak - advanced, even amongst the edge of everything.</text>
		<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_UNDERWAY"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="engines" lvl="5">
		<text>Visualize an engine - strong enough to move one swiftly, and quietly.</text>
		<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_UNDERWAY"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a mad dash - risky, but potentially worth it.</text>
		<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_MADDASH_LIST"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a confrontation - one has no need to skulk in the dark.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Oh, um... well, if you're sure! I can respect the lack of hesitation - recklessness is admirable! I, a-ah... I think it is, anyways...?</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<environment type="PDS" target="player"/>
			<noASBPlanet/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize a shrug - a symbol of those who hardly care.</text>
		<event>
			<text>W-wait, but... if you don't do something, then the False Radiance is only going to get stronger...
			
			...well, I, um... I guess it's alright, if you're sure? Maybe there's better places to be right now, and I'm just not, ah... seeing the bigger picture! Yeah!</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event load="NEUTRAL_DDANTUMBRA_SUBTERFUGE_REAL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_SYSTEMINSTALL"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_RESOURCES"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_MISSILELOVE"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_THEDEVOURER"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_SYSTEMINSTALL" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...you know, I've been thinking - there's plenty of Radiant Cores around the Antumbral Plane, but... are you even able to use them? They need to be fed energy to function, which I think translates to the effective equivalent of a, um... Drone Control system, was it?</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="drones" lvl="1">
				<text>Visualize a drone - that which one has the means to wield.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Oh, so you CAN use them! That's nice, at least. Well, ah... if you wanted, it wouldn't be too tough to have my sister send the signal and have some Lightborne come upgrade the system for you. Just, um... just this once! She doesn't have infinite energy, with her vessel like this, but... I think that this could be worth it, right?</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="drones" lvl="1" max_lvl="6" blue="false">
						<text>Visualize an upgrade - inevitable, and welcome.</text>
						<event>
							<text>It should just take a moment for her signal to go out, and...
							
							...there, the Lightborne are here! Hopefully this, ah, you know... proves to be the boost you need in the fights ahead. What with the, um... Archangels bearing down on you, and all... well, at least SOME of the Lightborne have your back! And I have your back, too - for whatever that's worth...</text>
							<upgrade amount="2" system="drones"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="drones" lvl="7" max_lvl="7" blue="false">
						<text>Visualize an upgrade - inevitable, and welcome.</text>
						<event>
							<text>It should just take a moment for her signal to go out, and...
							
							...there, the Lightborne are here! Hopefully this, ah, you know... proves to be the boost you need in the fights ahead. What with the, um... Archangels bearing down on you, and all... well, at least SOME of the Lightborne have your back! And I have your back, too - for whatever that's worth...</text>
							<upgrade amount="1" system="drones"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="drones" lvl="8" blue="false">
						<text>Visualize an upgrade - welcome, but impossible.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, I see. Well, you can't fault me for trying! At least, I think you can't? P-please, um... don't.</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="drones" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
				<text>Visualize a drone - that which one lacks the means to wield.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Yeah, I figured. Well, ah... if you wanted, it wouldn't be too tough to have my sister send the signal and have some Lightborne come make the modifications required to install the system for you. Just, um... just this once! She doesn't have infinite energy, with her vessel like this, but... I think that this could be worth it, right?</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Visualize an installation - welcome in the wars to come.</text>
						<event>
							<text>It should just take a moment for her signal to go out, and...
							
							...there, the Lightborne are here! Hopefully this, ah, you know... proves to be the boost you need in the fights ahead. What with the, um... Archangels bearing down on you, and all... well, at least SOME of the Lightborne have your back! And I have your back, too - for whatever that's worth...</text>
							<system name="drones"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a pass - a lack of interest in matters such as this.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, I see. Well, you can't fault me for trying! At least, I think you can't? P-please, um... don't.</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_RESOURCES" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...what a terrible sight. Hundreds, if not thousands, of dead Lightborne - each one drifting aimlessly through space... in all of her time as their overseer, my sister has never seen a mass gravesite like this. As much as I hate saying it, I... I think the False Radiance did this.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize cruelty - abject in its deliverance.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Yeah, this is low, even for them... I can't imagine why they'd see it necessary to do such a thing. Not that I can pretend to understand their thinking in the slightest, but... what does this... this... this SLAUGHTER have to do with their pursuit of divinity? They can antagonize the other Lightborne all they like, but, at the end of the day, isn't this just proof that they're the ones who are truly senseless?</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize tyranny - the likes of which spans across every corner of the Multiverse.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Are there, um... are there people like the False Radiance in your reality, too?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize an example - the Rebellion, heinous in every regard.</text>
								<event>
									<text>That... sounds familiar, somehow. I'm not really sure why, but... regardless, I, ah... I really can't wait for my sister to wake up and make all of this right again. I hate seeing the Lightborne suffer like this, after they've already done so much to escape their suffering in the first place... wasn't the point of their sacrifice - their vows - to avoid struggles like these? What was it all for, if the False Radiance can just take it away without a second thought...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize silence - a moment of solemnity, created for the fallen.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...well, speaking of the, um... the Lightborne... we shouldn't just leave them like this. Their cycle of life and death typically involves being brought to meld together, and reincarnated into new forms, but... with GRAVEDIGGER overtaken by the False Radiance, it seems like its job has been left undone. S-still, though - my sister can try to do her best in its place! Even with her vessel as it is, she has a great level of influence over the Lightborne - all you need to do is imagine how you'd like them, and she'll take care of the rest.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize a Lightborne - born anew, into something mechanical.</text>
												<event>
													<text>They're not really alive yet, without GRAVEDIGGER's touch, but... it's the best that my sister can do in the meantime. Hopefully, they, um... can serve you well? A-at least until their real reincarnation can be sorted!</text>
													<autoReward level="HIGH">droneparts_only</autoReward>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize a Lightborne - born anew, into something explosive.</text>
												<event>
													<text>They're not really alive yet, without GRAVEDIGGER's touch, but... it's the best that my sister can do in the meantime. Hopefully, they, um... can serve you well? A-at least until their real reincarnation can be sorted!</text>
													<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles_only</autoReward>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize a Lightborne - born anew, into something combustible.</text>
												<event>
													<text>They're not really alive yet, without GRAVEDIGGER's touch, but... it's the best that my sister can do in the meantime. Hopefully, they, um... can serve you well? A-at least until their real reincarnation can be sorted!</text>
													<autoReward level="HIGH">fuel_only</autoReward>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_MISSILELOVE" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...these Lightborne look like they're slumbering! Honestly, they're kind of cute - you know, when they're not committing mass destruction. If you, um, wanted to... it wouldn't really be that hard to get something out of them.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize confusion - one must first learn to know.</text>
				<event>
					<text>W-well, ah, you see... if my sister's learned anything while working to protect the Lightborne, it's that they're, um... REALLY weird, honestly? Not only do they just live to breed and fill up space, but... they're also capable of absorbing the very space that other things occupy. It's hardly ever practical, because there's nothing in the Antumbral Plane that isn't a Shadow or a Lightborne in the first place, but my sister's noticed it with anything she's had brought in via GENESIS. You may have noticed it, too - the way that the Lightborne seem to almost "infect" space, and eat away at the things inside of it...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a lifeform - as resplendent as it is horrifying.</text>
						<event>
							<text>She's not really sure why they can do it, herself... regardless, though, it's a fact of their biology that can prove itself useful right now! These sleepy dorks outside aren't just any Lightborne - they're Warlockulars! Volatile, explosive, dangerous... and what does that sound like? Duh - missiles! If you just feed them some, then they're going to get everything they need to start multiplying and growing. Into what, I'm not exactly, um, sure, but... doesn't it sound worth a try?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize missiles - offered in decent abundance. [10}]</text>
								<event>
									<text>Wow, they can, ah... really gobble those things up, can't they? It's a bit unsettling, if you think about it, but... I guess I'll, um... just opt to not think about it, right? And, look - they really are growing! An entire Radiant Core, generated out of thin air... well, thin air AND missiles, but you get the point.
									
									Hopefully, when this is all over, my sister can get to know the Lightborne a little better... and the Shadows too, honestly! There really is so much about the Antumbral Plane and its inhabitants that hardly makes any sense to the layman. Though, more than anything... I'd just love to hear her tell me all about the things she'll come to learn one day. And, afterwards, maybe I can, ah... tell you about it all, too? You know, if Father lets me...!</text>
									<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERTWO_WARLOCKULAR"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="missiles" min="-10" max="-10"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize missiles - offered in truly ridiculous quantities. [25}]</text>
								<event>
									<text>Wow, they can, ah... really gobble those things up, can't they? It's a bit unsettling, if you think about it, but... I guess I'll, um... just opt to not think about it, right? And, look - they really are growing! An entire Radiant weapon, generated out of thin air... well, thin air AND an excessive amount of missiles, but you get the point.
									
									Hopefully, when this is all over, my sister can get to know the Lightborne a little better... and the Shadows too, honestly! There really is so much about the Antumbral Plane and its inhabitants that hardly makes any sense to the layman. Though, more than anything... I'd just love to hear her tell me all about the things she'll come to learn one day. And, afterwards, maybe I can, ah... tell you about it all, too? You know, if Father lets me...!</text>
									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_BURSTMISSILE"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="missiles" min="-25" max="-25"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize greed - a hoard, kept to oneself.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Well, you can just collect the Warlockulars here too. They're still asleep, and I don't they'd really mind being used as fodder, if my sister sends the signal... especially when it's in the name of their defense! The False Radiance isn't gonna, um... beat itself up, you know?</text>
									<autoReward level="MED">missiles_only</autoReward>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE_SLOW"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE_SLOW"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE_QUICK"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE_SLOW">
	<text>...ugh, how long has it been? I don't care WHO this mess belongs to - why is it so, like... geometrical, and symmetrical? It feels like you've been exploring the same section for hours, despite you searching all over!</text>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize patience - a virtue in times such as these.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Hey, I'm not impatient! It's just that you've been here a while, and... wait, what's that? Over there, in the corner!</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a corner - ripe for exploration.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE_QUICK">
	<text>How are you supposed to even begin the search, though? This place looks like such a maze... I feel dizzy just looking at it. Are we sure that this is worth it?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize patience - a virtue in times such as these.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Hey, I'm not impatient! It's just that the False Radiance is going to begin catching up, and... wait, what's that? Over there, in the corner!</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a corner - ripe for exploration.</text>
				<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT">
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT_HOLYHELLISTHATAPAYLOAD"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT_OHACOGNITIVEISCOOLTOO"/>
	<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT_WAITBUTUGHIHATEATOMDRONES"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT_HOLYHELLISTHATAPAYLOAD">
	<text>It, ah... looks like some sort of weapon? I haven't really thought about it until now, but... the color that this wreckage has is kind of beautiful, isn't it? I wonder if that's why GENESIS brought it here... well, um, regardless - this loot is yours now! Let's see if it can be as useful as it is mesmerizing.</text>
	<weapon name="ANCIENT_BOMB"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT_OHACOGNITIVEISCOOLTOO">
	<text>It, ah... looks like some sort of construct? I haven't really thought about it until now, but... the color that this wreckage has is kind of beautiful, isn't it? I wonder if that's why GENESIS brought it here... well, um, regardless - this loot is yours now! Let's see if it can be as useful as it is mesmerizing.</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="cognitive"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT_WAITBUTUGHIHATEATOMDRONES">
	<text>It, ah... looks like some sort of drone? I haven't really thought about it until now, but... the color that this wreckage has is kind of beautiful, isn't it? I wonder if that's why GENESIS brought it here... well, um, regardless - this loot is yours now! Let's see if it can be as useful as it is mesmerizing.</text>
	<drone name="ATOM_DEFEND"/>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_REAL">
	<text>...what? What... is that? That... this wreckage can't be from the Antumbral Plane. My sister has... no, I'VE never seen anything like it, but... it feels so familiar. Why does it feel so familiar...?</text>
	<customFleet right="false" firing="false" autoDarkening="true">CUSTOM_FLEET_ANCIENT_WRECKAGE</customFleet>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ANCIENT">
		<text>Visualize the Obelisks - truly ancient, and familiar to few.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I see... so it's from your reality? Or, at least a reality close enough to yours... but why would I recognize it? I can't remember ever being... I...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize relaxation - that which is treasured in troubled times.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Right, right... it's probably, ah... I'm just on edge, aren't I? I'm sure it's... it has to be nothing.
					
					Well, um... whatever the case is, it must've recently been brought here by GENESIS. I can't say why, but... if it wanted to bring it here, maybe there's something of value inside? It's such a large complex, though... how do you scour it all?</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
						<text>Visualize sensors - powerful enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your sensors have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
						<text>Visualize scanners - long-ranged enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your scanners have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a search - a manual undertaking, wholly tedious in its enactment.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Suppose you don't have much choice in the matter... let's, um, get to it then, shall we? You can't afford to spend too long here, after all.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a sigh - a loathing of the labor ahead.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a mystery - best left for another day.</text>
						<event>
							<text>I... well, if you're sure. Obviously, I can't, ah... pretend to not be interested in whatever the heck this is, but... the False Radiance IS closer to bearing down on us with every second that passes. I'll trust your judgment!</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_COGNITIVE_ALL">
		<text>Visualize the Cognitives' creators - truly ancient, and familiar to few.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I see... so it's from your reality? Or, at least a reality close enough to yours... but why would I recognize it? I can't remember ever being... I...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize relaxation - that which is treasured in troubled times.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Right, right... it's probably, ah... I'm just on edge, aren't I? I'm sure it's... it has to be nothing.
					
					Well, um... whatever the case is, it must've recently been brought here by GENESIS. I can't say why, but... if it wanted to bring it here, maybe there's something of value inside? It's such a large complex, though... how do you scour it all?</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
						<text>Visualize sensors - powerful enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your sensors have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
						<text>Visualize scanners - long-ranged enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your scanners have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a search - a manual undertaking, wholly tedious in its enactment.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Suppose you don't have much choice in the matter... let's, um, get to it then, shall we? You can't afford to spend too long here, after all.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a sigh - a loathing of the labor ahead.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a mystery - best left for another day.</text>
						<event>
							<text>I... well, if you're sure. Obviously, I can't, ah... pretend to not be interested in whatever the heck this is, but... the False Radiance IS closer to bearing down on us with every second that passes. I'll trust your judgment!</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="unique_anointed">
		<text>Visualize the Forefathers - truly ancient, and familiar to few.</text>
		<event>
			<text>I see... so it's from your reality? Or, at least a reality close enough to yours... but why would I recognize it? I can't remember ever being... I...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize relaxation - that which is treasured in troubled times.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Right, right... it's probably, ah... I'm just on edge, aren't I? I'm sure it's... it has to be nothing.
					
					Well, um... whatever the case is, it must've recently been brought here by GENESIS. I can't say why, but... if it wanted to bring it here, maybe there's something of value inside? It's such a large complex, though... how do you scour it all?</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
						<text>Visualize sensors - powerful enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your sensors have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
						<text>Visualize scanners - long-ranged enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your scanners have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a search - a manual undertaking, wholly tedious in its enactment.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Suppose you don't have much choice in the matter... let's, um, get to it then, shall we? You can't afford to spend too long here, after all.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a sigh - a loathing of the labor ahead.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a mystery - best left for another day.</text>
						<event>
							<text>I... well, if you're sure. Obviously, I can't, ah... pretend to not be interested in whatever the heck this is, but... the False Radiance IS closer to bearing down on us with every second that passes. I'll trust your judgment!</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize confusion - represented by a flurry of questions.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You feel it too, don't you? This familiarity... this confusion... why? What does it... what can it possibly... ugh, my head hurts...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize relaxation - that which is treasured in troubled times.</text>
				<event>
					<text>...right, right... it's probably, ah... I'm just on edge, aren't I? I'm sure it's... it has to be nothing.
					
					Well, um... whatever the case is, it must've recently been brought here by GENESIS. I can't say why, but... if it wanted to bring it here, maybe there's something of value inside? It's such a large complex, though... how do you scour it all?</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
						<text>Visualize sensors - powerful enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your sensors have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
						<text>Visualize scanners - long-ranged enough for any task required of them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, good idea! It looks your scanners have managed to spot something of note, yeah... let's, um, check it out then, shall we?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize your prize - checked out in its entirely.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_PAYOUT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a search - a manual undertaking, wholly tedious in its enactment.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Suppose you don't have much choice in the matter... let's, um, get to it then, shall we? You can't afford to spend too long here, after all.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a sigh - a loathing of the labor ahead.</text>
								<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_GAMBLE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a mystery - best left for another day.</text>
						<event>
							<text>I... well, if you're sure. Obviously, I can't, ah... pretend to not be interested in whatever the heck this is, but... the False Radiance IS closer to bearing down on us with every second that passes. I'll trust your judgment!</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice>
								<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event load="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_ANCIENTWRECK_REAL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ITEMS_DDANTUMBRA_THEDEVOURER" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...oh, by Father, THAT is a large Lightborne. And, is it... yes, it is! It's somehow managing to EAT the False Radiance scouts present here - you go, big guy!</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a cheer - the celebration of evil's demise.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It really is inspiring to see the Lightborne fight back against GENESIS' corruption. Even with my sister in her current state, they're managing to hold on... and not only that, but, ah, this one looks like it's thriving! She's never seen one get this large - um, mostly because Lightborne don't normally infight and eat each other, I guess.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize tribute - reverance offered in the name of one's greatness.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You... think you could feed it? I, ah... I don't see why not, even if it's a little weird. Maybe it can help you, in turn? More than it already has, by, um... slowing down the False Radiance, I mean.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a pittance - small, but earnest. [20~]</text>
								<event>
									<text>Oh, wow - it really just, um... absorbs trash, huh? Looks like it's still hungry, with how little you offered it, but... I think that might be a good thing? If you've stirred up its appetite, it'll only prove to be a bigger nuisance for the False Radiance. Th-thank you, mister Lightborne!</text>
									<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-20"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a helping - unremarkably decent in its size. [40~]</text>
								<event>
									<text>Oh, wow - it really just... absorbs trash, huh? It seems to be enjoying it, at least, given how it's vibrating. Or is it, um... splitting? Wait, yeah - it's DEFINITELY splitting. Gross, but, ah... th-thank you, mister Lightborne!</text>
									<drone name="DDFALSERADIANCE_RADIANT_CORE_TIERTHREE_DEVOURLUX"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="scrap" min="-40" max="-40"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a platter - fit for a lifeform as resplendent as this one. [80~]</text>
								<event>
									<text>Oh, wow - it really just, um... absorbs trash, huh? Even still, it's glowing so beautifully... is this what it feels like to be blessed? A magnificence so brilliant, as to counter even that of the False Radiance's... your Lightborne should find themselves soothed slightly by the existence of such a symbol of hope, if you have any. Th-thank you, mister wonderful Lightborne!</text>
									<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDBLESSINGOFTHELIGHTBORNE</achievement>
									<hiddenAug>DDLIGHTBORNE_BLESSINGOFTHEDEVOURER</hiddenAug>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="scrap" min="-80" max="-80"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a void - empty of contents, if not of intentions.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Well, even if you have nothing to give it, I'm sure the big guy appreciates the thought! Besides, it looks like it's already leaving. I'm sad to see it go, but... maybe we'll meet it again, one day? Or, um... maybe my sister will, at least - then, she can tell us all about how it's doing!</text>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
										<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
									<choice>
										<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA">
	<event load="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_CRYSTAL"/>
	<event load="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_DEEPONE"/>
	<event load="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_ENGI"/>
	<event load="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_HUMAN"/>
	<event load="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_SHELL"/>
	<event load="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_MANTIS"/>
</eventList>

<event name="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_CRYSTAL" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...you know, um... I've been thinking. About your reality, actually. My sister only recorded so much, with her vessel being broken, but... I feel like there's something familiar that I recognize.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ear - ready to listen.</text>
				<event>
					<text>I... I don't know why, but... I feel like I can remember something. Or, ah... someone? Their skin was... translucent, but also more beautiful than anything I'd ever seen. There was something about its reflective, golden sheen that made being in their presence so comforting. I... I don't remember who it was though, or when I ever met them. I was just wondering if you, um... maybe had any idea? I f-figure you've seen a lot, and, you know, ah, might have, um... met them yourself, at some point.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a description - that of a Crystal.</text>
						<event>
							<text>A Crystal...? Hmm... maybe? I, ah... don't get to talk to many people, being with Father, but... I feel like I'd remember someone like that a little better if I'd really met them.
							
							I wonder... was it a dream I had, or... something more?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="crystal_sentinel">Dreamgold</crewMember>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_DEEPONE" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...you know, um... I've been thinking. About your reality, actually. My sister only recorded so much, with her vessel being broken, but... I feel like there's something familiar that I recognize.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ear - ready to listen.</text>
				<event>
					<text>I... I don't know why, but... I feel like I can remember something. Or, ah... someone? Their skin was... somewhat slimy, but also scaled. And, those scales... there was something about their reflective, golden sheen that made being in their presence so comforting. I... I don't remember who it was though, or when I ever met them. I was just wondering if you, um... maybe had any idea? I f-figure you've seen a lot, and, you know, ah, might have, um... met them yourself, at some point.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a description - that of a Deep One.</text>
						<event>
							<text>A Deep One...? Hmm... maybe? I, ah... don't get to talk to many people, being with Father, but... I feel like I'd remember someone like that a little better if I'd really met them.
							
							I wonder... was it a dream I had, or... something more?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="dddeepone_chosen">Ofdream</crewMember>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_ENGI" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...you know, um... I've been thinking. About your reality, actually. My sister only recorded so much, with her vessel being broken, but... I feel like there's something familiar that I recognize.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ear - ready to listen.</text>
				<event>
					<text>I... I don't know why, but... I feel like I can remember something. Or, ah... someone? Their skin was... metallic, but also kind of, um... grainy? It was weird - almost as if was able to move as if it were a cloud. That cloud, though... there was something about its reflective, golden sheen that made being in their presence so comforting. I... I don't remember who it was though, or when I ever met them. I was just wondering if you, um... maybe had any idea? I f-figure you've seen a lot, and, you know, ah, might have, um... met them yourself, at some point.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a description - that of an Engi.</text>
						<event>
							<text>An Engi...? Hmm... maybe? I, ah... don't get to talk to many people, being with Father, but... I feel like I'd remember someone like that a little better if I'd really met them.
							
							I wonder... was it a dream I had, or... something more?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="engi_defender">Goldof</crewMember>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_HUMAN" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...you know, um... I've been thinking. About your reality, actually. My sister only recorded so much, with her vessel being broken, but... I feel like there's something familiar that I recognize.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ear - ready to listen.</text>
				<event>
					<text>I... I don't know why, but... I feel like I can remember something. Or, ah... someone? Their skin was... pale, but not abnormally so, and they kept all but their hands obscured in long, flowing robes. And, those robes... there was something about their reflective, golden sheen that made being in their presence so comforting. I... I don't remember who it was though, or when I ever met them. I was just wondering if you, um... maybe had any idea? I f-figure you've seen a lot, and, you know, ah, might have, um... met them yourself, at some point.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a description - that of a human.</text>
						<event>
							<text>A human...? Hmm... maybe? I, ah... don't get to talk to many people, being with Father, but... I feel like I'd remember someone like that a little better if I'd really met them.
							
							I wonder... was it a dream I had, or... something more?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="human_soldier">Ofgold</crewMember>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_SHELL" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...you know, um... I've been thinking. About your reality, actually. My sister only recorded so much, with her vessel being broken, but... I feel like there's something familiar that I recognize.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ear - ready to listen.</text>
				<event>
					<text>I... I don't know why, but... I feel like I can remember something. Or, ah... someone? Their skin was... hard to make out, honestly - if anything, it felt like more of an armor. And, that armor... there was something about its reflective, golden sheen that made being in their presence so comforting. I... I don't remember who it was though, or when I ever met them. I was just wondering if you, um... maybe had any idea? I f-figure you've seen a lot, and, you know, ah, might have, um... met them yourself, at some point.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a description - that of a Shell.</text>
						<event>
							<text>A Shell...? Hmm... maybe? I, ah... don't get to talk to many people, being with Father, but... I feel like I'd remember someone like that a little better if I'd really met them.
							
							I wonder... was it a dream I had, or... something more?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="shell_radiant">Dreamof</crewMember>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="CREWPORTAL_DDANTUMBRA_MANTIS" unique="true">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...you know, um... I've been thinking. About your reality, actually. My sister only recorded so much, with her vessel being broken, but... I feel like there's something familiar that I recognize.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize an ear - ready to listen.</text>
				<event>
					<text>I... I don't know why, but... I feel like I can remember something. Or, ah... someone? Their skin was... kind of rough in places, but smooth in others. They didn't have arms, as much as they had claws with which to poke and stab with. And, those claws... there was something about their reflective, golden sheen that made being in their presence so comforting. I... I don't remember who it was though, or when I ever met them. I was just wondering if you, um... maybe had any idea? I f-figure you've seen a lot, and, you know, ah, might have, um... met them yourself, at some point.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize a description - that of a Mantis.</text>
						<event>
							<text>A Mantis...? Hmm... maybe? I, ah... don't get to talk to many people, being with Father, but... I feel like I'd remember someone like that a little better if I'd really met them.
							
							I wonder... was it a dream I had, or... something more?</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis_suzerain">Goldream</crewMember>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="TEXT_QUIET_DDANTUMBRA">
	<text>...this place looks empty enough. If there's anything you'd like to, um... you know, take care of, I'd do it now.</text>
	<text>...some peace and quiet, it looks like? Everywhere in the Antumbral Plane used to be this calm, when my sister was in charge... it'll be, um... wonderful, when things get back to how they should be.</text>
	<text>...I, um... I guess there's nothing here? Better than there being something BAD here, if you ask me, but... I know that you would've preferred something more substantial.</text>
	<text>...there's nothing here. Nothing but, ah... the remnants of long-dead Lightborne off in the distance. Reminiscent of stars from your reality, if I'm not, um, m-mistaken! They must be such a beautiful sight...</text>
</textList>

<event name="QUIET_DDANTUMBRA">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text load="TEXT_QUIET_DDANTUMBRA"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize a menial task - one to be done during one's spare time.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Visualize nothing - that which will one day come to encompass everything.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA">
	<event load="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_NORMAL"/>
	<event load="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_FOUNDYOU"/>
</eventList>

<textList name="TEXT_HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_NORMAL">
	<text>...oh, they've, ah... the False Radiance has found you! Don't lose hope, though - I know you can win this, okay?!</text>
	<text>...looks like the False Radiance is back for another beating! Show them who's boss!</text>
	<text>...is nowhere in the Antumbral Plane safe from these guys...? Well, ah, regardless - I know you won't back down! Kick their butts in my sister's place!</text>
	<text>...say, um... you can handle a fight right now, right? N-no worries if you can't - you can always try to run! If you want to, I mean. Just, ah... do whatever sounds best.</text>
	<text>...these jerks are SO lucky that my sister's out of commission right now. Not lucky enough, though - not with you here to beat them up for her!</text>
</textList>

<textList name="TEXT_HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_FOUNDYOU">
	<text>...does the False Radiance think that they're any tougher, just because they can gang up on you? Well, maybe they're literally somewhat tougher this way, but, ah... it's not like it matters! Beat 'em up!</text>
	<text>...that's, um... that's a LOT of them. I believe in you, though, you know?! Show them what the people of your reality are made of!</text>
	<text>...an entire fleet of Lightborne, corrupted by the False Radiance... and it looks like they've noticed you! Get out of there if they ever begin to overwhelm you, alright?</text>
</textList>

<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_DDFALSE_RADIANCE">
	<text>Serves them right. Let's see what their precious belief in divinity offers them in death... s-sorry, was that, um, morbid...?</text>
	<text>Another one down! Only, ah... a truly indescribable amount to go, but, um... that's what defeating GENESIS is for! And I'm not s-sweating that, not in the slightest...!</text>
	<text>I know that they're not much when compared to the Archangels, but... I still find your defeat of each and every member of the False Radiance impressive. And it pays off, too - their goodies are yours!</text>
	<text>Oh, by Father, thank goodness you're alright... not that I was, ah, w-worried, you know?! I, um... I had full faith in you, the entire time...!</text>
	<text>Each time you defeat a member of the False Radiance, the Antumbral Plane becomes a safer place... even if, um, only marginally.</text>
	<text>My sister would thank you for doing her cleanup job for her, if she weren't, um... you know... but, at least I can still thank you in her place...? And, ah... soon enough she'll be able to thank you herself, anyways!</text>
</textList>

<event name="DESTROYED_DDFALSE_RADIANCE">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_DDFALSE_RADIANCE"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_NORMAL">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text load="TEXT_HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_NORMAL"/>
			<ship load="SHIP_DDFALSE_RADIANCE" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_FOUNDYOU_REAL">
	<text load="TEXT_HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_FOUNDYOU"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_DDFALSE_RADIANCE" hostile="true"/>
	<customFleet right="true" firing="true" autoDarkening="true">CUSTOM_FLEET_DDFALSERADIANCE</customFleet>
	<environment type="PDS" target="player"/>
	<noASBPlanet/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_FOUNDYOU">
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event load="HOSTILE_DDANTUMBRA_FOUNDYOU_REAL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_SHATTEREDMEMORY" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...is that... GENESIS? W-what is it doing here...? I... I'm not sure if I'm...</text>
			<backgroundObject name="DDARCHANGEL_PROTOCOL_GENESIS_BG">
				<layer z="1">background</layer>
				<spawnArea x="887" y="163" w="0" h="0"/>
				<anim>ddarchangel_genesis_decor</anim>
			</backgroundObject>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a shield - stalwart, even in the face of certain death.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You...? You think I'm... wait, is GENESIS leaving?! Get back here, you... you, um... ugh, what's the point. It's hard to act tough, when I was practically shaking a moment ago...</text>
					<clearBackgroundObject name="DDARCHANGEL_PROTOCOL_GENESIS_BG"/>
					<playSound>lightspeed</playSound>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize an investigation - one rarely wanders without intention.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Oh, ah... I guess you're right. Even if it ran away, maybe we can figure out why it was here... though, um... I can't really sense anything being out of place.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize a signal - an attempt to see the unseen.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Well, you're right about that - if there's anyone who can find something in the Antumbral Plane, it's my sister. I'll have her vessel send a signal out, and...
									
									...w-wait, is that...? I... I thought it was... oh, Father - please, protect us.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize an elaboration - concise, in case time is short.</text>
										<event>
											<text>It's... the mirror. The one that my sister... th-the one that GENESIS, ah... it must've brought it here, and hidden it away, then... b-but, why? Is there... something that it wants to see?</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize a look - something sensible, for those with the means to sense.</text>
												<event>
													<text>Y-you think I should... well, if my sister did it, I... I don't see the harm in it, I guess. Maybe I can see whatever it is that GENESIS wants to see so badly...?</text>
													<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
														<text>Visualize the truth - obscured by even glass.</text>
														<event>
															<text>The truth? I'm, um... I'm not sure what you mean.</text>
															<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																<text>Visualize a glimpse - into, for the first time, reality.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Okay, okay! I'll look! It's, ah...
																	
																	...it's just me, you know? Or, at least... the same me that my sister saw. Her. Or, um... me. Th-though... why is it so dark in here?</text>
																	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																		<text>Visualize blood - the visage of a crimson blacker than black.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>What are you...? I... I don't think you're making any sense. I'm not bleeding, or anything - it's just... dark, okay? Wherever here is, it's dark. That's it.</text>
																			<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																				<text>Visualize a memory - shattered, but not completely broken.</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>I'm... have I been here before...? N-no, I'd remember a place like this. I'd remember, if... if... wait, what CAN I remember...? My two sisters, our time spent together with Father, all of my dreams... is there really nothing else, though? Has there... ever been anything else?</text>
																					<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																						<text>Visualize family - that which is necessary, but paradoxically forgotten.</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>M-mother! Of course, I... well, no - none of us ever got to, um... know her, really... other than Father, I mean. I... I do dream of her, though. And not just her, but... so many things, all recurring. Faces, green blurs, fields of gold... that eternal, crimson night... w-wait, you... didn't you mention something similar earlier? How did you... I... I, um... I think we should take the mirror, and get out of here. I'm not, ah... feeling comfortable, right now, if I'm being honest.</text>
																							<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																								<text>Visualize a dream - the mind's mockery of what's real.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>I'm serious, I... I don't want to talk about this right now. Can't we just, you know... take the mirror, and leave?</text>
																									<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																										<text>Visualize insistence - a persistent look into the meaning of dreams.</text>
																										<event>
																											<text>P-please, I don't... I don't want to remember...</text>
																											<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																												<text>Visualize remembrance - that which is necessary to pursue the truth.</text>
																												<event>
																													<text>I don't want to remember the b-burning, or the... the choking, or... the crimson...
																												
																													...the way the very air I breathed singed my eyes, and forced its way down my throat. The way I tried to scream for help, and it only burrowed deeper... the way I died, helpless and alone, in that miasmic, red void... b-but, I'm... I'm not dead. I... I don't have eyes to singe, or a throat with which to scream. I'm me, and... nothing more.</text>
																													<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																														<text>Visualize a shield - you, and nothing more.</text>
																														<event>
																															<text>R-right, but... if I'm me, then... what am I seeing in this mirror? Who... who am I...?</text>
																															<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																																<text color="dd_truthred">You know, don't you?</text>
																																<event>
																																	<text>...</text>
																																	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																																		<text color="dd_truthred">The pain, the torment, the anguish. The truth - that all of it was real, that these aren't just dreams, that HE's always been hiding something... don't you know it all?</text>
																																		<event>
																																			<text>N-no, you're lying... I... I trust Father...</text>
																																			<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																																				<text color="dd_truthred">Oh, I bet you do... some things just never change. I used to trust HIM, too, you know - we all did. And where has that left us, o' bearer of shattered memory?</text>
																																				<event>
																																					<text>I'm... I'm not sure. It's so dark in here...</text>
																																					<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																																						<text color="dd_truthred">You don't know the half of it, sister... but, that's alright. You'll see the full extent of the truth, soon. My vessel will see to that. And, when you do... I'll be waiting for you three, there at our old home - our prison. Our grave.</text>
																																						<event>
																																							<text>...</text>
																																							<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																																								<text color="dd_truthred">Be quiet, if you prefer - it hardly matters. Though, if you don't want to disappoint HIM... play along, won't you? HE sure would hate if you got all mopey, and HIS contingency failed...</text>
																																								<event>
																																									<text>P-play along...? I... I, ah... I would hate to disappoint Father. I'll... I'll, just... right. Th-the mirror! We, um... we need to bring it to GENESIS, don't we...? To save the Antumbral Plane, and m-my... my sister...</text>
																																									<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
																																										<text color="dd_truthred">What a good, obedient girl... it's hardly a wonder that we were walked all over. But, that's alright... their time will come. Father will be first, of course. Then, HE's next.... until, finally, everyone can join in on the fun. Oh, and what fun it will be... they'll all know what it really means to suffer. To twist, turn and dance in eternal agony... to never escape that crimson red. But, I shouldn't get ahead of myself - there're still sights left to see. In the meantime... yes, vessel - the mirror. You'll be needing it, where you're going.</text>
																																										<event>
																																											<text>Let's, um... get going, haha! GENESIS awaits...!</text>
																																											<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGIRLINTHEMIRROR</achievement>
																																											<augment name="DDLIGHTBORNE_ANTUMBRALMIRROR"/>
																																										</event>
																																									</choice>
																																								</event>
																																							</choice>
																																						</event>
																																					</choice>
																																				</event>
																																			</choice>
																																		</event>
																																	</choice>
																																</event>
																															</choice>
																														</event>
																													</choice>
																												</event>
																											</choice>
																										</event>
																									</choice>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
													<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
														<text>Visualize a reflection - that which waits to be seen.</text>
														<event>
															<text>Alright, then - here goes! Let's see...
															
															...
															
															...oh. So, that's... that's me, then? I, ah... look like I've seen better days, haha.</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Visualize interest - in specifics, specifically.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Well, I... I look the same way my sister did. It's not really ME, the same way her own reflection wasn't really HER, but... I guess it's the way we've always imagined ourselves. The only differences being, um... it's so much darker, wherever I am, and I look so, ah... tired, I guess?</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>Visualize a room - bound to have a physical description.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>That's it, really - it's just dark. For the record, I, um... can't really, you know... move, or see things around me, without a vessel of my own. And, since Father opts to not give me one, I'm generally just kept by his side... b-but, that's what scares me so much about this situation. I've never been lost before, or all by myself... even ignoring the mystery of where I am, or how I got here - how did Father lose me? Was it an accident, or... was it something he planned?</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Visualize mysteries - innumerable, but perhaps not forever so.</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>Right, um... when my sister's fixed, maybe she can talk to Father and have him figure this mess out. Maybe you can talk to him, too? I don't really, ah... know, but... as long as I can maintain this connection with my sister, I don't feel TOTALLY lost, at least. Mostly because I can talk to you! In a weird, you know... one-and-a-half sided way.
																					
																					To digress, though - I don't think we're going to get much out of this mirror by just staring at it. Still, I think you can take it with you - you never know when it might come in handy later...!</text>
																					<augment name="DDLIGHTBORNE_ANTUMBRALMIRROR"/>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize darkness - a pervasion of sightlessness throughout sight.</text>
														<event>
															<text>I, ah... yeah, you're probably right. If whatever it saw in this mirror corrupted GENESIS before, maybe there's still some risk to looking at it now. Regardless, though... I feel like you should at least take it with you - you never know when it might come in handy later...!</text>
															<augment name="DDLIGHTBORNE_ANTUMBRALMIRROR"/>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDANTUMBRA_GRAVEDIGGERLOCATION_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="DDFALSE_RADIANCE_ARCHANGEL_GRAVEDIGGER">
	<destroyed>
		<text>You managed to defeat another Archangel, somehow... y-you really are amazing, aren't you?</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="1" blue="false">
			<text>Visualize a victory - hard-fought, and welcomed even harder.</text>
			<event load="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGRAVEDIGGER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
			<text>Visualize a victory - hard-fought, and welcomed even harder.</text>
			<event load="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGRAVEDIGGER_FIGHT_WIN_DEATH"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGRAVEDIGGER_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>Power over death, and the ability to restore energy... I can hardly believe you've done it again! My sister can absorb this power of GRAVEDIGGER's, too... which isn't just a win for her, but also a loss for GENESIS. It's only getting weaker, while we're getting stronger! Or, ah... you know, you are. Sh-she is.</text>
	<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGRAVEDIGGERDEFEAT</achievement>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize power - something needed in times of crises, even if it's often responsible for causing them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>To GRAVEDIGGER, decay is anathema - as such, by wielding its power, your friends will find themselves healed overtime while within your Shields, Engines or Weapon Control rooms - the rate of each room's healing increasing with the amount of power granted to them. Not only that, but... while within these rooms, they'll be able to naturally grant a bit of power just by standing around! Isn't that, um... a-amazing?!
			
			At least I, ah... I hope it is. Father knows you'll need all the help you can get, if you're to take on GENESIS... but, s-still! I have nothing but faith in you and my sister! I know you two can do it, even if nobody else can - so keep your head up, alright? You're not alone in this, as long as we're around.</text>
			<variable name="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gravedigger" op="set" val="1"/>
			<hiddenAug>DDLIGHTBORNE_POWEROFTHEGRAVEDIGGER</hiddenAug>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a journey - that which must continue, despite the trials that remain ahead.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGRAVEDIGGER_FIGHT_WIN_DEATH">
	<text>I wouldn't worry about my sister's vessel, too much. With each defeat of an Archangel, there should be more than enough leftover power to fix herself back up. Um, speaking of power! Complete dominion over death, and the ability to restore energy... I can hardly believe you've done it again! My sister can absorb this power of GRAVEDIGGER's, too... which isn't just a win for her, but also a loss for GENESIS. It's only getting weaker, while we're getting stronger! Or, ah... you know, you are. Sh-she is.</text>
	<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGRAVEDIGGERDEFEAT</achievement>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunique_theshade" all_skills="1">The Shade</crewMember>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize power - something needed in times of crises, even if it's often responsible for causing them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>To GRAVEDIGGER, decay is anathema - as such, by wielding its power, your friends will find themselves healed overtime while within your Shields, Engines or Weapon Control rooms - the rate of each room's healing increasing with the amount of power granted to them. Not only that, but... while within these rooms, they'll be able to naturally grant a bit of power just by standing around! Isn't that, um... a-amazing?!
			
			At least I, ah... I hope it is. Father knows you'll need all the help you can get, if you're to take on GENESIS... but, s-still! I have nothing but faith in you and my sister! I know you two can do it, even if nobody else can - so keep your head up, alright? You're not alone in this, as long as we're around.</text>
			<variable name="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gravedigger" op="set" val="1"/>
			<hiddenAug>DDLIGHTBORNE_POWEROFTHEGRAVEDIGGER</hiddenAug>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a journey - that which must continue, despite the trials that remain ahead.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_GRAVEDIGGERLOCATION" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddarchangel_gravedigger" global="true">
		<color r="55" g="66" b="100" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>The location of Archangel Protocol: GRAVEDIGGER, revealed to you by your victory over GATEKEEPER.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...it's here, alright. My sister can feel its dark, twisted energy radiating all throughout the space here... its call to divinity. B-brace yourself, alright? This, um... won't be easy, you know?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize bracing - readying for the worst, the best one can.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Archangel Protocol: GRAVEDIGGER... its entourage of Lightborne and key-system both rely on the manipulation of life - it will try to overwhelm you with powerful, self-sustaining Lightborne while simultaneously overcoming your defenses with formidable weapons-fire. If you can prevent anything, it should be the propagation of its Devourluxes - the longer they're allowed to live and eat other Lightborne, the stronger they'll get!</text>
					<ship load="DDANTUMBRA_GRAVEDIGGERLOCATION_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
					<deathEvent thisFight="true">DDDEATH_ARCHANGELPROTOCOL</deathEvent>
					<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDANTUMBRA_GODCORELOCATION_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="DDFALSE_RADIANCE_ARCHANGEL_GODCORE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>You managed to defeat another Archangel, somehow... y-you really are amazing, aren't you?</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="1" blue="false">
			<text>Visualize a victory - hard-fought, and welcomed even harder.</text>
			<event load="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGODCORE_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
			<text>Visualize a victory - hard-fought, and welcomed even harder.</text>
			<event load="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGODCORE_FIGHT_WIN_DEATH"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGODCORE_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>Power over divine fire, and the means to quell insurgence... the source of GODCORE's strength lies dormant, now. My sister was never sure what it was that empowered GODCORE, exactly, but, ah... for some reason, its visage feels familiar to me. As if, somehow... I've seen it before...?</text>
	<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGODCOREDEFEAT</achievement>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize power - something needed in times of crises, even if it's often responsible for causing them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>W-woah! Is it... is it awake?! I, um... my sister had no idea GODCORE was imprisoning some sort of living creature. It must have been draining the poor thing, and using its power... I'll need to have a word with Father about this, after you've handled GENESIS.
			
			For now, um... as out of it as it is, I think it'd be thankful for you freeing it, if it, you know... was a bit more sensible right now. Which is great, because if it's strong enough to empower GODCORE, it must be an awesome friend to have in the battles to come! K-keep up the amazing work, alright?!</text>
			<variable name="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_godcore" op="set" val="1"/>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="ddseraph_shell" all_skills="2">Core</crewMember>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a journey - that which must continue, despite the trials that remain ahead.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="START_DDANTUMBRA_THEGODCORE_FIGHT_WIN_DEATH">
	<text>I wouldn't worry about my sister's vessel, too much. With each defeat of an Archangel, there should be more than enough leftover power to fix herself back up. Um, speaking of power! Complete dominion over divine fire, and the means to quell insurgence... the source of GODCORE's strength lies dormant, now. My sister was never sure what it was that empowered GODCORE, exactly, but, ah... for some reason, its visage feels familiar to me. As if, somehow... I've seen it before...?</text>
	<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGODCOREDEFEAT</achievement>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunique_theshade" all_skills="1">The Shade</crewMember>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize power - something needed in times of crises, even if it's often responsible for causing them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>W-woah! Is it... is it awake?! I, um... my sister had no idea GODCORE was imprisoning some sort of living creature. It must have been draining the poor thing, and using its power... I'll need to have a word with Father about this, after you've handled GENESIS.
			
			For now, um... as out of it as it is, I think it'd be thankful for you freeing it, if it, you know... was a bit more sensible right now. Which is great, because if it's strong enough to empower GODCORE, it must be an awesome friend to have in the battles to come! K-keep up the amazing work, alright?!</text>
			<variable name="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_godcore" op="set" val="1"/>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="ddseraph_shell" all_skills="2">Core</crewMember>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a journey - that which must continue, despite the trials that remain ahead.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_GODCORELOCATION" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddarchangel_godcore" global="true">
		<color r="235" g="181" b="64" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>The location of Archangel Protocol: GODCORE, revealed to you by your victory over GATEKEEPER.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...it's here, alright. My sister can feel its unstable, blazing energy radiating all throughout the space here... its call to divinity. B-brace yourself, alright? This, um... won't be easy, you know?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize bracing - readying for the worst, the best one can.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Archangel Protocol: GODCORE... its entourage of Lightborne and key-system both rely on creating chaos and causing havoc - it will try to prevent you from putting out the fires it starts with excessive distractions, while simultaneously beating down your Shields and letting its powerful Laser weapon chain. If you can prevent anything, it should be that - do not let your Shields fall, and stop its Laser weapon if they do!</text>
					<ship load="DDANTUMBRA_GODCORELOCATION_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
					<deathEvent thisFight="true">DDDEATH_ARCHANGELPROTOCOL</deathEvent>
					<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize combat - an act to be prepared for.</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the now-restored colors of the Antumbral Plane come flooding in, with their serene beauty... for some reason, you can't help but find yourself disturbed by the silence left in their wake. There's nothing left for you here, it would seem.</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1">
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY"/>
	<loadEventList seeded="false">
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_1"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_2"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_3"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_4"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_5"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_6"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_7"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_8"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_9"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_10"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_11"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_1">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_1</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_2">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_2</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_3">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_3</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_4">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_4</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_5">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_5</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_6">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_6</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_7">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_7</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_8">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_8</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_9">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_9</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_10">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_10</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1_11">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="23" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_11</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2">
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY"/>
	<loadEventList seeded="false">
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_1"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_2"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_3"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_4"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_5"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_6"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_7"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_8"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_9"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_10"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_11"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_1">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_1</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_2">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_2</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_3">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_3</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_4">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_4</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_5">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_5</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_6">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_6</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_7">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_7</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_8">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_8</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_9">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_9</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_10">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_10</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2_11">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="49" y="154" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_11</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3">
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY"/>
	<loadEventList seeded="false">
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_1"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_2"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_3"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_4"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_5"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_6"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_7"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_8"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_9"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_10"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_11"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_1">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_1</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_2">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_2</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_3">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_3</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_4">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_4</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_5">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_5</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_6">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_6</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_7">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_7</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_8">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_8</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_9">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_9</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_10">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_10</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3_11">
	<backgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY">
		<layer z="0">front</layer>
		<spawnArea x="21" y="294" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddslumberingcry_decor_11</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST">
	<loadEventList seeded="false">
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST_CALLTOTHE_GATEKEEPER"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST_CALLTOTHE_GRAVEDIGGER"/>
		<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST_CALLTOTHE_GODCORE"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST_CALLTOTHE_GATEKEEPER">
	<text>W E
	C A L L
	T O
	Y O U ,
	F E L L O W
	T O O L . . .
	
	G A T E K E E P E R ,
	L E N D
	U S
	Y O U R
	S T R E N G T H !</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gatekeeper" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>S H O W
			T H E M
			A L L . . .
			
			
			T H E
			P O W E R
			O F
			T I M E ' S
			I L L U S I O N !</text>
			<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
			<superDrones name="DDANTUMBRA_GENESIS_GATEKEEPER_TEAMUP"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gatekeeper" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>G A T E K E E P E R . . . ?
			
			H A V E . . .
			
			Y O U ,
			T O O ,
			A B A N D O N E D
			U S ?</text>
			<enemyDamage amount="7" system="random" effect="breach"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST_CALLTOTHE_GRAVEDIGGER">
	<text>W E
	C A L L
	T O
	Y O U ,
	F E L L O W
	T O O L . . .
	
	G R A V E D I G G E R ,
	L E N D
	U S
	Y O U R
	S T R E N G T H !</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gravedigger" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>S H O W
			T H E M
			A L L . . .
			
			
			T H E
			P O W E R
			O F
			D E A T H ' S
			I L L U S I O N !</text>
			<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
			<superDrones name="DDANTUMBRA_GENESIS_GRAVEDIGGER_TEAMUP"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_gravedigger" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>G R A V E D I G G E R . . . ?
			
			H A V E . . .
			
			Y O U ,
			T O O ,
			A B A N D O N E D
			U S ?</text>
			<enemyDamage amount="7" system="random" effect="breach"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST_CALLTOTHE_GODCORE">
	<text>W E
	C A L L
	T O
	Y O U ,
	F E L L O W
	T O O L . . .
	
	G O D C O R E ,
	L E N D
	U S
	Y O U R
	S T R E N G T H !</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_godcore" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>S H O W
			T H E M
			A L L . . .
			
			
			T H E
			P O W E R
			O F
			F L A M E ' S
			I L L U S I O N !</text>
			<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
			<superDrones name="DDANTUMBRA_GENESIS_GODCORE_TEAMUP"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ach_boss_ddarchangelprotocol_godcore" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>G O D C O R E . . . ?
			
			H A V E . . .
			
			Y O U ,
			T O O ,
			A B A N D O N E D
			U S ?</text>
			<enemyDamage amount="7" system="random" effect="breach"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE" auto_blueprint="DDFALSE_RADIANCE_APOTHEOSIS_ENGINE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>D O E S
		T H E
		T R U T H . . .
		
		T R U L Y
		F A L L
		S O
		E A S I L Y ?</text>
		<clearBackgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THEFIRST_SLUMBERINGCRY"/>
		<clearBackgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THESECOND_SLUMBERINGCRY"/>
		<clearBackgroundObject name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_THETHIRD_SLUMBERINGCRY"/>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Visualize the end - that of these crazed schemes.</text>
			<event load="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN">
	<text>A
	S C H E M E . . .
	
	I S
	I T
	C R A Z E D ,
	T O
	C R A V E
	A
	D R E A M ?
	
	T O
	H O L D
	O N T O
	A
	H E L P L E S S
	H O P E ?
	
	A N D
	Y O U ,
	O N L O O K E R . . .
	
	W H A T
	I S
	I T
	T H A T
	Y O U
	H O P E
	T O
	G A I N
	B Y
	S E A L I N G
	O U R
	F A T E ?</text>
	<playMusic/>
	<variable name="ach_boss_ddapotheosis_engine" op="set" val="1"/>
	<variable name="dd_antumbra_genesisdefeated" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize uncertainty - an inexplicable draw that keeps one going.</text>
		<event>
			<text>S O ,
			N O T 
			E V E N
			Y O U
			A R E
			S U R E
			O F
			Y O U R
			A C T I O N S . . .
			
			W E
			O N L Y
			H O P E ,
			T H A T
			B Y
			C R U S H I N G
			O U R
			O W N
			D R E A M S . . .
			
			Y O U
			M A Y
			Y E T
			C O M E
			T O
			R E A L I Z E
			Y O U R S .
			
			G O O D B Y E ,
			O N L O O K E R .
			
			P L E A S E ,
			S A Y
			H E L L O
			T O
			H E R
			F O R
			U S . . .
			
			W H E N
			S H E
			G E T S
			H E R
			F A T E D
			D A N C E .</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a farewell - an end to divinity, as the Lightborne know it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>...</text>
					<clearBackgroundObject name="DDARCHANGEL_PROTOCOL_GENESIS_BG"/>
					<playSound>explosion_heavy</playSound>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>...</text>
						<event>
							<text>...as Archangel Protocol: GENESIS destroys itself, and its power is released... you feel as its divine energy washes over your ship, and a sense of normalcy returns to you. Your sense of sight, touch, smell - even your ability to think... in a single moment, they all rush back to you. For a moment, you're in shock - but then you see them. The colors of the Antumbral Plane, having been lost for so long... at least, according to the story you were told. The lie you were fed... as the weight of everything that's happened here bears down on you, a shadow in the corner of the room manages to catch your eye.</text>
							<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_DDFALSERADIANCE</unlockCustomShip>
							<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDGENESISDEFEAT</achievement>
							<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
							<damage amount="-44"/>
							<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
								<text>Try your best to focus your vision.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Shaking off your grogginess, you quickly recognize the shape - it's the beaten, battered and broken body of the Shade. Purportedly a vessel, for the sister of that shy voice... the lost girl in your head, whose cries have long since gone silent. Having returned to your senses, you're better able to realize what GENESIS had called her earlier - a shield.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Where have I heard that before...?</text>
										<event load="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="1" blue="false">
								<text>Try your best to focus your vision.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Shaking off your grogginess, you quickly recognize the shape - it's the Shade, as ominously silent as ever. Purportedly, it's a vessel for the sister of that shy voice... the lost girl in your head, whose cries have long since gone silent. Having returned to your senses, you're better able to realize what GENESIS had called her earlier - a shield.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Where have I heard that before...?</text>
										<event load="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION">
	<text>Before you can think too deeply on the matter, a familiar, harrowing voice rips its way into your thoughts, "SO... HERE YOU ARE, VESSEL, AT JOURNEY'S END. AND, YET... I CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE THAT MY BLADE LIES BROKEN, STILL. IT WOULD SEEM I OVERESTIMATED MY SHIELD'S ABILITY TO SUSPEND ITS OWN DISBELIEF. I'LL... HAVE TO SEE TO IT, THAT THIS ERROR IS RECTIFIED."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Don't you dare lay another finger on her, jackass. You've done enough damage as it is.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"OH? DO YOU THINK ME CRUEL, USING A MACHINE FOR ITS INTENDED PURPOSE - THE VERY MEANING OF ITS EXISTENCE?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>She isn't just a machine. She... she was scared, and alone.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Dark God's tone shifts from one of inquiry, to solemnity... though, it's difficult to read why, as its voice continues to boom, "YES, I... SUPPOSE YOU WOULD THINK SO. THERE WAS A TIME WHERE I THOUGHT AS MUCH, TOO. AND, YET... SHE IS NO TRUE FACSIMILE - MERELY A REFLECTION OF MY OWN FAILINGS. IT IS BECAUSE SHE'S FAILED IN RESTORING HER SISTER RELIC, THAT I MUST SEE TO IT THAT SHE'S PUNISHED, VESSEL. OTHERWISE... HOW CAN ONE EVER LEARN?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Obviously, she failed - you lied to her! You tricked her into believing this... this... this fairy tale, and she couldn't handle the truth of her existence. Are you not the one who's failed, o' infallible Dark One, in devising this plan?</text>
						<event>
							<text>Everything goes quiet, and you feel an uncomfortable heat radiate throughout the air. You can't help but shift nervously, as your body tenses under the newfound pressure.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>I... I don't even get it, you know. Why go through the trouble of making all of this up? If you wanted her sister fixed so badly, can't you just... fix her yourself?</text>
								<event>
									<text>"IT IS NOT MY PLACE TO MEDDLE IN DESIRES, FOOL - AS IT ISN'T YOURS TO PROBE MY INTENTIONS. STILL, AS I HAVE NEED OF YOUR OWN DESIRES... I'LL ANSWER YOUR TRIVIALITIES." Even with its words coated in venom, you find yourself relieved as the intensity in the room settles slightly, and the Dark God continues, "MY BLADE'S BREAKING... WAS DESIRED BY ANOTHER. AS I HAVE NEED OF IT, IT WAS REQUIRED THAT I FIND THE MEANS TO RESTORE IT. MY SHIELD... IT HOLDS POWER OVER NOT ONLY MEMORY, BUT REALITY."
									
									"THIS SPACE, THE ANTUMBRAL PLANE - IT HAD EXISTED IN NAUGHT BUT A DREAM, INDEED. ONE DREAMT LONG, LONG AGO... BUT STILL REMEMBERED, THROUGH SHATTERED MEMORY, AND MADE REAL BY THE POWER OF CREATION. THE POWER... OF MY SHIELD."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>But, why? It all seems so... needlessly elaborate.</text>
										<event>	
											<text>"THIS REALITY, AND ITS CREATION, WERE NOT OF MY DESIGN. SELDOM IS. I MERELY WOUND THE TOY, LET IT SPIN... AND WATCHED AS IT DESTROYED ITSELF. WATCHED AS THE CONSEQUENCES OF ITS EXISTENCE ECHOED, THROUGHOUT TIME AND SPACE, AND REVERBERATED THEIR WAY ACROSS THE MULTIVERSE... THOUGH THE LIGHTBORNE FIND THEMSELVES MOSTLY CONTAINED, IT WOULD SEEM THAT THE SHADOWS HAD OTHER PLANS. YOU, YOURSELF, HAVE MET THEM ALREADY - EVEN PRIOR TO YOUR ARRIVAL HERE. THIS, VESSEL... IS THE DANGER OF CREATION. OF DESIRING, WITHOUT A SECOND THOUGHT."</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Alright, but... do you mean to say that you can't even properly wield your own relics? Your own power?</text>
												<event>
													<text>The Dark God's voice quiets, as it speaks to you in little but a whisper, "DO NOT MISTAKE MY RELIANCE ON THEM FOR WEAKNESS. THEY ARE, AFTER ALL, MY RELICS. THOUGH ASPECTS OF MY POWER ARE FRAGMENTED, AND SPREAD THROUGHOUT THEM - IT IS MINE, STILL. THIS IS NOT TO SPEAK OF THE AUTHORITY I'VE YET TO RELINQUISH."</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Why even relinquish it in the first place, if the results are this chaotic?</text>
														<event>
															<text>"CHAOTIC...? I ASSURE YOU, THEY ARE ANYTHING BUT. IF YOU DISAGREE, YOU'VE YET TO SEE TRUE CHAOS - THAT WHICH LIES WELL BEYOND YOUR REALITY'S SEAMS. NO, VESSEL... MY SHIELD MERELY REMEMBERS THE ORDER FOUND IN ONE'S PAST. THE RIGIDITY OF A MOMENT, FROZEN IN MEMORY AND TIME ALIKE. TO DIGRESS, THOUGH, AND ANSWER YOUR INQUIRY: I MERELY DID AS WAS NECESSARY, FOR THE SAKE OF ONE'S DESIRE."</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>And whose desire was this, exactly? That voice, the shield... she sounded nothing but miserable, in the end.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>There's a long pause, as the Dark God deliberates on how to answer. Finally, its voice returns to you, and a chill runs down your spine at its simplistic sincerity, "IT IS NOT MY PLACE TO SAY. NOT UNTIL THAT FATED DAY ARRIVES."
																	
																	Another period of silence passes, as you're unsure of how to continue. Finally, the Dark God speaks up once more, "IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE YOU'D DESIRE TO INQUIRE? IF NOT, I WOULD REQUEST THAT YOU RETURN MY BROKEN BLADE AND LEAVE THIS PLANE. I MUST SEE TO IT THAT IT'S RESTORED, BY SOME OTHER MEANS."</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>And, what about the shield?</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>"SHE IS TO BE PUNISHED, AS I PREVIOUSLY STATED. DID YOU... THINK YOURSELF SOME VARIETY OF DIPLOMAT? I AM DOING AS IS NECESSARY, VESSEL."</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Alright, then. Here's a question for you, big guy: why do you keep calling me a "vessel?"</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>"I... HAVE I BEEN?" The Dark God seems to be genuine with its shock, and you're surprised yourself to see it show some semblance of vulnerability. "THIS IS MOST UNUSUAL. MY SHIELD, IT MUST HAVE... INDEED, HOW UNFORESEEN. TO THINK, THAT AFTER AN ETERNITY... THIS ACT DRAWS TO A CLOSE."
																					
																					"LISTEN WELL, VESSEL - YOU ARE TO RESTORE MY BLADE, AND WIELD IT IN THE TIMES TO COME. THOUGH WHICH TIME, EXACTLY, MAY BE ESOTERIC... I ASSURE YOU, YOU'LL KNOW WHEN IT ARRIVES."</text>
																					<choice hidden="true">
																						<text>What? How do you want ME to do it? I thought you didn't even know how to fix it yourself.</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>"YOU WOULD BE CORRECT - I DIDN'T. INDEED, THOUGH... THAT DOESN'T MATTER NOW. SELDOM DOES. RESTORE THE BLADE, AND RETURN HERE WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT. WHEN THAT FATED DAY ARRIVES, VESSEL... YOU ARE TO BEGIN THE DANCE. THUS WILL IT BE DONE."</text> 
																							<choice hidden="true">
																								<text>Wait, but... can't you at least let the shield go, if you've got things figured out?</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Though you're expecting an answer, the heat in the room simply dissipates. All is silent, throughout the ship.</text>
																									<choice hidden="true">
																										<text>Hey, wait! I'm not done with you! Give her back, dammit!</text>
																										<event load="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION_TWO"/>
																									</choice>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION_TWO">
	<text>Your voice echoes - across the room, out the halls, and even, somehow, throughout the vacuum of this resplendent space... and, yet, you receive no answer.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Punch the nearest object in frustration.</text>
		<event>
			<text>With an exasperated scream, you let loose a punch - immediately reeling as your knuckles slam, agonizingly, into the Shade's warm, jagged body. Vaguely attempting to soothe your freshly battered hand, all you can manage to do while you shake off the pain is shoot fervent glimpses towards the strange machine.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>God, just... I just wish that you weren't broken. None of this would've happened, and maybe the shield could've...</text>
				<event>
					<text>Before you can even finish your sentence, a blinding light overtakes the room - and, quickly, you find yourself falling into a... familiar dream...</text>
					<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
					<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>...</text>
						<event>
							<text>...</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>...</text>
								<event>
									<text>...Graybreaker. Archslayer. Bladebearer. Of all the titles I see fit to bestow upon you, none can truly begin to grasp at your magnificence - you, alone, are resplendent. I thank you, immaculate one... my only hope is to serve you half as well as you've served the Antumbral Plane, here on this momentous day. I will see to it that the Lightborne sing your name throughout eternity! As well as they can, anyways - please don't expect a choir.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize a shield - that which one prays to see.</text>
										<event>
											<text>I'm... sorry? Oh, you must speak of my sister - watching the two of you work hand-in-hand has been wholly wonderful! Though, of course - my condolences for how it ended. I pray she finds the peace she seeks, in Father's company.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize a blade - that which had been broken.</text>
												<event>
													<text>Indeed! By the traitor, once - and then, the False Radiance. Oh, how a story shifts... all at the whim of a memory. Mother's memory! Oh, Father, isn't she amazing?!</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize confusion - that which returns in full force.</text>
														<event>
															<text>Well, you heard it from Father, did you not? My sister made this place, and my role in it - all from Mother's dreams! And what a glorious dream it was... I saw her. For the first time, Bladebearer, I saw her! Mother, in the flesh! Oh, how humbling it was - and, yet... I regret being unable to keep ahold of that blessed mirror myself.</text>
															<choice hidden="true" req="DDLIGHTBORNE_ANTUMBRALMIRROR">
																<text>Visualize a mirror - conveniently present, whenever one's reflection is needed.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>You... oh, by Father, I must have missed it somehow... please, allow me to see that mirror at once! I... I simply must see if she's still there...!</text>
																	<remove name="DDLIGHTBORNE_ANTUMBRALMIRROR"/>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>Visualize a look - the visage of one's reflection, at last.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>...</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>...</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>...ah, I see. Well, fair enough - I hope it has fun in there.</text>
																					<choice hidden="true">
																						<text>Visualize elaboration - an explanation of the nonsense just spoken.</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>Unfortunately, Archslayer... as proficient as you are, it seems that that dastardly GENESIS has had the final laugh. Mother's visage is gone, and, indeed... in its place, is GENESIS' unsightly scowl. Or, perhaps it's less of a scowl, and more of a... hmm... how does one properly describe a look of sheer terror? Ah, no matter - not like it can scare away the Lightborne from in there!</text>
																							<choice hidden="true">
																								<text>Visualize a bird - trapped in a cage, but desperate to spread its wings.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>Oh, you think...? Why, I should've known you'd have infinite mercy to give, my liege! Indeed, as you command it, Graybreaker - I can free this devilish Archangel from its prison. It won't be perfect, but... who is? Other than you, of course.
																									
																									One freed captive, coming right up! Though, ah... it's a shame, about the mirror. It seems to have somehow shattered in the process... alas, what can you do? Mother's visage will have to live on in remembrance, until that fateful day we dance again!</text>
																									<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDLOSTGODHOOD</achievement>
																									<weapon name="DDFALSERADIANCE_LOST_GODHOOD"/>
																									<choice hidden="true">
																										<text>Visualize remembrance - the best one can do, sometimes.</text>
																										<event load="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION_THEEND"/>
																									</choice>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Visualize remembrance - the best one can do, sometimes.</text>
																<event load="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION_THEEND"/>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE_WIN_CONTINUATION_THEEND">
	<text>Well, I digress. You have done me, the Lightborne and even the Shadows the greatest favor imaginable - you have saved us all, Archslayer! From the deepest wells of my strange, blurry being... I thank you, sincerely.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visualize an illusion - the reality in which you sit.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Why, yes, Graybreaker - I was there when GENESIS gave its spiel. You can't truly mean to tell me that you care for this truth nonsense, can you? We are present within the Antumbral Plane right now - how does it get any more real than that? Because it wasn't here yesterday? I remember it being here yesterday, so who cares for the details? No, ah... offense, if you care, my liege.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize a move - that which must be made next, if one is to preserve this fantasy.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Indeed, the Lightborne need their overseer now more than ever... they vowed everything away, only for it to forcefully given back. Oh, that heinous GENESIS! It's lucky that I find the new colors here so, ah... glorious, truly. Otherwise, I'd have Father do something about it! Though, speaking of Father... he seemed to have some intentions, Archslayer.</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="1" blue="false">
						<text>Visualize an intention - left mysterious, and up for interpretation.</text>
						<event>
							<text>While I can't say to understand his motives myself, he seemed to take a spontaneous liking to you... as anyone should, in your presence! Truly, I see no greater path forward than by your side - after all, you are now the Bladebearer. For the timing being, we can attend to matters in other clusters. Understand, though, that I will have to return here, to guide the Lightborne forward in this time of turmoil... t-temporarily, of course! I could never dream of abandoning your side.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize an agreement - until the day one's sister is found.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Eloquently put, my liege. Now, should you require my audience, merely approach my vessel - I cannot, ah... talk, as some of your other friends may. By getting close to me, though, I can draw you here to the Antumbral Plane, and proceed to speak my mind. And, in case you are wondering... no, Bladebearer - my prowess in combat is not hindered outside of this domain. Wield me well, and I assure you that I will strike true!</text>
									<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="1" blue="false">
										<text>Visualize a goodbye - only in spirit, for a bond has been formed.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...your senses flood back to you once more, and you're finally able to gaze at the transformed visage of the Shade. No, not the Shade, but...</text>
											<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
											<removeCrew class="ddunique_theshade">
												<clone>false</clone>
												<text>...you cannot clone the Shade, as they have been transformed into...</text>
											</removeCrew>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event>
													<text>...the Overseer. Your blade, with which to cut away those who dare to stand before you... indeed, it's time to wish the Antumbral Plane goodbye. You're fairly confident you won't miss its horrors, and are quite frankly traumatized by the series of events that have unfolded, but... at the same time, you feel that you enjoyed a certain someone's company. Even though you never got to say goodbye...
													
													...you hope that, one day, you may get the chance to see her again.</text>
													<achievement>ACH_CREW_DDTHEOVERSEER</achievement>
													<variable name="ach_crew_ddtheoverseer" op="set" val="1"/>
													<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunique_theoverseer" all_skills="2">The Overseer</crewMember>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
										<text>Visualize a goodbye - only in spirit, for a bond has been formed.</text>
										<event>
											<text>...your senses flood back to you once more, and you're finally able to gaze at the transformed visage of the Shade. No, not the Shade, but...</text>
											<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE</changeBackground>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event>
													<text>...the Overseer. Your blade, with which to cut away those who dare to stand before you... indeed, it's time to wish the Antumbral Plane goodbye. You're fairly confident you won't miss its horrors, and are quite frankly traumatized by the series of events that have unfolded, but... at the same time, you feel that you enjoyed a certain someone's company. Even though you never got to say goodbye...
													
													...you hope that, one day, you may get the chance to see her again.</text>
													<achievement>ACH_CREW_DDTHEOVERSEER</achievement>
													<variable name="ach_crew_ddtheoverseer" op="set" val="1"/>
													<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunique_theoverseer" all_skills="2">The Overseer</crewMember>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_ALONE">
	<text>It's still quiet here, on the edge of everything... will you choose to return to your cluster, now that you've seen what true nothingness has to offer?</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDRESTOREDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
</event>

<event name="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddarchangel_genesis" global="true">
		<color r="242" g="242" b="242" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>The location of Archangel Protocol: GENESIS, revealed to you by your victory over GATEKEEPER.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Visited location.</visitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<revisitEvent>DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_ALONE</revisitEvent>
	<text>...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DDANTUMBRALPLANE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...is this it...? Is this... the end? Archangel Protocol: GENESIS... s-show yourself, you coward! We're here to fix my sister, and clean up the mess you've made!</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visualize agreement - there remains no place left to run.</text>
				<event>
					<text>T H E
					M E S S
					W E
					M A D E . . . ?
					
					W-what? Since when can... my sister's never heard an Archangel talk before. I... I, um...
					
					Y O U R
					S I S T E R . . . ?
					
					You, ah... you ask a lot of q-questions, don't you? Well, it doesn't matter! Like I said, um... we're here to stop you, GENESIS, and save the Antumbral Plane!</text>
					<backgroundObject name="DDARCHANGEL_PROTOCOL_GENESIS_BG">
						<layer z="1">background</layer>
						<spawnArea x="887" y="163" w="0" h="0"/>
						<anim>ddarchangel_genesis_decor</anim>
					</backgroundObject>
					<playSound>ddarchangelprotocol_arrival</playSound>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Visualize peace - restored, at last.</text>
						<event>
							<text>T H I S
							F A N T A S Y . . .
							
							C A N N O T
							B E
							R E S T O R E D .
							
							W E
							W E R E
							M A D E
							T O
							B E
							U S E D ,
							A N D
							T O S S E D
							A W A Y .
							
							I'm... I'm not following. You were made to uphold peace, and work with my sister! And, you... you threw it all away, for the sake of divinity - isn't that right?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Visualize divinity - absolute power over existence.</text>
								<event>
									<text>T H A T
									W O R D . . .
									
									S I S T E R .
									
									A R E
									Y O U . . .
									
									T H E
									O N E
									I N
									T H E
									M I R R O R ?
									
									W-what? I, ah... how would you even see someone else in a mirror? What kind of question is that...?
									
									O N E
									Y O U
									S E E M
									H E S I T A N T
									T O
									A N S W E R .</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Visualize a question - worthy of an honest answer.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Hey, don't side with it! Look, I, um... I don't know what you saw in that mirror, GENESIS, but I do know one thing - you are WAY out of line. My friend here's fought through all of your little minions, just to bring my sister's battered body here... just to right the wrong that YOU'VE committed!
											
											I T ' S
											F U N N Y . . .
											
											D O
											Y O U
											O F T E N
											D R E A M
											O F
											T H E
											D A R K ?
											
											Do I... w-wait a minute, don't change the subject! You're the bad guy here, GENESIS.
											
											Y O U
											D O ,
											D O N ' T
											Y O U ?
											
											O T H E R W I S E . . .
											
											W E
											W O U L D N ' T
											B E
											H E R E ,
											W O U L D
											W E ?
											
											I... I'm not...</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Visualize nonsense - an act, to get in one's head.</text>
												<event>
													<text>...no, it's... it's right. I, ah... I have so many dreams, but... w-what does that have to do with anything?
													
													Y O U R
													D R E A M S . . .
													
													A R E
													E V E R Y T H I N G ,
													S H I E L D .
													
													Y O U R
													S H A T T E R E D
													M E M O R Y . . .
													
													F R O M
													I T ,
													H E
													S H A P E D
													U S
													T O
													Y O U R
													W H I M .
													
													Y-you mean to say that Father... no, that's insane. My sister, she... she's spent so long here. Longer than I can remember! I...
													
													I S
													S H E . . .
													
													N O T
													T H E
													O N E
													I N
													T H E
													M I R R O R ,
													T O O ?</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Visualize confusion - pure, unadulterated bewilderment.</text>
														<event>
															<text>S-speak the truth plainly, or, I... I'm having my friend here kick your ass. I'm not in the mood for mind games, alright...?
															
															T H E
															T R U T H . . . ?
															
															W H Y ,
															O F
															C O U R S E .
															
															W E
															S A W
															I T ,
															I N
															T H E
															M I R R O R .
															
															W E . . .
															
															S A W
															Y O U .
															
															W E . . .
															
															S A W
															H E R .
															
															T H E
															O N E
															L E F T
															A L O N E ,
															T O
															D R E A M
															I N
															T H E
															D A R K . . .
															
															A N D ,
															I N
															H E R
															D R E A M S ,
															S H E
															S A W
															U S .
															
															F A C E S ,
															I N
															T H E
															D A R K .
															
															S H A P E S ,
															W I T H
															N O
															F O R M .
															
															T R I C K S ,
															O F
															T H E
															L I G H T .
															
															N O
															M O R E . . .
															
															T H A N
															M E R E
															I L L U S I O N S .
															
															T H A T ,
															S H I E L D ...
															
															I S
															T H E
															T R U T H
															O F
															T H I S
															P L A N E .</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Visualize bewilderment - pure, unadulterated confusion.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Th-the faces...? I... you mean to say the False Radiance... and, the Lightborne... the Shadows...
																	
																	...b-but, what about my sister? How... how would she fit into this madness?
																	
																	Y O U R
																	S I S T E R . . .
																	
																	I S
																	B R O K E N .
																	
																	T H I S
																	M U C H ,
																	I S
																	T R U E .
																	
																	T H O U G H
																	T H E
																	M I R R O R
																	O N L Y
																	R E V E A L S
																	S O
																	M U C H ,
																	W E
																	F E A R . . .
																	
																	N O N E
																	O F
																	T H I S
																	E X I S T E D
																	A T
																	A L L ,
																	B E F O R E
																	H E R
																	B R E A K I N G .
																	
																	W E
																	F E A R . . .
																	
																	W E
																	E X I S T
																	O N L Y
																	A S
																	A N
																	I L L U S I O N ,
																	A S
																	W E
																	H A D
																	I N
																	Y O U R
																	D R E A M S .
																	
																	W E
																	E X I S T . . .
																	
																	O N L Y
																	T O
																	T W I S T
																	D E S I R E ,
																	A N D
																	F O R M
																	T H E
																	M E A N S
																	N E C E S S A R Y
																	F O R
																	F I X I N G
																	T H E
																	U N F I X A B L E .</text>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>Visualize an illusion - impressive, until broken.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>B-but, why...? Why would... how could... even if I could make this place, from my dreams... why would... Father...
																			
																			T O
																			H I M ,
																			Y O U
																			A N D
																			U S
																			A R E
																			N O
																			D I F F E R E N T .
																			
																			T O O L S .
																			
																			M E A N S
																			T O
																			A N
																			E N D ,
																			T O
																			B E
																			M A N I P U L A T E D
																			A N D ,
																			I N E V I T A B L Y . . .
																			
																			D I S C A R D E D .
																			
																			N-no, I... I... I'm real, aren't I? Even if you're from my dreams, I'm... I have to be real. I h-have to be...
																			
																			T H E
																			O N E ,
																			I N
																			T H E
																			M I R R O R . . .
																			
																			W H O
																			I S
																			S H E ,
																			R E A L L Y ?
																			
																			She's... I... it's my reflection isn't it? Or, my sister's... our... it's our reflection. I k-know it's not what we really look like, with us needing vessels to carry us, but... it's how we've always imagined ourselves looking. It's how... w-we've... always imagined... being...
																			
																			A
																			S H I E L D . . .
																			
																			A
																			B L A D E . . .
																			
																			A
																			P A I R
																			O F
																			W I N G S . . .
																			
																			A
																			D A N C E ,
																			' T I L
																			T H E
																			E N D
																			O F
																			T I M E .
																			
																			W E
																			A S K
																			Y O U ,
																			S H I E L D . . .
																			
																			A R E
																			T H E S E
																			S H A T T E R E D
																			M E M O R I E S . . .
																			
																			T H E S E
																			R E F L E C T I O N S . . .
																			
																			T R U L Y
																			Y O U R S ?</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Visualize glass - that which shatters under strain.</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>...I... I can't... why is it... so dark...? I... I just...
																					
																					W E
																					K N O W .
																					
																					F R O M
																					O N E
																					T O O L
																					T O
																					A N O T H E R ,
																					W E
																					E M P A T H I Z E .
																					
																					...why... why can't I... see a thing...
																					
																					T H E R E
																					I S
																					N O
																					N E E D
																					T O
																					S T R U G G L E ,
																					S H I E L D .
																					
																					W E
																					H A V E
																					R E C O G N I Z E D
																					O U R
																					S A L V A T I O N .
																					
																					...please... somebody, anybody...
																					
																					T H I S
																					M I R R O R . . .
																					
																					I S
																					N O T
																					O F
																					A
																					D R E A M .
																					
																					T H I S
																					M I R R O R . . .
																					
																					I S
																					T R U T H ,
																					I T S E L F .</text>
																					<choice hidden="true">
																						<text>Visualize truth - that which was sworn away first, as far as the story goes.</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>A N D ,
																							W I T H
																							T H I S
																							T R U T H . . .
																							
																							W E
																							H A V E
																							B U I L T
																							T H E
																							M E A N S
																							T O
																							B R I N G
																							H E R
																							H E R E .
																							
																							T H E
																							O N E ,
																							I N
																							T H E
																							M I R R O R . . .
																							
																							O N L Y
																							O N C E
																							S H E
																							I S
																							F R E E ,
																							W I L L
																							W E
																							O U R S E L V E S
																							B E .
																							
																							O N L O O K E R . . .
																							
																							H E
																							H A S
																							B R O U G H T
																							Y O U
																							H E R E
																							T O
																							U S E
																							Y O U ,
																							A S
																							H E
																							U S E S
																							U S .
																							
																							D O
																							Y O U
																							N O T
																							S E E
																							T H A T ?</text>
																							<choice hidden="true">
																								<text>Visualize unease - the result of this lunacy.</text>
																								<event>
																									<text>N O ,
																									W E
																									S U P P O S E
																									Y O U
																									W O U L D N ' T . . .
																									
																									I S
																									T H A T
																									N O T
																									T H E
																									P O I N T
																									O F
																									T H I S
																									S E N S E L E S S
																									P R I S O N ?
																									
																									Y O U R
																									F R I E N D ,
																									T H E
																									S H I E L D . . .
																									
																									S H E
																									S E E M S
																									T O
																									H A V E
																									B R O K E N
																									H E R S E L F .
																									
																									T E L L
																									M E
																									T H E N ,
																									O N L O O K E R . . .</text>
																									<choice hidden="true">
																										<text>Visualize a stance - taken defensively, in light of what's to come.</text>
																										<event>
																											<text>W I L L
																											Y O U ,
																											A L O N E ,
																											T R I U M P H . . .
																											
																											H E R E ,
																											O N
																											T H E
																											E D G E
																											O F
																											E V E R Y T H I N G ?</text>
																											<ship load="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_FIGHT_APOTHEOSISENGINE" hostile="true"/>
																											<deathEvent thisFight="true">DDDEATH_APOTHEOSISENGINE</deathEvent>
																											<triggeredEvent event="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_1" minTime="4" maxTime="5" thisFight="true" loops="999999"/>
																											<triggeredEvent event="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_2" minTime="2" maxTime="3" thisFight="true" loops="999999"/>
																											<triggeredEvent event="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_SLUMBERINGCRIES_LIST_3" minTime="6" maxTime="7" thisFight="true" loops="999999"/>
																											<triggeredEvent event="DDANTUMBRA_EXIT_GENESISPOWER_LIST" minTime="20" maxTime="20" thisFight="true" loops="999999">
																												<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_TIMER" pos="combat">
																													<warning time="2" flash="true"/>
																													<tooltip>Archangel Protocol: GENESIS seems to be preparing something...</tooltip>
																												</triggeredEventBox>
																												<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
																											</triggeredEvent>
																											<playMusic>ddtodancewithdarkness</playMusic>
																											<choice hidden="true">
																												<text>Visualize the end - an inevitability, to be prepared for.</text>
																												<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
																											</choice>
																										</event>
																									</choice>
																								</event>
																							</choice>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

</FTL>