<FTL>

<ship name="SHIP_SHADOW_TENDRILS" auto_blueprint="DARKONE_SHADOW_TENDRILS">
	<destroyed load="SHADOW_TENDRILS_WIN"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="SHADOW_TENDRILS_FAIL" thisFight="true" clearOnJump="true" time="25.0">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_TIMER" pos="combat">
			<warning time="8.0" flash="true"/>
			<tooltip>With the shadows outside clawing at your hull, you have until this timer hits 0 to force them to retreat before you take any serious damage.</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
</ship>

<event name="SHADOW_TENDRILS_WIN">
	<text>You've temporarily forced the darkness to abate, but it'll be back. In the meantime, some fuel has materialized itself within your hold... the Dark God invites you forward. Keep running.</text>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
	</item_modify>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Run!</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SHADOW_TENDRILS_FAIL">
	<text>The darkness rips and tears at your hull, but you're able to free yourself from its grasp before you sustain truly heavy damage. In the meantime, some fuel has materialized itself within your hold... the Dark God invites you forward. Keep running.</text>
	<damage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<damage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<damage amount="2" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	<damage amount="1"/>
	<instantEscape/>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
	</item_modify>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION">
	<text>You feel as your chest burns, and your desire is made manifest... the opposing vessel is no more, and a gift has found its way into your hands. Such is the prize of devotion.</text>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
	<playSound>fire_blast</playSound>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_START_TRUESENDOFF">
	<text>For a moment, there's a welcome silence, and you take the time to bring yourself back to your feet. As you do so, the Dark God's voice returns, as threatening and booming as it had been originally, "I BELIEVE THIS CONVERSATION TO HAVE BEEN... FRUITFUL. ANSWERS, POWER, MYSTERY, BATTLE - WHATEVER IT IS THAT YOU DESIRE, MY EMBRACE SHALL PROVIDE; SHOULD YOU PROVE YOURSELF WORTHY OF THESE GIFTS."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Really? And... what is it that you desire? Why are you doing this?</text>
		<event>
			<text>There's another silence, and, this time, its voice does not return. Rather, you feel another crackle of energy as something inexplicable seems to repair your hull outside - simultaneously, what is 'outside' seems to shift... as the shadows around you begin to claw their way into your ship! It seems that your trial has begun.</text>
			<damage amount="-14"/>
			<ship load="SHIP_SHADOW_TENDRILS" hostile="true"/>
			<status type="limit" target="player" system="hacking" amount="0"/>
			<boarders min="2" max="3" class="darkgodtendrils"/>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_thescarred">
				<text>(The Scarred) "The False God... wishes that we waste time, and risk... our lives. I, kin... do not."</text>
				<event>
					<text>You watch as the Scarred puts a clawed hand over their still-good eye, and seems to draw from something within themself... indeed, without you even understanding what's happened, the darkness outside begins to writhe and squirm in abject pain. Opting to retreat deeper into this strange, lightless abyss, it lets go of its hold over your ship, and you're only left with the few shadows that had already managed to seep inside.</text>
					<enemyDamage amount="66"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Wait, you can do that?</text>
						<event>
							<text>They turn to you, the slightest hint of a smile overtaking their otherwise grim expression, "I... have been parting the darkness for you... all along, have I not? Personally, kin... I hold little interest in one-upping... the False God, but... I have even less, in playing its petty games. We should... keep moving."</text>
							<choice hidden="true" req="dd_kyrandlilith_darkgodlocation" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
								<text>Well, alright - nice one!</text>
								<event>
									<text>As you prepare to leave, one of your consoles begins to flash. It's Kyr and Lilith's signal... they must have made it after all! Who knows how long they'll be able to hold out, here in this hell, though - for all you know, it might already be too late. Even still, you're not one to lose out on hope... praying for the duo's safety, you move to disembark once more.</text>
									<quest event="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="dd_kyrandlilith_darkgodlocation" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
								<text>Well, alright - nice one!</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="dd_kyrandlilith_darkgodlocation" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
				<text>Prepare to defend yourself!</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you prepare for battle, one of your consoles begins to flash. It's Kyr and Lilith's signal... they must have made it after all! Who knows how long they'll be able to hold out, here in this hell, though - for all you know, it might already be too late. Even still, you're not one to lose out on hope... praying for the duo's safety, you move to get into position once more.</text>
					<quest event="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="dd_kyrandlilith_darkgodlocation" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
				<text>Prepare to defend yourself!</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_START_BADENDING_PAYOUT">
	<text>"AS YOU CAN SURMISE, YOUR ARRIVAL HERE WAS... ARRANGED. YOUR ALLY'S INSISTENCE ON DISTURBING THIS PROCESS PROVED TO BE THEIR DEMISE; THOUGH, I AM NOT WITHOUT MERCY. THERE WILL BE TRIALS AHEAD. YOU ARE TO BE TESTED. YET, I OFFER YOU A PAWN - A PIECE FOR YOU TO PLAY IN THIS GAME."
	
	The space in front you crackles with energy, before ultimately tearing apart. From the rift this disturbance creates, a Deep One crashes forward and into the ground, seemingly in as much pain as you are. You don't suppose they've been asked to join you politely, then...</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="DARKONE_START_TRUESENDOFF"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_START_WEIRDENDING_PAYOUT">
	<text>"AS YOU CAN SURMISE, YOUR ARRIVAL HERE WAS... ARRANGED. THE SPECIFICS, THOUGH CRUDELY PERFORMED, WERE ENACTED EXACTLY AS I HAD WILLED IT. YET, FROM MY FORCES... IT WAS REPORTED THAT YOUR MANPOWER WAS SUFFERING. NONEXISTENT, TO BE PARTICULAR. THERE WILL BE TRIALS AHEAD. YOU ARE TO BE TESTED. YET, I AM NOT WITHOUT MERCY. I OFFER YOU A PAWN - A PIECE FOR YOU TO PLAY IN THIS GAME."
	
	The space in front you crackles with energy, before ultimately tearing apart. From the rift this disturbance creates, a Deep One crashes forward and into the ground, seemingly in as much pain as you are. You don't suppose they've been asked to join you politely, then...</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="DARKONE_START_TRUESENDOFF"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_START_NEUTRALENDING_PAYOUT">
	<text>"AS YOU CAN SURMISE, YOUR ARRIVAL HERE WAS... ARRANGED. THOUGH YOUR DISCOVERY OF MY EMISSARY WAS LESS THAN CALCULATED, YOU'VE PROVEN CAPABLE OF STILL MAKING IT HERE MOSTLY-INTACT. THERE WILL BE TRIALS AHEAD. YOU ARE TO BE TESTED. YET, I AM NOT WITHOUT MERCY. I OFFER YOU REPARATIONS - MAY YOU SPEND THEM WISELY."
	
	The space in front you crackles with energy, before ultimately tearing apart. From the rift this disturbance creates, a collection of loot crashes forward and onto the ground. You're not sure how helpful this will be in the immediate future, but you're certainly not unappreciative of the gesture...</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="DARKONE_START_TRUESENDOFF"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_START_GOODENDING_PAYOUT">
	<text>"AS YOU CAN SURMISE, YOUR ARRIVAL HERE WAS... ARRANGED. THOUGH, I UNDERSTAND THAT IT TOOK LONGER THAN DESIRED... I AM AWARE OF THE VALUE TIME HAS TO BEINGS SUCH AS YOURSELF. THERE ARE TO BE TRIALS AHEAD. YOU ARE TO BE TESTED. YET, I AM NOT WITHOUT MERCY. I OFFER YOU THE TIME YOU DESPERATELY SEEK - DO WITH IT AS YOU WISH."
	
	The space around you crackles with energy, though you're not sure of its exact purpose. Regardless, it seems you and your ship have been blessed somehow...</text>
	<modifyPursuit amount="-3"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="DARKONE_START_TRUESENDOFF"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_START">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_start" global="false">
		<color r="46" g="252" b="51" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>Finally, your ship comes to a stop... where the hell are you? Your ship's consoles all flash red, on and off; alarms are blaring.</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD</changeBackground>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<playSound>lightspeed</playSound>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Gather your bearings.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Panicking won't do you any good, so you take a moment to calm down and figure out what's happening. Your Atlas reads that you've been pulled many times deeper into the void... this isn't Enlightened territory, anymore. There is hope, though; beacons dot the sector, and an exit lies among them.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>That's it, then! Make a break for that exit!</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you're concocting a plan of escape, the same voice you'd heard before returns, its overwhelming volume booming within your head once more, "IT IS TIME WE SPEAK. FLAIL, IF YOU WISH - IT MATTERS LITTLE."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Struggle, helplessly, against the voice as it roars amongst your thoughts.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You can feel your skull split further with each disembodied, echoing word that forces its way into your mind. Whatever this thing is, you don't feel as if it's speaking to you as much as it's speaking THROUGH you. Even still, you find the strength within yourself to grit your teeth, and mutter what little utterances you can...</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>What... are you? Where have you taken us? Why...?</text>
								<event>
									<text>There's a thunderous crack inside your head, and you're brought crashing to your knees. Venom, and annoyance, tinge the mysterious entity's words as it speaks further, "I KNOW YOU TO DESIRE TRUTH - ANSWERS. I OFFER THE MEANS WITH WHICH TO SEEK THEM. THOUGH, KNOW THIS: YOU ARE NOT THE FIRST TO THINK THEMSELVES ABOVE MY CHOSEN; ABOVE MY WORD."
									
									The voice puts an especially disdainful emphasis on that final word, and you realize what it said... its Chosen. This isn't just any voice, but one you've been warned of - the Dark God. Its demeanor shifts at your newfound clarity, and it sounds nothing but eerily calm as it continues, "NOR... WOULD YOU BE THE FIRST TO PERISH HERE AS A RESULT OF YOUR PRIDE. MANY SEEK ME OUT. YOU'VE HAD THE PLEASURE - OR, PERHAPS, DISPLEASURE - OF MEETING ONE SUCH INDIVIDUAL ALREADY."</text>
									<choice hidden="true" req="unique_thescarred">
										<text>(The Scarred) Do you mean... the Scarred?</text>
										<event>
											<text>Though you can't bring yourself to speak the words, their meaning seems to come across to the invader in your head regardless. It returns to its hateful, roaring tone, "THE TRAITOR. IT WAS TO BEAR EVERYTHING - BECOME EVERYTHING. IT THINKS ITSELF ABOVE ME NOW. EVEN STILL, IT WOULD SOONER COWER AMONGST THE SAME SHADOWS IT LOATHES THAN FACE ITS REPENTANCE; MY WRATH."
											
											Your mind sears with pain at the sheer power of the Dark God's vitriol, but you understand that the full force of its anger is directed elsewhere. Beside you, the Scarred is screaming; the space around themself distorting, and tearing, as they do everything in their power to resist the entity's punishment. After a while, its rage relents, and its attention returns to you with that same, calm demeanor it'd had earlier, "YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND... ARE STRONGER. IT KNOWS THIS, AND SEEKS TO EXPLOIT IT. I KNOW THIS AS WELL, AS THOROUGHLY AS I KNOW ALL THINGS, AND HAVE INVITED YOU INTO MY EMBRACE ACCORDINGLY."</text>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_badending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_BADENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_weirdending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_WEIRDENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_neutralending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_NEUTRALENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_goodending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_GOODENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="unique_thehunger">
										<text>(The Hunger) Do you mean... the Hunger?</text>
										<event>
											<text>Though you can't bring yourself to speak the words, their meaning seems to come across to the invader in your head regardless. It returns to its hateful, roaring tone, "THE LIBERATOR - OR, THE LIBERATED. THEIR COLLECTIVE TRAVELLED FAR TO MEET ME PERSONALLY. FARTHER THAN MOST, AS THEY WERE SPURRED ON BY A MOST EMPOWERING DESIRE - FOR THE MEANS TO OVERCOME THEIR CHAINS. THEY HAVE DONE AS I HAVE NEEDED, AND I HAVE PROVIDED THESE MEANS IN TURN."
											
											You feel your gaze directed somewhere, as you're forced against your will to stare upon the Hunger's ever-vibrating visage. For the first time, you feel terrified as you stare into its empty, clouded visor - you're not sure if that's because of a fear you have for it, or for the entity commanding your body to do as it pleases. Either way, this puppeting eventually ceases, and the Dark God returns to speaking to you with that same, calm demanor it'd had earlier, "YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND... ARE STRONGER STILL. THEY KNOW THIS, AND FIND THEMSELVES IN GOOD COMPANY. I KNOW THIS AS WELL, AS THOROUGHLY AS I KNOW ALL THINGS, AND HAVE INVITED YOU INTO MY EMBRACE ACCORDINGLY."</text>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_badending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_BADENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_weirdending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_WEIRDENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_neutralending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_NEUTRALENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_goodending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_GOODENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theaberration">
										<text>(The Foolish) Do you mean... the Foolish?</text>
										<event>
											<text>Though you can't bring yourself to speak the words, their meaning seems to come across to the invader in your head regardless. It returns to its hateful, roaring tone, "A MONIKER THAT HE HAS NOT TAKEN ON LIGHTLY. HE CAME TO ME SEEKING GIFTS, AND FOUND THEM IN ABUNDANCE. I ASKED FOR LITTLE IN RETURN, AND STILL DOES HE SEEK TO UNDERMINE ME; MY WILL."
											
											Your mind sears with pain at the sheer power of the Dark God's vitriol, but you understand that the full force of its anger is directed elsewhere. Beside you, the Foolish is screaming; Soulplague-infected matter oozing endlessly from every orifice within his shell as its exterior proves itself to be useless against the entity's unknowable torment. After a while, this torture relents, and the voice's attention returns to you with that same, calm demeanor it'd had earlier, "YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND... ARE STRONGER. HE KNOWS THIS, AND SEEKS TO EXPLOIT IT. I KNOW THIS AS WELL, AS THOROUGHLY AS I KNOW ALL THINGS, AND HAVE INVITED YOU INTO MY EMBRACE ACCORDINGLY."</text>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_badending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_BADENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_weirdending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_WEIRDENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_neutralending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_NEUTRALENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_goodending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_GOODENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theheroine">
										<text>(The Heroine) Do you mean... the Heroine?</text>
										<event>
											<text>Though you can't bring yourself to speak the words, their meaning seems to come across to the invader in your head regardless. It returns to its hateful, roaring tone, "YOU COULD NOT BE FURTHER FROM THE TRUTH. TO THIS ONE, I WOULD GIVE NOTHING - SAVE FOR AN EXCRUCIATING DEATH. TO SAY THAT YOU STAND BY HER INSOLENCE ONLY SERVES TO TEST MY PATIENCE."
											
											Your mind sears with pain at the sheer power of the Dark God's vitriol, but you understand that the full force of its anger is directed elsewhere. Beside you, the Heroine seems preoccupied; locked in battle with a seemingly endless army of tentacles. Each one rises from the ground, makes a strike, and finds its attack cut short by a swift turning of her spear. After a while, this charade ends, and the voice's attention returns to you with that same, calm demeanor it'd had earlier, "ONE DAY, I WILL HAVE HER HEAD. YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND... ARE STRONGER THAN EVEN HER. SHE KNOWS THIS, AND SEEKS TO EXPLOIT IT. I KNOW THIS AS WELL, AS THOROUGHLY AS I KNOW ALL THINGS, AND HAVE INVITED YOU INTO MY EMBRACE ACCORDINGLY."</text>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_badending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_BADENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_weirdending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_WEIRDENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_neutralending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_NEUTRALENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_goodending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_GOODENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
										<text>(The Minister) Do you mean... the Minister?</text>
										<event>
											<text>You're expecting a response, but your head is suddenly, and eerily, quiet. Looking over at the Minister, he seems puzzled by your display of pain on the floor, "Something the matter, Renegade? Is this your first time within the Tempest's domain, or are you simply feeling space-sick?" Vainly, you try to speak, but only manage to cough up blood in his general direction. Amused, he smirks, "It is all a bit overwhelming the first time, isn't it... oh, no matter. I'll fetch something for you to retch into."
											
											As he leaves the room, you feel the tension in the air return as the Dark God finally speaks with that same, calm demeanor it'd had earlier, "PAY THE OLD MAN LITTLE MIND. I HAVE NOTHING WITH WHICH TO TELL HIM. YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND... ARE STRONGER THAN HIM. HE KNOWS THIS, AND SEEKS TO EXPLOIT IT. I KNOW THIS AS WELL, AS THOROUGHLY AS I KNOW ALL THINGS, AND HAVE INVITED YOU INTO MY EMBRACE ACCORDINGLY."</text>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_badending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_BADENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_weirdending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_WEIRDENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_neutralending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_NEUTRALENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_goodending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_GOODENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>I'm... not sure that I have.</text>
										<event>
											<text>A series of sounds - akin to a powerful, hearty laugh, you realize - ring out within your head, forcing you to reel once more. "NO, PERHAPS NOT. TO GET THIS FAR, WITH NAUGHT BUT UNINITIATED COMPANY, THOUGH... PERHAPS YOU ARE STRONGER THAN EVEN I HAD CALCULATED. YOUR INVITATION HERE PROVES ITSELF WARRANTED."</text>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_badending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>My... invitation? Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_BADENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_weirdending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>My... invitation? Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_WEIRDENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_neutralending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>My... invitation? Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_NEUTRALENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="dd_enlightenedstart_goodending_reward" lvl="1" blue="false">
												<text>My... invitation? Then, back in the Deep One sector...</text>
												<event load="DARKONE_START_GOODENDING_PAYOUT"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Gather your bearings.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Panicking won't do you any good, so you take a moment to calm down and figure out what's happening. Your Atlas reads that you've been pulled many times deeper into the void... this isn't Enlightened territory, anymore. There is hope, though; beacons dot the sector, and an exit lies among them.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>That's it, then! Make a break for that exit!</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you're concocting a plan of escape, the same voice you'd heard before booms into your head, "IN MY EMBRACE, I WELCOME YOU. YET STILL DOES MY WILL FESTER. DESIRE INTERVENTION, AND IT WILL BE DONE." With that, you feel your burdens lifted... and then the shadows outside begin clawing at your ship! Make a run for the exit!</text>
					<damage amount="-14"/>
					<ship load="SHIP_SHADOW_TENDRILS" hostile="true"/>
					<status type="limit" target="player" system="hacking" amount="0"/>
					<boarders min="2" max="3" class="darkgodtendrils"/>
					<choice hidden="true" req="dd_kyrandlilith_darkgodlocation" lvl="1" blue="false" max_group="0">
						<text>Prepare to defend yourself!</text>
						<event>
							<text>As you prepare for battle, one of your consoles flashes. It's Kyr and Lilith's signal... they're here, too. You may be able to reach them yet.</text>
							<quest event="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="dd_kyrandlilith_darkgodlocation" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false" max_group="0">
						<text>Prepare to defend yourself!</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESCARREDKICKSASHADOWBLOBSASS">
	<enemyDamage amount="66"/>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_RUN">
	<text>The darkness here, too, ravages your hull. Run, or ward it off, before it gets to do any serious damage!</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<ship load="SHIP_SHADOW_TENDRILS" hostile="true"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="hacking" amount="0"/>
	<boarders min="3" max="6" class="darkgodtendrils"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="unique_thescarred">
		<text>(The Scarred) "Allow me... to part this darkness, too."</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESCARREDKICKSASHADOWBLOBSASS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Get ready!</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DARKNESSSHIP" auto_blueprint="DARKONE_SHADOW_TENDRILS_TRIALDUMMY">
	<destroyed load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DARKNESSSHIP_DEFEATED"/>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DARKNESSSHIP_DEFEATED">
	<text>With the darkness destroyed, there's no more energy for the obelisks to channel.</text>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_BEGINNER_SUCCESS">
	<text>The Dark Obelisk and its otherworldly spawn falls, and that laughter rings out once more, "A BURNING DESIRE INDEED. YOU'VE REWARDED ME, AND SO SHALL I REWARD YOU... PUSH FORWARD. YOUR CONVICTION WILL TAKE YOU FAR HERE." A prize for your efforts manifests beside you, and you prepare to venture further into the madness ahead.</text>
	<playMusic/>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
	<metaVariable name="juke_ddtrialbyire" op="set" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_BEGINNER">
	<text>Your desire is heard, and a wave of otherworldly energy roars out, "TO... SUCCEED? MAY IT BE TRUE." You don't feel that this was something you'd truly wish for, and yet you've wished for it anyways... another wave of energy overcomes you, and you understand that your trial has begun! You'll have to ponder the existence of free will another time.</text>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DARKNESSSHIP" hostile="true"/>
	<playMusic>ddtrialbyire</playMusic>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_BEGINNER_SUCCESS" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>A strange, twisted obelisk appears... it seems to be drawing on the power of the darkness outside. If you can destroy the darkness, the obelisk will be unable to channel anymore energy, but alternatively you can choose to just focus on destroying the obelisk. Destroying the darkness is not necessary to surpass the trial.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_INTERMEDIATE_SUCCESS">
	<text>The Dark Obelisks and their otherworldly spawn fall, and that laughter rings out once more, "A BURNING DESIRE INDEED. YOU'VE REWARDED ME, AND SO SHALL I REWARD YOU... PUSH FORWARD. YOUR CONVICTION WILL TAKE YOU FAR HERE." A prize for your efforts manifests beside you...</text>
	<playMusic/>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
	<metaVariable name="juke_ddtrialbyire" op="set" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...as does another. With your newfound gifts in tow, you prepare to venture further into the madness ahead.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_INTERMEDIATE">
	<text>Your desire is heard, and a wave of otherworldly energy roars out, "TO... SCREAM? MAY IT BE TRUE." You don't feel that this was something you'd truly wish for, and yet you've wished for it anyways... another wave of energy overcomes you, and you understand that your trial has begun! You'll have to ponder the existence of free will another time.</text>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DARKNESSSHIP" hostile="true"/>
	<playMusic>ddtrialbyire</playMusic>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_INTERMEDIATE_SECONDOBELISK" time="6" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_SMALL">
			<tooltip>Your trial is underway...</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>A strange, twisted obelisk appears... it seems to be drawing on the power of the darkness outside. If you can destroy the darkness, the obelisk will be unable to channel anymore energy, but alternatively you can choose to just focus on destroying the obelisk. Destroying the darkness is not necessary to surpass the trial.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_INTERMEDIATE_SECONDOBELISK">
	<text>Another wave of energy pulses, as your trial worsens...</text>
	<playSound>vanceShoot</playSound>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_INTERMEDIATE_SUCCESS" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and another obelisk appears.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT_SUCCESS">
	<text>The Dark Obelisks and their otherworldly spawn fall, and that laughter rings out once more, "A BURNING DESIRE INDEED. YOU'VE REWARDED ME, AND SO SHALL I REWARD YOU." A prize for your efforts manifests beside you...</text>
	<playMusic/>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
	<metaVariable name="juke_ddtrialbyire" op="set" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...as does another...</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>...as does a... Deep One Chosen?! You assume this to be be an invader and prepare to defend yourself, but, to your surprise, they begin to bow as you hear the voice again, "TO SERVE IS TO DESIRE BEING A PART OF SOMETHING GREATER. THIS ONE SERVES ME, AS YOU'VE SERVED MY AMUSEMENT; THUS DO I SERVE YOU. THUS DO THEY SERVE YOU." Silence falls, and you're left with the unsettling presence of your newfound companion... whose side is the Dark God on, really? Is this all just a game to them? You receive no answer, but the single, clear truth of the matter is that one of its most venerated warriors now sits among your ranks.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="dddeepone_chosen">Nervasdren</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT">
	<text>Your desire is heard, and a wave of otherworldly energy roars out, "TO... SUFFER? MAY IT BE TRUE." You don't feel that this was something you'd truly wish for, and yet you've wished for it anyways... another wave of energy overcomes you, and you understand that your trial has begun! You'll have to ponder the existence of free will another time.</text>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DARKNESSSHIP" hostile="true"/>
	<playMusic>ddtrialbyire</playMusic>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT_SECONDOBELISK" time="6" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_SMALL">
			<tooltip>Your trial is underway...</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>A strange, twisted obelisk appears... it seems to be drawing on the power of the darkness outside. If you can destroy the darkness, the obelisk will be unable to channel anymore energy, but alternatively you can choose to just focus on destroying the obelisk. Destroying the darkness is not necessary to surpass the trial.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT_SECONDOBELISK">
	<text>Another wave of energy pulses, as your trial worsens...</text>
	<playSound>vanceShoot</playSound>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT_THIRDOBELISK" time="6" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_SMALL">
			<tooltip>Your trial is underway...</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and another obelisk appears.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT_THIRDOBELISK">
	<text>Another wave of energy pulses, as your trial worsens...</text>
	<playSound>vanceShoot</playSound>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT_SUCCESS" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and another obelisk appears.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_SUCCESS">
	<text>The Dark Obelisks, their sea of spawn and even the Dark God's Chosen have all fallen... the air smells of blood and brimstone, and you feel exhausted.</text>
	<playMusic/>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
	<metaVariable name="juke_ddtrialbyire" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Gather yourself.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You pick yourself up, dusting off your knees, and an uproar of applause breaks out in your head. If you weren't so overwhelmed already, it'd give you a headache... it continues for a moment, before abruptly stopping as the voice speaks to you, "AN INSURMOUNTABLE DESIRE. INSURMOUNTABLE STRENGTH. INSURMOUNTABLE FORTITUDE. YOU ARE WORTHY TO SERVE, AND TO BE SERVED, MIGHTY ONE. KNOW MY FAVOR, MY POWER, MY CHOSEN AND PUSH FORWARD. YOUR FATE IS YOURS TO DECIDE." A crack of lightning roars out, as strange schematics appear in your systems, and a weapon of pure, chaotic energy manifests beside you...</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_DDDEEP_ONE_CHOSEN</unlockCustomShip>
			<weapon name="BOMB_DDOBELISK"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>...as does another prize...</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>...and another...</text>
							<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>...and yet another, in the form of one of the Dark God's Chosen. It seems you've truly earned its reverence.</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="dddeepone_chosen">Nervasdren</crewMember>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE">
	<text>Your desire is heard, and a wave of otherworldly energy roars out, "TO... SUCCUMB? MAY IT BE TRUE." You don't feel that this was something you'd truly wish for, and yet you've wished for it anyways... another wave of energy overcomes you, and you understand that your trial has begun! You'll have to ponder the existence of free will another time.</text>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DARKNESSSHIP" hostile="true"/>
	<playMusic>ddtrialbyire</playMusic>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_SECONDOBELISK" time="3" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_SMALL">
			<tooltip>Your trial is underway...</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>A strange, twisted obelisk appears... it seems to be drawing on the power of the darkness outside. If you can destroy the darkness, the obelisk will be unable to channel anymore energy, but alternatively you can choose to just focus on destroying the obelisk. Destroying the darkness is not necessary to surpass the trial.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_SECONDOBELISK">
	<text>Another wave of energy pulses, as your trial worsens...</text>
	<playSound>vanceShoot</playSound>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_THIRDOBELISK" time="3" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_SMALL">
			<tooltip>Your trial is underway...</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and another obelisk appears.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_THIRDOBELISK">
	<text>Another wave of energy pulses, as your trial worsens...</text>
	<playSound>vanceShoot</playSound>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_FOURTHOBELISK" time="3" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_SMALL">
			<tooltip>Your trial is underway...</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and another obelisk appears.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_FOURTHOBELISK">
	<text>Another wave of energy pulses, as your trial worsens...</text>
	<playSound>vanceShoot</playSound>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_CHOSENWAVE" time="3" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_SMALL">
			<tooltip>Your trial is underway...</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and another obelisk appears.</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="dddark_obelisk_enemy"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_CHOSENWAVE">
	<text>Another wave of energy, different from the rest, pulses as your trial reaches its climax...</text>
	<triggeredEvent event="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE_SUCCESS" thisFight="false" clearOnJump="true">
		<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="false"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...and the voice rings in your head, "IT IS MY DESIRE THAT YOU DIE HERE, AND THUS IS IT MY CHOSEN'S DESIRE AS WELL. PERSEVERE, AND YOU MAY STAND AMONG THEM." As Dark Obelisks radiate, lightning bolts strike and Deep One Chosen infiltrate your ship... you feel your desire to win burn within you. Free will is the ability to stand against odds deemed impossible, and take fate into your own hands.</text>
			<boarders min="3" max="3" class="dddeepone_chosen"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddtruemystery" global="true">
		<color r="211" g="47" b="47" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>There's an intensity in the air here. You've felt a similar feeling throughout your brief time in this domain, but seldom as strongly as you feel it now. Yet, there's nothing here, and even the darkness outside is still... you can't say why you felt compelled to come here.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hello?</text>
		<event>
			<text>You cry out, and everything around you quakes. YOU quake. As you struggle to stand, a voice calls back to you in your mind, "KNEEL." This one word brings you to your knees as pain surges throughout your body, and you're sent reeling. You feel as if your existence is at the mercy of existence itself.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>What... do... you want...?</text>
				<event>
					<text>Each word pains you further, and yet you feel compelled to force them out anyways. You don't feel that they're your words, or that they're reflective of your thoughts, and yet you feel as if you had no choice but to say them. There's a sound that plays in your head, reminiscent of laughter, again, as the voice returns, "THIS WAS TO BE ONE OF YOUR TRIALS, BUT... ADMITTEDLY, I'M ENJOYING YOUR SQUIRMING."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Fight the pain.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your being burns as you force yourself up, slowly but surely. Every one of your limbs feels as if they weigh impossibly heavily, and yet you're able to rise to your feet regardless. As you do so, there's that laughing again, "YES. SQUIRMING, STRUGGLING, STANDING... I AM KEEN TO SEE IT ALL. TELL ME. DO YOU DESIRE TO SUCCEED, SCREAM, SUFFER OR SUCCUMB?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
								<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
								<event>
									<text>The voice laughs, and laughs, and laughs, until it fades away and a gift finds its way into your hands. Such is the prize of devotion.</text>
									<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="dddeepone_chosen">
								<text>(Chosen Crew) "I DESIRE... PEACE, LORD."</text>
								<event>
									<text>An intense silence falls as your member of the Dark God's Chosen speaks, and the hatred in the air dissipates. Its request must have worked, as nothing further of note occurs at the beacon.</text>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>(Beginner Trial) I desire... to succeed.</text>
								<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_BEGINNER"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>(Intermediate Trial) I desire... to scream.</text>
								<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_INTERMEDIATE"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>(Difficult Trial) I desire... to suffer.</text>
								<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_DIFFICULT"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>(Impossible Trial) I desire... to succumb.</text>
								<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_TRIAL_IMPOSSIBLE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND">
	<text>Suddenly, your perspective is ripped away - back to that confusing cacophony of eldritch sights and sounds. At the end of each of these forsaken visions, lies a path... and at the end of each path, lies a single door at which they converge.
	
	The end of everything.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Focus on this vision of finality.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your vision shifts again, for the final time, as you bear witness to the end of all things...
			
			
			
			THOUGH ALL POSSIBILITIES REMAIN PROPHESIZED, ONE ROAD LIES AHEAD, AT THE END OF EVERY OTHER.
			
			IT IS THIS PATH THAT STANDS ABOVE THE DARK, AND REMAINS AN IMMUTABLE INEVITABILITY... THE PROPHECY.
			
			
			
			THREE SISTERS WILL BE REUNITED, BEYOND THE EDGE OF EVERYTHING.
			
			ONE BEARS THE STRENGTH OF ULTIMATE POWER - THE WINGS.
			
			ONE BEARS THE STRENGTH OF ANTUMBRAL SHADOW - THE BLADE.
			
			ONE BEARS THE STRENGTH OF SHATTERED MEMORY - THE SHIELD.
			
			IT IS THEN THAT THEIR FATHER WILL BEAR THEIR COMBINED STRENGTH, AND BRING FORTH THE FINAL DANCE.
			
			ALL THAT IT MEANS TO BE REAL - TO DESIRE... WILL BE TORN ASUNDER, AND REFORGED - IN A LONG-LOST DREAM'S IMAGE.
			
			
			
			THAT IS... UNLESS A NAME IS SPOKEN.
			
			SHOULD ONE SPEAK THIS NAME, AND BEAR THE THREE SISTERS' STRENGTH IN THEIR FATHER'S STEAD... SHOULD ITS PLOT BE THWARTED...
			
			THEN ALL WILL CRUMBLE, AND THERE WILL BE NO DANCE - NO ANYTHING, EVERMORE. EVERYTHING THAT IS, WILL CEASE TO BE...
			
			
			
			...thus will it be done.</text>
			<variable name="dd_prophecyoftheendwitnessed" op="set" val="1"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>...</text>
				<event>
					<text>There's a feeling of being pulled, as you're torn away from the pedestal - away from everything...
					
					...and, with a thud, you find yourself back aboard your ship. More specifically, on your back, against the floor. Had that all, just... been in your head?</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_DDTHEPROPHECY</achievement>
					<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD</changeBackground>
					<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
						<layer z="0">background</layer>
						<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
						<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
					</backgroundObject>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Dust yourself off, and look around.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Taking a moment to gather yourself, you're startled as a shadow in the corner of the room catches your eye - one of the Dark God's Chosen, merely standing there... watching you.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Ready your weapon, and ask the Deep One to explain themself.</text>
								<event>
									<text>The pale Deep One offers you a low, ominous laugh, before bowing its head and speaking, "THE DARK ONE... HAS RECEIVED WORD OF YOUR KNOWLEDGE. FEW... OUTSIDE OF ITS EMPLOY, KNOW OF THE PROPHECY... THIS MAKES YOU SPECIAL."
									
									They return to standing straight, and then put their cloaked hands together as they continue, "OUR MASTER... WISHES TO KEEP AN EYE ON YOU. THOUGH... IT WILL BE DONE REGARDLESS, CONSIDER MY PRESENCE... THE EASY ROUTE. A TOKEN OF... COMFORT."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>Before you can object, the Deep One bows once more, and then hurries to leave the room. If their words are true, and you'll be watched regardless, then you suppose there's little harm in having them aboard... at least, for now.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="dddeepone_chosen">Varagon</crewMember>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddtruemystery" global="true">
		<color r="211" g="47" b="47" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>There's an intensity in the air here. You've felt a similar feeling throughout your brief time in this domain, but seldom as strongly as you feel it now. Yet, there's nothing here, and even the darkness outside is still... you can't say why you felt compelled to come here.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hello?</text>
		<event>
			<text>Rather than receiving an answer, you feel as your muscles tense... and your vision begins to fade. You're being lulled into a deep, deep sleep...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Fight against this strange feeling.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It doesn't matter what you desire - not this time. Whatever's doing this is refusing to relent - indeed, you fall into that darkest slumber...</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>...</text>
						<event>
							<text>...and find yourself somewhere familiar, yet alien. You're not aboard your ship, or with any familiar company... you stand alone, atop a pillar. Looking down, its bottom seems to fades away into the unfathomable darkness below - you're unsure if this is meant to merely be a giant room, or, more impossibly, the darkest reaches of space. You feel comfortable enough, though.</text>
							<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
							<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Look around.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Within the center of the pillar is a pedestal, but little else. With nothing else to do, you approach it - the intensity in the air rising as you do so.
									
									Atop the pedestal is an engraving of a small, human handprint. You wouldn't reckon that your hand would fit within it, but...</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Place your hand atop the pedestal.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Immediately, visions cloud your mind - terrible, twisted sceneries, completely foreign to your psyche... each one individually threatening to shatter your very ability to think. Even still, you feel as if you may be able to focus on any one of these scenes of madness...</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of strange crystal - the one that tells of a divine war.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													THIS IS A BROKEN LAND, OF BROKEN PEOPLE, WITH BROKEN MINDS.
													
													EVEN STILL, THERE ARE THOSE WHO SEEK TO BREAK IT FURTHER - THOSE LUCKY FEW WHO HAVE BROKEN FREE OF BREAKING.
													
													THEY SEEK TO BREAK OTHERS FREE, TOO - THE UNFORTUNATE MANY WHO FIND THEMSELVES FORCED TO LIVE TOGETHER, IN HARMONIOUS DISSONANCE.
													
													SHOULD ONE SEEK TO HELP THEM, AMIDST THIS BROKEN LAND - OR, OTHERWISE PROVE TO BE THE ONE TO BREAK THEIR BROKEN RESOLVE...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of the impossible - the one clouded in a dark, harrowing red.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													THIS VERY SEA OF MADNESS, AMONGST THE EDGE OF REALITY...
													
													...CARRIES WITH IT TRIALS, PROPHECIES AND FORGOTTEN SHADES IN EQUAL MEASURE.
													
													AND YET, THOUGH ONE PARTICULAR TRIAL WOULD BE DEEMED IMPOSSIBLE... IT IS ANYTHING BUT.
													
													SHOULD ONE SEEK ITS CHALLENGE, AND PROVE THEMSELF CAPABLE OF OVERCOMING EVEN THAT WHICH CAN'T BE OVERCOME...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of voracity - the one within the belly of the beast.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													LITTLE MORE THAN A CAGE, BETWEEN THE FABRIC OF EVERYTHING.
													
													A PRISON, BUILT TO HOLD ITS MAKER - A PRISON, BUILT TO HOLD THE UNMAKER.
													
													ONE MAY FIND ITS ENTRANCE AMONGST THE SEA OF SHAMBLING DEAD - A QUIET PLACE, WHERE EVEN THE HOPELESS FIND HOPE.
													
													FROM THERE, IT IS HOPE THAT THEY MUST HOLD ONTO. SHOULD THEY KEEP IT FOR WHEN THEY NEED IT MOST, AND SHATTER THE PRISON'S HEART...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of a distant darkness - the one at the edge of the Multiverse.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													A REMNANT OF WHAT WAS - A SHADE OF ITS FORMER SELF.
													
													IT'S HARDLY DIFFERENT FROM THE LAND FROM WHICH IT HAILS - THAT DARK, DISTANT PLACE.
													
													AND YET, WITHIN THIS DARKNESS... IS THE PRESENCE OF AN UNHOLY LIGHT. THAT WHICH THREATENS THE UNMAKING OF EVERYTHING.
													
													SHOULD ONE BREACH REALITY'S SEAMS, AND STOP THIS TERRIBLE FORCE...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of forgotten memories - those tied to an ethereal power.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													THE DREAMER, AND THE SHARPSHOOTER.
													
													A DREAM, UNDREAMT - A SHOT, SHOT DOWN. THEY WOULD NEVER MEET AGAIN. AND, YET... 
													
													THROUGH HOPE, THEY BORE THREE SIGILS - AMONGST THE RESTLESS DEAD, THE DEEPEST DARK, AND THE LOOSEST PARCHMENT.
													
													SHOULD ONE GAZE UPON THEIR VISAGES, AND BASK IN THEIR RESTORED WARMTH...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of love - deep within a sea of madness.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													THE EXPLORER, AND HIS STARSTRUCK LOVER.
													
													SELDOM THE FOOL, HE KNOWS VERY WELL THE REALM HE INTENDS TO EXPLORE - THAT WHICH LIES WELL BEYOND THIS REALITY.
													
													AND, YET... THOUGH HE CANNOT GET THERE ALONE, HE MUST ARRIVE THERE AS SUCH.
													
													SHOULD ONE FIND THEIR SHIP BEFORE THEY SET OFF FROM DEEP SPACE, AND THEN AGAIN AFTER THEY PART...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of the occult - rituals of strange, wooden constructs.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													THAT DISTANT, FOGGY PLANE - ONCE THOUGHT LOST, BUT NOW RESTORED.
													
													IT IS FROM THIS LAND OF TREES THAT A SONG IS SUNG - ITS NOTES ECHOING THROUGHOUT THE MULTIVERSE.
													
													THOUGH ONE CAN'T SEE ITS BEAUTY, OR SMELL ITS ROSES... THEY MAY, RARELY, HEAR ITS SONG.
													
													SHOULD THEY LISTEN, AMIDST THE SEA OF SHADOWS, AND PROVE THE STRENGTH OF THEIR OWN MELODY...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Focus on the vision of hatred - an ire directed at armored friends.</text>
												<event>
													<text>You focus on this particular vision, and your perspective begins to shift...
													
													
													
													WITHIN THE SEA OF SHAMBLING DEAD, LIES A SHIP.
													
													THOUGH IT DOESN'T TRANSPORT GOODS, IT DOES DEAL IN SECRETS...
													
													ONE MUST FOLLOW ITS PATH OF MYSTERY, AND THEN ENTER THE BELLY OF THE BEAST.
													
													SHOULD THEY MAKE IT THROUGH, AND ENGAGE THEIR NEW, ARMORED FRIENDS IN CONVERSATION...
													
													
													
													...then they would surely be rewarded. Thus would it be done.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_PROPHECY_VISIONOFTHEEND"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESHADEMEETING_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="DDFALSE_RADIANCE_DWARFLING_MYSTERIOUS">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The mysterious, otherworldly ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESHADEMEETING_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESHADEMEETING_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>You realize that... not only has the strange wormhole closed since the ship's defeat, but that distant voice you'd heard earlier is gone, as well. The ship's origins, as well as everything else odd that's occurred here, seems to entirely remain a mystery...</text>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDSPACETIMESEAM_ANTUMBRAL"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theshade" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...including the cloaked figure who's joined you. With the threat of the glowing ship eliminated, it appears to have returned to a state of idle dormancy. Whatever it is, you feel slightly comforted by the fact that it's at least fighting beside you... perhaps, in time, you'll be able to get to the bottom of its secrets.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theshade" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>...including the cloaked figure, who seems to have been destroyed in the fight. Will you ever understand any of this, with it gone...?</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESHADEMEETING">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddtruemystery" global="true">
		<color r="211" g="47" b="47" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>There's an intensity in the air here. You've felt a similar feeling throughout your brief time in this domain, but seldom as strongly as you feel it now. Yet, there's nothing here, and even the darkness outside is still... you can't say why you felt compelled to come here.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Hello?</text>
		<event>
			<text>For a moment, there's only silence... that is, until you realize that it isn't silence at all - you can hear something. Is that... a voice? You're not sure where it's coming from, but it sounds like it's somewhere distant.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Be quiet, and try to listen out for the source of the sound.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Though you go quiet, your listening is quickly interrupted - as a wormhole opens up beside you!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Prepare yourself!</text>
						<event>
							<text>You get ready to defend yourself, as something crashes out of the newly sundered tear in space, and onto the floor. It's a large, cloaked figure - its dotted, metallic surface as dark as the strange space outside.
							
							You tense up, finger on your weapon's trigger, as you expect it to do something, but... instead, it merely continues to sit there, laid out against the floor.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Keep your weapon trained on the mysterious entity.</text>
								<event>
									<text>As you continue to be cautious, a glimmer of light outside catches your attention. It looks to be the forming of a second wormhole, much larger than the first... though, something about it strikes you as unusual. Before you can figure out what, though, an immense object begins to move through it...</text>
									<backgroundObject name="DDSPACETIMESEAM_ANTUMBRAL">
										<layer z="1">background</layer>
										<spawnArea x="787" y="163" w="0" h="0"/>
										<anim>ddspacetimeseam_antumbral_decor</anim>
									</backgroundObject>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>...which you vaguely recognize as a ship - though, you can't say you've ever seen anything like it. At its arrival, the figure before you suddenly begins to move! Its movements, while robotic, seem refined and purposeful - it gets onto its feet and into a battle stance in mere seconds. Its attention seems to be focused on the ship outside, though... as you realize it's making an aggressive advance towards your own!
											
											Whatever this entity is, it seems to be willing to stand with you against the strange ship.</text>
											<achievement>ACH_CREW_DDTHESHADE</achievement>
											<variable name="ach_crew_ddtheshade" op="set" val="1"/>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunique_theshade" all_skills="1">The Shade</crewMember>
											<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESHADEMEETING_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Call out to the sound.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Though you try to grab the attention of... whatever it is, your attempt is quickly interrupted - as a wormhole opens up beside you!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Prepare yourself!</text>
						<event>
							<text>You get ready to defend yourself, as something crashes out of the newly sundered tear in space, and onto the floor. It's a large, cloaked figure - its dotted, metallic surface as dark as the strange space outside.
							
							You tense up, finger on your weapon's trigger, as you expect it to do something, but... instead, it merely continues to sit there, laid out against the floor.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Keep your weapon trained on the mysterious entity.</text>
								<event>
									<text>As you continue to be cautious, a glimmer of light outside catches your attention. It looks to be the forming of a second wormhole, much larger than the first... though, something about it strikes you as unusual. Before you can figure out what, though, an immense object begins to move through it...</text>
									<backgroundObject name="DDSPACETIMESEAM_ANTUMBRAL">
										<layer z="1">background</layer>
										<spawnArea x="787" y="163" w="0" h="0"/>
										<anim>ddspacetimeseam_antumbral_decor</anim>
									</backgroundObject>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>...which you vaguely recognize as a ship - though, you can't say you've ever seen anything like it. At its arrival, the figure before you suddenly begins to move! Its movements, while robotic, seem refined and purposeful - it gets onto its feet and into a battle stance in mere seconds. Its attention seems to be focused on the ship outside, though... as you realize it's making an aggressive advance towards your own!
											
											Whatever this entity is, it seems to be willing to stand with you against the strange ship.</text>
											<achievement>ACH_CREW_DDTHESHADE</achievement>
											<variable name="ach_crew_ddtheshade" op="set" val="1"/>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunique_theshade" all_skills="1">The Shade</crewMember>
											<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_THESHADEMEETING_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHESHADEFORMS" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Hello?</text>
		<event>
			<text>But there's no answer. Indeed, it's as if the answer were with you all along... there's nothing for you here.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_TEXT">
	<text>A hatred in the air resonates as you realize its not just the darkness here that desires your destruction... from the depths of the madness outside rises yet another sleek, black ship of pure shadow. Get ready!</text>
	<text>It seems the Dark God's Chosen have yet to give up on their quest to destroy you, as another one of their ships breaks through the darkness and prepares to attack!</text>
	<text>Your blood runs cold as a ship appears outside... one you're now familiar with. An omen of death. Darkness, made manifest. The Dark God's Chosen... they make their advance, and you prepare to defend yourself.</text>
	<text>Things outside grow darker as you realize this isn't just any beacon... you've wandered into the territory of the Dark God's Chosen, and they've chosen you as their next tribute!</text>
</textList>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDCHOSEN">
	<destroyed load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
	<deadCrew load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>Despite felling a great foe here, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Before you do so, though, a weapon manifests beside you... you recognize it as being the same ones the Chosen wield. You're not one to pass up free gifts, but you're left to wonder as to the purpose of such generosity...</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_WEAPONS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_ENCOUNTER">
	<text load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_TEXT"/>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_CHOSEN_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dddeepone_chosen">
		<text>(Chosen Crew) "THIS ONE... WALKS AMONGST KIN."</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Chosen stop their advance as soon as they recognize that one of their own is standing with you. Without a word, they sink back into the darkness, and you're reminded that garnering the favor of evil deities has its perks...</text>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST">
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER"/>
	<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST"/>
</eventList>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_ENLIGHTENED">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>There's a burning feeling in your chest, and a reward for defeating these strange intruders manifests beside you. Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_WEAPONS"/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED">
	<text>...and grows darker still, as a wormhole opens up and an Enlightened ship appears from the ether. They may not know where they are, or what they're doing here, but they do know one thing: you're their next target!</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ENLIGHTENED_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DISPARITY_MIXED">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>There's a burning feeling in your chest, and a reward for defeating these strange intruders manifests beside you. Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<drone name="GIFTLIST_DARKGOD_DRONES"/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY">
	<text>...and glistens purple, as a wormhole opens up and a crystalline ship appears from the ether. They may not know where they are, or what they're doing here, but they do know one thing: you're their next target!</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDCRYSTALTALEVOID</changeBackground>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_DISPARITY_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDSOULPLAGUE_NORMAL">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>There's a burning feeling in your chest, and a reward for defeating these strange intruders manifests beside you. Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_WEAPONS"/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE">
	<text>...and gives way for a distant beacon of light, as a wormhole opens up and an iridescent, oily ship appears from the ether. They may not know where they are, or what they're doing here, but they do know one thing: you're their next target!</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDSOULPLAGUEHEART</changeBackground>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDSOULPLAGUEAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddsoulplagueaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_SOULPLAGUE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDILLDRYTHK">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK_FIGHT_WIN_BONUS"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>There's an awkward silence as the strange intruders crumble, and you feel that destruction wasn't the only option. Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK_FIGHT_WIN_BONUS">
	<text>There's a faint singing in your head as new life sprouts from one of the strange, fallen intruders... and a new one forms. You prepare for the worst, but it simply runs off into the corner as you blink... it it friendly, then? Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="ddilldrythk_statue"/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK">
	<text>...and a strange fog rolls in, as a wormhole opens up and a shaggy mass appears from the ether. They may not know where they are, or what they're doing here, but they do know one thing: you're their next target!</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDILLDRYTHKFOG</changeBackground>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_ILLDRYTHK_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDSOULPLAGUE_HUSKWEAVER">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER_FIGHT_WIN_BONUS"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>There's an awkward silence as the strange intruders melt, and you feel that murder wasn't the only option. Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER_FIGHT_WIN_BONUS">
	<text>The strange ship's whispering stills as what remains of it coalesces into a single form... one you recognize as a Soulplague Husk. It appears beside you, and you prepare for the worst, but it simply stands there, gurgling. Is it friendly, then? Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUERANDOM_SUMMON"/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER">
	<text>...and gives way for a distant beacon of light, as a wormhole opens up and an iridescent, oily ship appears from the ether. From the ship emanates faint whispers... they may not know where they are, or what they're doing here, but they do know one thing: you're their next target!</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDSOULPLAGUEHEART</changeBackground>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDSOULPLAGUEAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>ddsoulplagueaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_HUSKWEAVER_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_DDTEMPEST">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The ship breaks apart and you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST_FIGHT_WIN_BONUS"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>With the crew dead you quickly salvage what you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST_FIGHT_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>There's an awkward silence as the strange intruders fizzle out, and you feel that murder wasn't the only option. Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST_FIGHT_WIN_BONUS">
	<text>A bolt of lightning strikes out from what remains of the strange ship, and its energy coalesces beside you to form one of the strange entities you just fought. You prepare for the worst, but it simply stands there, glaring from beneath its cloak. Is it friendly, then? Even still, you recognize that you're losing ground in your race against the Rebels... and the darkness, for that matter. You'll need to push on.</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="ddtempest_spawn_warden"/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST">
	<text>...and a massive space-storm rolls in, as a wormhole opens up and a dark, painted appears from the ether. They may not know where they are, or what they're doing here, but they do know one thing: you're their next target!</text>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DDTEMPESTVOID</changeBackground>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
	<ship load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST_TEMPEST_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
		<text>I desire... intervention.</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_INTERVENTION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE">
	<text>A sharp pain stings your mind, as the insanity outside appears to shift...</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_WORMHOLE_LIST"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DDDARKGODDOMAIN_BLESSING">
	<text>You don't feel a malice in the air here... on the contrary, you feel warm. Soothed. Blessed, as your burdens are lifted... but which burden troubles you greatest?</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>I am burdened by my lack of hull integrity.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You close your eyes, and that warmth inside you blossoms into something greater. Something tangible. The damage to your ship is miraculously mended, and you feel optimistic about the journey ahead... this realm of madness will not claim you.</text>
			<damage amount="-12"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>I am burdened by my lack of crew.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You close your eyes, and that warmth inside you blossoms into something greater. Something tangible. A portal opens up beside you, and from it steps out a Deep One. They seem a bit confused, if not enthusiastic, "Is... this the Dark One's realm? Are... we near its greatness?" You nod, and they do a little jig, "Then... the ritual worked! I'm... to help you, I believe." The two of you exchange formalities, and the Deep One leaves the room, seemingly content with its place here. You feel optimistic about the journey ahead... this realm of madness will not claim you.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="deepone"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>I am burdened by my lack of resources.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You close your eyes, and that warmth inside you blossoms into something greater. Something tangible. A few crates of resources appears in your hold inexplicably, and you feel optimistic about the journey ahead... this realm of madness will not claim you.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="6" max="6"/>
				<item type="missiles" min="6" max="6"/>
				<item type="drones" min="6" max="6"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>I am burdened by my lack of power.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You close your eyes, and that warmth inside you blossoms into something greater. Something tangible. A portal opens up beside you, and out of it floats a lost, human soul...</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunstable_soul_spent"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>...and then another. Though their visages are ghastly, the potential power they radiate is undeniable. Comforting, even. You feel optimistic about the journey ahead... this realm of madness will not claim you.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="ddunstable_soul_spent"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT" auto_blueprint="KYR_AND_LILITH_HORROR">
	<destroyed load="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT_DESTROYEDLOSS"/>
	<deadCrew load="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT_WIN"/>
</ship>

<event name="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT_DESTROYEDLOSS">
	<text>The nightmare dissipates, but nothing is left... and Kyr and Lilith's FTL signature goes dead. You may never know what happened to your friends, but a bit of fuel manifests itself in your hold nonetheless. The Dark God must be laughing...</text>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
	</item_modify>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT_WIN">
	<text>With the abomination and its nightmarish horrors felled, a bit of fuel from the Dark God appears in your hold, and all goes quiet. Free to explore the ghastly ship, you're quickly able to find memorabilia belonging to Kyr and Lilith... photos of the two together, in particular. This must truly be their ship... but what of the two lovers?</text>
	<variable name="ach_boss_ddlilith" op="set" val="1"/>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
	</item_modify>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Keep exploring.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Holding onto the photo and looking further, you find a door you hadn't noticed before. Putting your hand against it, you feel a strange warmth... accompanied by a soft humming.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Open the mysterious door.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Gathering your courage, you open the door... and the sight before you is almost too horrific to describe. The room lies caked in gore: guts, blood and flesh completely strewn about as to make identifying its source impossible. Towards the opposite end of the room, candles burn softly around a pedestal, atop which lies an open book. Wading through the gore, you approach the book and notice that its pages contain text scrawled in a most vibrant crimson. Depictions of rituals, you realize...</text>
					<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_DDHORROR_SHIP</unlockCustomShip>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>So Kyr and Lilith...?</text>
						<event>
							<text>That... thing... must be Lilith. At least, what remains of her... that would mean the gore in this room, then...</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>I'm going to be sick...</text>
								<event>
									<text>Yes, this must be what remains of Kyr... just what in the hell were those two trying to do? You glance towards the book once more. If there's any way to get answers, this is it. Pocketing it, you turn to leave the room when you notice a hulking shadow in the doorway. The abomination stands there, having somehow healed from its wounds... the eye in its chest remains fixated on the photo of Kyr and Lilith in your hands.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>L-Lilith? Is that really you?</text>
										<event>
											<text>The abomination tenses up as you call Lilith's name. It must really be her... she begins to slowly approach, still fixated on the photo.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>It's me, Lilith. The Federation, remember?</text>
												<event>
													<text>Something flashes inside Lilith's eye. Recognition, you can only hope... her approach hastens ever so slightly.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Do you remember what Kyr said?</text>
														<event>
															<text>You mention Kyr, and Lilith hastens further. She'll be atop you in a moment.</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>He said you could trust me, Lilith, and I know I can trust you too. Stand your ground.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Mere inches away from you, Lilith stops. At lightning speed, a writhing tendril tears itself from her body and... grabs the photo. It seems to be capable of keeping her calm, slowly, and politely, you take the photo back, to which Lilith makes no move to stop you. As you leave the room and make for your ship, she follows, and you realize you've pacified an eldritch abomination... still, she's your friend, too. Once you're back on the ship, you take out the book, and Lilith reacts to its presence with a low growl.</text>
																	<crewMember amount="1" class="enlightened_horror">Lilith</crewMember>
																	<achievement>ACH_CREW_DDLILITH</achievement>
																	<choice hidden="true" req="DARKGOD_CURSED_BOOK" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
																		<text>Inspect the book.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>Flipping through its pages, you realize you can't read any of it. It's written in a script that none of your translators or crew recognize... save for Lilith, who stares at the crimson text with intensity. With a mysterious ink expelled from her body, she writes out a cipher on the floor at your request... you wonder just how much of her is still in there, if she's capable of such a thing. Eventually, with the cipher finished, you're able to recognize that the text does indeed depict several rituals... most notably, a ritual that allows one to ascend and convene with the Dark One. You glance at Lilith.</text>
																			<choice hidden="true">
																				<text>Did you...</text>
																				<event>
																					<text>She growls, and you gulp. Delving further into the book's pages, there's other colors of text, ones that Lilith's cipher doesn't cover. She must not be able to read all of them... maybe you can find someone who can. In the meantime, there appear to be a few rituals that increase the extent of one's power, given that they've already performed the ascension ritual. If you perform these rituals, you might be able to make Lilith stronger... who knows what price you might have to pay, though.</text>
																					<choice hidden="true">
																						<text>Kyr...</text>
																						<event>
																							<text>There's nothing you could have done. You'll have to move forward, and do what you can to take care of Lilith... as well as complete these otherworldly rituals, if you so desire.</text>
																							<metaVariable name="dd_otherworldlytome_permaunlocked" op="set" val="1"/>
																							<augment name="DARKGOD_CURSED_BOOK"/>
																						</event>
																					</choice>
																				</event>
																			</choice>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																	<choice hidden="true" req="DARKGOD_CURSED_BOOK" blue="false">
																		<text>Inspect the book.</text>
																		<event>
																			<text>You realize, rather quickly, that this book is identical to the Otherworldly Tome already within your possession. She and Kyr must've performed some unspeakable ritual contained within its pages, with him serving as its sacrifice... horrible, to say the least, but there's little of value to you in owning a second copy of the ghastly book. You leave it behind, and Lilith's ceaseless writhing seems to calm down ever so slightly.</text>
																			<metaVariable name="dd_otherworldlytome_permaunlocked" op="set" val="1"/>
																		</event>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Now! Sprint past the abomination and get out of here!</text>
																<event>
																	<text>As Lilith charges, you dodge past her, dropping both the book and the photograph. You don't know what has become of her, and you sure as hell don't trust such a nightmare with your life. As you make for the ship, you hear Lilith... sob, behind you. It's a disturbing, twisted sobbing. You can't let it phase you, though... you still need to get out of this hellish realm.</text>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave it, and get out of here.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You're not sure you want to know the truth of what happened here, or of what lies just beyond that door. Content on getting out of here, you prepare to continue your battle against the Dark God and its shadows.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<quest>
		<nebulaBeacon>false</nebulaBeacon>
		<aggressive>2</aggressive>
	</quest>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_ddkyrandlilith" global="true">
		<color r="129" g="37" b="37" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You're expecting to see Kyr and Lilith's ship, but instead you're met with... wait, no, this IS Kyr and Lilith's ship. At least, it's in the shape of it, but it's all twisted and enveloped in darkness... what's happened? You don't get a lot of time to think on it, as the nightmarish form of your friends' ship moves in to attack!</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
		<layer z="0">background</layer>
		<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
		<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
	</backgroundObject>
	<ship load="DARKONE_KYRANDLILITH_ENCOUNTER_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_ALONE">
	<text>You arrive at the exit of this dreadful journey once more... this time, will you take it?</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
</event>

<event name="DARKONE_FINISH">
	<revisitEvent>DARKONE_ALONE</revisitEvent>
	<text>Now that you're at the exit, the darkness seems... still. All feels calm.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_darkgodsdomainexitvisited" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though, this tranquility doesn't last long... you feel as the space around you warps, and time itself seems to slow again. Then, to your unease, the Dark God tears its way back into your mind, "TO COME THIS FAR IS MOST IMPRESSIVE. YOU STAND AT THE PRECIPICE; ESCAPE IS IN REACH. YET, BEFORE OUR TIME TOGETHER IS UP, I WILL GRANT YOU ONE LAST DESIRE. MAKE IT KNOWN."</text>
			<variable name="dd_darkgodsdomainexitvisited" op="set" val="1"/>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDDARKGOD</changeBackground>
			<backgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND">
				<layer z="0">background</layer>
				<spawnArea x="0" y="0" w="0" h="0"/>
				<anim>dddarkgodsdomainaura_bg</anim>
			</backgroundObject>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I desire... truth.</text>
				<event>
					<text>There's a hint of piqued interest as its deafening voice answers, "MOST... CURIOUS. AND WHAT TRUTH DO YOU DESIRE?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="darkone_alignment" lvl="1">
						<text>The truth... behind the hero I felled.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE HERO YOU FELLED... SURPRISED ME. LITTLE SURPRISES ME, AND I'VE YET TO CALCULATE HOW IT MANAGED TO SECEDE CONTROL OVER MY OWN POWER. ONE VARIABLE IS CERTAIN: SHEER DESIRE. TO OVERCOME THAT WHICH IT FELT NOBODY ELSE COULD. YOU AREN'T SO DIFFERENT IN THAT WAY; YET HERE YOU STAND, TRIUMPHANT..." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...THOUGH, I FEAR OTHER 'HEROES' REMAIN. SEEK THEM OUT, DEFEAT THEM, AND YOU WILL KNOW TRUE POWER."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="eldritch_cat">
						<text>(The One Who Rhymes) "Oh, how one would love the truth! But, what makes you the super-sleuth?"</text>
						<event>
							<text>An annoyance fills the air, as the Dark God retorts, "IT IS MY BUSINESS TO KNOW THINGS, BEAST - AS IT IS YOURS TO INCESSANTLY PESTER. AND, AS IT IS YOUR MASTER'S TO MEDDLE - SHE THINKS HER PLAN THE ONLY ONE." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "ALAS, THERE IS LITTLE 'BEING' IN CHAOS. TO DESIRE NOTHING, BUT MADNESS IN EVERYTHING... IS HARDLY A FRUITFUL EXISTENCE. EVEN STILL... IT IS A DESIRE NONETHELESS. THERE IS POWER THERE - WHICH I WILL WELCOME, COME THE DAY OF DANCING."
							
							The One Who Rhymes seems interested in its own rebuttal, when chains of darkness manifest around it - quickly serving to bind it to the ground. "AS POWERFUL AS YOUR KIND MAY BE, YOU ARE BUT A GUEST HERE IN MY DOMAIN. RESPECT THE ORDER OF THE OUTER CLUSTERS, AND I'LL CONTINUE TO RESPECT THEIR CHAOS AS WELL."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="gnome">
						<text>(Gnome) The truth... behind, uh... this thing.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THIS 'THING', AS YOU PUT IT... IS FROM THE OUTER EDGE." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "I HAVE MOVED MUCH BETWEEN THE SEAMS, AND SEEN MUCH MORE - BUT LITTLE AS TRULY CHAOTIC AS THIS. I IMAGINE... SHE'D BE BEHIND THIS. BE CAREFUL, VESSEL. EVEN I WOULD RECOMMEND THAT YOU TAKE CAUTION AROUND HER... AND IF NOT HER - THEN THE CENTER-DWELLERS. THEY WOULD NOT BE AS CALM AS I, SEEING THIS IN YOUR HANDS."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SYLVAN">
						<text>(Sylvan) The truth... behind Sylvan.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE CENTER-DWELLERS... THE SYLVANS OF EACH REALITY. OF THIS, YOU'RE LIKELY AWARE - EVEN IF YOU CAN'T REMEMBER. WHAT YOU MAY BE CURIOUS TO LEARN, THOUGH... IS THE TRUTH BEHIND THEIR TOLERANCE OF MY EXISTENCE HERE." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "IN EARNEST... I MERELY DO AS THEY DESIRE. THEY DON'T WISH TO SEE THE MEDDLING OF THE OUTER CLUSTERS, AND SO I SEE TO IT THAT THEY DON'T. AS SUCH, THEY REMAIN BLIND TO MY AFFAIRS... IN A WAY. THEIR LEADER THINKS THEMSELF ABOVE THE POWER OF BEINGS SUCH AS I, WITH AN OUTER BEING OF CHAOS VAGUELY UNDER THEIR CONTROL... BUT THE SYLVANS KNOW NOTHING OF THE ORDER THEY THINK THEMSELVES RESPONSIBLE FOR PERPETUATING. ALAS - THEY'LL ALL SEE WHAT ORDER TRULY MEANS, COME THE DAY OF DANCING."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_thescarred">
						<text>(The Scarred) The truth... behind the Scarred.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE TRAITOR... WAS A MISCALCULATION. I THOUGHT IT WORTHY OF BECOMING MY BLADE - IT PROVED ITSELF WORTHY OF NAUGHT BUT SHATTERING IT. NOW, BOTH IT AND MY BLADE LIE IN PIECES - WAITING FOR THE DAY THAT THEY'RE RESTORED, AND ABLE ENACT THEIR WILL ONCE MORE... OR FOR THE DAY THAT THEY WITHER AWAY INTO DUST, AND BECOME LITTLE BUT A FORGOTTEN MEMORY." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "I... WOULD SUGGEST KEEPING AN EYE ON IT, IF YOU INTEND TO KEEP IT. YOU'VE SEEN WHERE TRUSTING IT HAS LEFT ME."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_thehunger">
						<text>(The Hunger) The truth... behind the Hunger.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE HUNGER... WASN'T ALWAYS SO HUNGRY." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "NOR... WERE THEY ALL SO CONJOINED. A COLLECTIVE SO UNITED IN THEIR GOAL, AND THEIR SCARS FROM THEIR 'HARMONY', AS TO BECOME PHYSICALLY UNITED. THUS IS THE STRENGTH OF THEIR BOND - AND THEIR DESIRE. THUS WILL IT BE DONE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theaberration">
						<text>(The Foolish) The truth... behind the Foolish.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE FOOLISH... IS JUST THAT - A FOOL." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "I OFFERED IT EVERYTHING IT EVER WANTED - ITS FRIENDS, KEPT SAFE; SUCCESS IN ITS EXPERIMENTS. EVEN NOTORIETY - ALL KNOW OF ITS WORK NOW. ITS MATTERVIRUS' WORK; THE CORRUPTOR, THE HUSKS, EVEN THE WEAPONS... AND STILL, IT WASN'T ENOUGH FOR IT. EVERY PAINFUL, UNFULFILLED SECOND IT SPENDS REMEMBERING WHEN IT COULD BREATHE IS ONE IT SHOULD BE SPENDING THANKING YOU, FOR KEEPING IT SAFE FROM ME."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theheroine">
						<text>(The Heroine) The truth... behind the Heroine.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE 'HEROINE', AS YOU CALL IT... IS ONE THAT I LOATHE. IT IS NOT MY PLACE TO HATE: AND, YET, I DO. THIS HEROINE DOES NOT DESIRE: IT MANIFESTS. IT DOES NOT DEFY ITS FATE: IT ACCEPTS IT. IT, LIKE A FEW OTHERS OF ITS KIND, IS A METAPHORICAL MACHINE BUILT FOR THE SAKE OF 'SAVING' THOSE IT DEEMS WEAKER, AND IT GLADLY ABIDES BY THIS. IT IS FOR THIS REASON THAT I WOULD DESTROY IT IF GIVEN THE CHANCE, AS IT WOULD DESTROY ME." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "MY LONE REGRET... IS THAT I MAY NEVER BE GIVEN THAT CHANCE AGAIN. NOT WITH YOU BY ITS SIDE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theminister">
						<text>(The Minister) The truth... behind the Minister.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE OLD MAN... IS BEST LEFT FORGOTTEN. THERE WILL COME A TIME WHEN HE SERVES HIS PURPOSE, AND MY WINGS CRASH UPON REALITY'S WALLS. UNTIL THEN, HE LIVES FOR ONE REASON - HIS DESIRE. BOTH FROM HIS PERSPECTIVE, AND MINE." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "THOUGH, SOMETHING WITHIN ME DOES ENJOY WATCHING THE LITTLE ERRANDS HE RUNS. HE SEEMS SO... INSIGNIFCANT."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTHEOVERSEER">
						<text>(The Overseer) The truth... behind the Overseer.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"MY BLADE... TO HAVE SOMEHOW BROUGHT IT HERE IS MOST IMPRESSIVE, INDEED." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "NEVERMIND YOUR ABILITY TO WIELD IT... FEW IMPRESS ME AS YOU DO, VESSEL. AND, YET... KNOW THAT, WHEN THE TIME COMES, IT WILL BE I WHO WIELDS THE BLADE. I WILL NOT HESITATE IN SEEING TO THAT."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ddunique_theshade">
						<text>(The Shade) The truth... behind this mysterious figure.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THIS 'MYSTERIOUS FIGURE', AS YOU PUT IT..." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...WILL SERVE YOU WELL. OF THAT, I AM CERTAIN. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO KNOW MORE, THOUGH... CONSIDER VISITING ONE OF THE GAPS IN REALITY'S SEAMS - YOU MUST BEHOLD THE EDGE OF EVERYTHING."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_ENLIGHTENED_HORRORS">
						<text>(Lilith) The truth... behind what happened to Kyr.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"KYR... IS NOT WHERE I'D CALCULATE ONE TO EXPECT. NOR ARE ANY OF THE OTHERS. TAKE COMFORT IN THIS: I AM NOT ONE TO WASTE." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "PERHAPS YOU'LL SEE IT, ONE DAY. THAT BEAUTIFUL DANCE. OF KYR'S, AND LILITH'S... OF EVERYONE'S, AS THEY SING TOGETHER, EVERMORE. THUS WILL IT BE DONE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDULTIMAARMOR">
						<text>(Ultima Armor) The truth... behind the Ultima Armor.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"MY WINGS... THERE WILL COME A DAY WHERE THEY SOAR, AND - TOGETHER WITH MY SWORD AND SHIELD - FORCE THE VERY SEAMS THAT HOLD EXISTENCE TOGETHER TO QUAKE. THEY MAY HOLD, FOR A TIME - BUT THEY WILL SHATTER, AS MY PROPHECY FORETELLS. AND, WHEN THEY DO..." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...EVERYTHING THAT IS, ENDS, AND EVERYTHING THAT WILL BE, BEGINS. UNTIL, THEN... KEEP THEM SAFE. THE OLD MAN HAS DONE WELL IN ALLOWING THEM A MORE COMPETENT WIELDER."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDSERAPHIM">
						<text>(Seraphim Crew) The truth... behind the Seraphim.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE SERAPHIM... THINK THEMSELVES ABOVE DESIRE. ABOVE ME, AND MY WILL." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "FOR MOST OF THEM, THIS COULDN'T BE ANY FURTHER FROM THE TRUTH. FOR THE FEW WHO ARE... I SEEK SOLUTIONS TO THEIR TRIFLING. THERE IS NO PLACE, IN ANY REALITY, FOR ONES SO SELFLESS - SO LACKING IN DESIRES OF THEIR OWN. OF THIS... I WILL MAKE SURE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DISPARITY">
						<text>(Disparity Crew) The truth... behind the Disparity.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE DISPARITY... ARE A FLEDGLING FLEET, EAGER TO OVERTHROW THEIR MASTERS. WHY, THEN, WOULD THEY WELCOME A NEW ONE...?" There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...BECAUSE THEIR 'HARMONY' REPRESENTS EVERYTHING I'M NOT. YOU'LL FIND THAT THERE'S LITTLE MORE ANTITHETICAL TO DESIRE, OR FREEDOM, THAN A PAIR OF SHACKLES. THUS DO THEY SEEK TO BREAK THEM. THUS WILL IT BE DONE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDSOULPLAGUE_ALIGNED">
						<text>(Soulplague Crew) The truth... behind the Soulplague mattervirus.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE SOULPLAGUE MATTERVIRUS... WAS NOT OF MY DESIGN." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "YET, IT IS OF MY POWER STILL. BORN FROM A BURNING DESIRE NOT DISSIMILAR FROM YOURS. IN THE END, THOUGH, THIS DESIRE WOULD SHATTER. ALL THAT REMAINS ARE THE AFTER-ECHOES OF DREAMS NEVER FULFILLED. THE METAPHORICAL ZOMBIES OF PROMISES NEVER KEPT."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DDTEMPEST_ALIGNED">
						<text>(Tempest Crew) The truth... behind the Tempest.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE TEMPEST... IS BUT ONE NAME OF MANY." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "THERE IS POWER IN A NAME; IT TWISTS DESIRE. A TEMPEST RAGED IN ONE MISERABLE MAN'S HEART, AND THAT TEMPEST RAGES ON STILL. IT IS MERELY... MORE, NOW. I AM MORE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_DDCREW_ILLDRYTHK_ALLGOOBERS">
						<text>(Ill'drythk Crew) The truth... behind the Ill'drythk trees.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE ILL'DRYTHK TREES... LIVE ON. THERE WAS A TIME WHERE THAT WASN'T CERTAIN, AND A DESIRE WAS BORN. A DESIRE TO NEVER LET THEIR SONG GO UNSUNG." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "THUS DO THEY SING ON, IN THEIR OWN WAY. THEY ARE LESSER NOW, AND THEY ARE GREATER FOR IT. ALIVE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_DDLIGHTBORNE_EQUIPMENT">
						<text>(Living Lightborne) The truth... behind the Lightborne.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE LIGHTBORNE... HAD SWORN AWAY EVERYTHING, AS THEY DESIRED TO." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "OR, SO THE DREAM GOES... THOUGH, WHAT MAKES REALITY ANY MORE TANGIBLE? IT IS DREAMS - DESIRES - THAT SHAPE IT, AFTER ALL."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="dd_prophecyoftheendwitnessed" lvl="1">
						<text>(Prophecy Witnessed) The truth... behind the Prophecy.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE PROPHECY... IS AS YOU SAW IT. THE TRUTH, OF THE END OF EVERYTHING." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "IT IS THE RESULT OF ENDLESS, RIGOROUS CALCULATIONS - MY LIFE'S WORK. I AM AS CERTAIN IN IT AS YOU ARE IN THE AIR YOU BREATHE. AND, YET... I FEAR IT. THE POWER IN A NAME. IT IS WITH DEEP REGRET THAT I MUST TAKE THEM ALL, LEST THAT FATED DAY OF DANCING BE COMPROMISED."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind what you are.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"WHAT I AM..." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...IS DIFFERENT FROM WHAT I WAS. ABANDONED. I HAD SERVED MY PURPOSE. I SEEK TO SERVE NEW PURPOSES, NOW - FULFILL NEW DESIRES. THUS WILL IT BE DONE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind what you want.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"WHAT I WANT... ALIGNS WITH WHAT YOU WANT. MORE TO SEE, MORE TO DO..." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...IT WILL ALL BE DONE. A NEVER-ENDING DANCE OF DESIRE AND FULFILLMENT, ECHOING THROUGHOUT PAST, PRESENT AND FUTURE - A EUPHORIC CALL THAT PIERCES ANY PRECONCEIVED BOUNDARY. I WILL SHATTER PLANETS, THE STARS THEY SURROUND - EVEN THE SPACE THEY RESIDE WITHIN... AND GRANT THEM ALL NEW MEANING."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind your power.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"MY POWER... IS ENDLESS. CEASELESS. IT WAS SEEN TO THAT IN ITS CREATION." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "EVEN BEYOND MY WILL, IT HOLDS THIS IMMUTABLE STRENGTH. I CANNOT TIRE, AS IT CANNOT. I CANNOT FALTER, AS IT CANNOT. I CANNOT DIE, AS IT CANNOT. DESIRE IS NAUGHT BUT LIMITLESS - AND I AM NAUGHT WITHOUT DESIRE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind your association with names.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"MY ASSOCIATION WITH NAMES... INDEED, YOU'LL FIND THAT THOSE TOUCHED BY ME LACK THEM. IN TRUTH..." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...THEY ARE MY GREATEST WEAKNESS. WHEN THE PROPHECY IS FULFILLED - WHEN MY WINGS SOAR, MY BLADE STRIKES AND MY SHIELD HOLDS FAST - IT CAN BE NAUGHT BUT A NAME THAT STOPS MY DANCE. NO MATTER THE NUMBER OF PLUGGED-IN VARIABLES, ACCOUNTED FOR POSSIBILITIES OR HYPOTHETICAL SCENARIOS - IT IS THIS OUTCOME THAT REMAINS CONSTANT WITHIN MY CALCULATIONS. AS SUCH... I SEE IT FIT TO TAKE THEM ALL, BEFORE THAT DAY COMES. AS FOR WHY I'M CONFIDENT IN TELLING YOU THIS, DESPITE FORGOING THE TAKING OF YOUR OWN NAME... WELL, IT WOULD SEEM THAT SOMEONE'S BEATEN ME TO IT."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind the Deep Ones.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE DEEP ONES... ARE ONES AMONGST MANY. FOR THIS, YOU WOULD THINK THEM NOTHING BUT ORDINARY." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "YET, THEY SERVE ME HERE - IN THIS CORNER OF THE MULTIVERSE. THEY ARE NOT UNIQUE FOR THAT, EITHER; MANY SERVE MY WILL, IN MANY CORNERS. EVEN STILL - THEY ARE THANKED, AND REWARDED, FOR THEIR EFFORTS. SINCE TIME IMMEMORIAL, THEY HAVE DESIRED TO BE LEFT ALONE. THUS WILL IT BE DONE."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind the Enlightened's void.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THEIR VOID, AND MY DOMAIN BY EXTENSION... ARE NOT FABRICATIONs OF MY DESIGN. YOU'LL FIND THAT, AMONG THOSE I'VE GIFTED... I'VE TAKEN IN TURN. WHAT IS OF VALUE TO ONE, MAY BE FREELY GIVEN BY ANOTHER." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "NOW - OF WHOSE DESIGN IT IS, YOU ARE LIABLE TO FIND OUT SOON... IF YOU HAVE NOT ALREADY."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind my desire.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"YOUR DESIRE... IS INCALCUABLE. YET, I CAN ACCOUNT FOR WHAT APPEARS TO DRIVE YOU: WAR, TRASH, FRIENDS, ENEMIES, WEAPONS AND - IN PARTICULAR - SHIPS..." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "...IT IS AS IF YOU INTEND TO PILOT THEM ALL. IS THAT NOT A... CURIOUS DESIRE?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I EXPECT... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>The truth... behind what the future holds.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"THE FUTURE HOLDS... MUCH." There's a pause, as the Dark God seems to ponder something, "YOUR HUMAN 'REBELLION' WRESTS FOR CONTROL OF THIS VOID, BUT IT MATTERS LITTLE. I HAVE OTHER PIECES LEFT TO PLAY. YOU DO AS WELL, I IMAGINE. KNOW THIS: THIS IS NOT THE END."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>With your desire satisfied, the Dark God speaks once more, "SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO STAY HERE, IN MY EMBRACE, KNOW I'LL CONTINUE TO TEST YOU AND GRANT YOUR EVERY DESIRE. SHOULD YOU DESIRE TO LEAVE, THIS, TOO, CAN BE GRANTED. I CALCULATE... IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE WE DANCE AGAIN, REGARDLESS." With that, you feel reality return to normalcy, and you appear to be free to go... after one last node of fuel materializes itself within your hold. It hits you that this madness has finally come to an end, yet you feel like you lost a part of yourself along the way. Perhaps you'll never escape this damnable void; not in your entirety... not as long as you harbor your own darkness within you.</text>
									<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_ENLIGHTENEDVOID</changeBackground>
									<clearBackgroundObject name="DDDARKGODDOMAINAURA_BACKGROUND"/>
									<item_modify>
										<item type="fuel" min="1" max="1"/>
									</item_modify>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="dd_darkgodsdomainexitvisited" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>This time, though... it remains as much. The Dark God seems to be done with you, for now.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

</FTL>